Chapter 1339: Advanced Mutually Assured Destruction

The moment that the Subduing Tree King released the power of the World Tree, all the World Tree members on the battlefield glowed with a green light. As if they were on steroids, their overall combat power increased by a large amount.

The halo covered the entire army, and the flow of the entire battlefield immediately changed. The entire World Tree fleet was buffed, and many of the three Universal Civilizations' fleets that were originally in a stalemate suffered heavy damage.

Many Beyond Grade As were the first ones to feel the change. The increase in the strength of the World Tree's experts broke the stalemate. Many of the Beyond Grade As who were originally in a tug-of-war with their opponents were suddenly robbed of the initiative and fell into a disadvantage in the blink of an eye. Many of them fell into mortal danger.

Golden rays of light shot out frequently, landing on the Beyond Grade As who were in danger one after another, providing them with healing at critical moments, allowing a large number of Beyond Grade As to breathe a sigh of relief. However, the World Tree powerhouse also responded, using various methods to try to disperse or isolate the life force that shot over, preventing this recovery-type Esper from healing her comrades.

Hila was the only one who had a Soul Connection with Aurora. She could ignore the distance between them and receive Aurora's Dawn of Life instantly. It was as if she was bound with a healing source. The other Beyond Grade As naturally did not receive such treatment; although there was enough healing power, they needed to receive it first.

Although Aurora's Esper Ability was powerful, her current level was only that of an ordinary Beyond Grade A, so she could not ignore all kinds of obstructive methods This was even more of a test for her. Not only did she have to pay attention to the life state of every Beyond Grade A, but she also had to find a way to successfully heal her target.

Han Xiao used his quantum network vision to monitor the situation of the various areas. He could see the changes in the battlefield clearly.

"The halo of the entire army is still very powerful. Luckily, it can't be stacked. Otherwise, the effect of the five Great Tree Kings transforming together would be insane…"

Han Xiao's eyes were fixed on the Subduing Tree King.

Only by killing the Subduing Tree King would they be able to remove the halo of the enemy and turn the situation around. Otherwise, their total losses would skyrocket.

However, right at this moment, the Subduing Tree King, who had been strengthened after liberating the power of the World Tree, did not charge forward. Instead, he retreated into the layers of protection of the World Tree fleets and retracted the World Tree Roots. He had no intention of fighting Han Xiao.

Han Xiao's expression changed, and his emotions were in turmoil.

He had thought that after transforming, the Subduing Tree King would rush forward to continue fighting and try to defeat him. He did not expect the other party to directly avoid the battle after unleashing his potential.

If you didn't want to fight, you should have said so earlier. You were so imposing, it made my blood boil.

This is not good. If I don't get rid of him quickly, it will be troublesome…

Han Xiao felt helpless.

After transforming, the Tree King had an extremely high strategic value. He no longer took risks and hid in the fleet, continuously providing bonuses to the army. This was a safe method, but this rarely happened in his previous life. The Tree King had finally released the power of the World Tree, and his desire for battle also increased. Usually, he would fight to his heart's content.

If the other Tree Kings had chosen to avoid the battle, he would have been able to accept it, but this time, it was the Subduing Tree King…

Holy sh*t, a Pugilist is no longer stubborn. My youth is over!

Countless World Tree battleships protected their commander, the Subduing Tree King. Facing the countless cannons, Han Xiao felt his scalp go numb. Although he was confident in his tankiness, charging alone in a battlefield of this scale was too arrogant.

Furthermore, the Subduing Tree King was strong. He would not be able to deal with him amid the enemy camp in a short period of time. If he charged in, he would only be a target for focus fire.

"If you have the guts, don't ever come out."

Seeing this, Han Xiao left the Subduing Tree King behind and turned to attack the other World Tree experts.

If you don't stop me, I will kill your teammates!

Although the members of the World Tree had never cared about the casualties of their teammates, this battle was an exchange battle, and the Subduing Tree King cared about the capital used for this. Otherwise, the meaning of his transformation would be very limited.

However, Han Xiao's attention did not completely leave the Subduing Tree King. He was still focused on the other party's movements, preventing the Subduing Tree King from adjusting his tactics.

The Subduing Tree King did not stop him. From another perspective, it could also be said that he got rid of this annoyance and used his companions as bait to lure him away. He also used his superior combat strength to attack the other Beyond Grade As.

"Because this is an exchange battle, he doesn't want to waste time on an expert like me. He is targeting and killing the other high-level combatants; killing one means one win. Maybe that's what he thinks…"

Han Xiao guessed the intentions of the Subduing Tree King.

At the same time, from behind the protection of layers of fleets, the Subduing Tree King watched Han Xiao moving from one target to another.

After the battle just now, he judged that even if he transformed, he might not be able to take down this outsider with astonishing combat strength. Therefore, he suppressed his desire to attack and focused on the strategic goal. As a tree king who had fought many civilizations, he would not lose his cool so easily.

However, he also could not remain idle. Otherwise, if he allowed the outsider to kill his comrades, there would be no point in him trying to improve the exchange results with his transformation.

Since he could not stop the other side's strongest person, he could only make the same choice and change his target.

All sorts of thoughts flashed through his mind, and the Subduing Tree King turned around to look in the direction of the recovery-type Esper.

…

In one area of the battlefield, a group of Arcane Church troops had their defenses breached by the World Tree Assault Team, and the formation of the frigate was torn apart. The Glorious Sun Grade flagship in the middle was latched onto by the World Tree Assault Battleship, and the charge cabins bit onto the main ship one after another, penetrating through the armor and sending in batches of World Tree Supers to launch a boarding battle, attempting to snatch this flagship from within.

The interior of the flagship had turned into a chaotic battlefield, and bloody battles broke out in all the cabins and corridors. The guards on the ship were constantly resisting the World Tree Supers, and from time to time, new charge cabins would smash open new holes.

"Reinforcements! Reinforcements!"

One of the squad leaders pulled out the blade that had been stabbed into the enemy's body, and a large amount of blood splashed onto the armor. He had no time to wipe it as he requested reinforcements in the channel.

However, the next moment, a blurry shadow flashed past his eyes, and a huge force suddenly exploded on the side of his head. His head was gripped by a large hand and smashed into the wall. His body twitched a few times before stopping.

The owner of the hand was a burly World Tree officer. A large group of troops were massacring the soldiers inside the flagship, and they had already broken through the defense line.

"Head to the main control room!" the officer shouted and was about to lead the team forward.

However, right at this moment, the ground beneath their feet suddenly shook, and the wall nearby shattered, revealing half of a black charge cabin.

The hatch opened, and a group of army players rushed out. Without saying a word, they charged toward the World Tree squads. Battle erupted instantly.

After a fierce battle, the burly officer wiped out this team of players with his troops, but they also suffered quite a bit from their opponents' fearless and ferocious fighting style.

"Do these people not care about their lives?"

This officer frowned. He had seen people who were not afraid of death, but just now, this group of people had charged forward one after another, practically using their own heads in exchange for their injuries… In his opinion, there was only one possibility, and it was that the enemy had a strong belief and did not hesitate to exchange their lives for injuries.

However, as a member of the World Tree, he was not afraid of death at all. No one was afraid of death.

If you want to risk your life, I'll fight you. Who's afraid of who?

Without any time to rest and reorganize, this World Tree officer threw this matter to the back of his mind and was about to lead his troops forward.

However, at this moment, the sound of footsteps could be heard in the corridor ahead. Another batch of reinforcements had arrived. Their appearance and abilities were exactly the same as the team that had been wiped out earlier.

"Hmm? These people…"

The World Tree officer was shocked.

They had just killed this group of people, and now they appeared again. What was going on with this group of people? Could it be that they could not be killed and could revive like them‽

Before he could think about it, battle erupted once again. Due to the damage from the previous wave, the combat strength of this World Tree battle team had decreased, and they were wiped out by the same group of players. This officer was also surrounded and blasted into pieces—a similar scene played out in many battleships.

…

In the command ship of the three Universal Civilizations, Aurora used Dawn of Life a few times, but before it could reach her comrades who were in danger, the skill was scattered by the high-level combatants of the World Tree.

Aurora frowned and lowered her hand.

"I'm too far away from the battlefield. The opponent has plenty of time to react and can easily block my energy. This won't do. It's difficult for me to unleash my abilities. I need to get closer and shorten the distance."

Without waiting for Simon's reply, Aurora left the cabin and stepped into space. She turned into a golden stream of light and quickly approached the battlefield where the Beyond Grade As were.

This scene immediately attracted the attention of many World Tree powerhouses. A large number of high-level combatants immediately approached this Esper, but they were stopped by their opponents.

Not long after, Aurora stopped inside the main fleet of the three Universal Civilizations. Although she had closed the distance between them, she did not step onto the battlefield. She kept releasing the Dawn of Life, scattering rays of light. If the previous time the distance that the Dawn of Life needed to cross was ten, now it was at most two to three. The hit rate was higher than before.

Not only that, all the life forms on her side within a certain range would receive an increase in recovery speed. This was the passive halo of Aurora's Esper Ability after she entered the Beyond Grade A realm, and the range would increase with her grade. When she was on the command ship, the range of the halo was not enough to cover this area, but now that she was on this battlefield, her halo took effect and covered most of the Beyond Grade As on her side.

"This place is very dangerous. Don't come closer!" Hila saw Aurora immediately, and her expression changed.

Aurora turned a deaf ear and softly harrumphed.

Ever since she entered the Beyond Grade A realm, she had never experienced such a fierce battle. She had healed more than a hundred Beyond Grade As, and the amount of life energy consumed far exceeded the speed of replenishment. Her face gradually turned pale, and she felt like her body was being squeezed dry.

At this time, dozens of World Tree Roots suddenly attacked the main fleet from the side. Every root contained astonishing energy, and they quickly shattered a large number of battleships, creating a hole in the formation.

The next moment, the Subduing Tree King shot toward Aurora through the gap like a green beam of light.

He had been looking for an opportunity to kill this recovery-type Esper. The moment Aurora arrived at the frontline, he saw an opportunity. He used the fleet as cover to launch a sneak attack near the edge of the main fleet, vowing to eliminate the biggest factor that affected their battle strategy.

The World Tree roots seemed to have formed a gigantic war chariot, charging forward and sweeping away the obstacles in the way. At the same time, they blocked the concentrated fire of the fleet for the Subduing Tree King. With the protection of the World Tree's power, the Subduing Tree King dug his way into the main battleship.

Aurora seemed to be in a panic as she hurriedly retreated, condensing beams of holy light to hit the Subduing Tree King's body. However, it was like scratching an itch, unable to stop the Subduing Tree King's momentum.

In the blink of an eye, the Subduing Tree King appeared in front of Aurora as though he had teleported. A green light shot out from his arm and slashed at Aurora's head in a semicircle, as though he wanted to smash her into meat paste.

The pressure from a being two levels higher locked onto Aurora's body. Aurora seemed to have been stunned; she maintained a panicked expression without moving.

However, right at this moment, a violent mental shockwave exploded with Aurora as the center. It was extremely invasive and almost materialized.

The Subduing Tree King felt a sharp pain in his head, and his fist could not help but tilt to the side. The crescent-shaped fist lightly brushed past Aurora and shattered hundreds of battleships along the way.

Sorokin's figure separated from Aurora's body, and he appeared behind her like a double agent. He gently pressed his forehead, and his mental energy was constantly being released.

"Another protector?"

The Subduing Tree King's expression did not change. Just as he was about to get rid of Sorokin's mental power and continue attacking Aurora, something happened.

The panic on Aurora's face disappeared in an instant, and she regained her calmness as though she had expected it. The necklace she was wearing suddenly opened up, and the mechanical structure instantly covered her entire body, turning into a familiar mechanical suit.

Swoosh!

The next moment, there was a flash of light, and Aurora disappeared, leaving only Sorokin and a throne.

At the same time, Han Xiao's figure appeared out of thin air and replaced her original position. Without waiting for the Subduing Tree King to respond, he locked himself onto the Subduing Tree King, hanging on his body.

"I knew you wouldn't give up on attacking our milkmaid!"

Han Xiao's strong arms wrapped around the Subduing Tree King's neck, and he felt a huge force slamming into his chest. It was as though he was hugging a big, lively fish, and the Subduing Tree King was struggling in his arms.

The Subduing Tree King had always been hiding in the fleet, so Han Xiao did not have many opportunities to attack. He had deliberately made Aurora come out. Although it was a simple bait tactic, he believed that the World Tree experts would not be able to sit still. After all, the World Tree's battle strategy was different. Han Xiao thought about it from the other party's point of view and felt that only by cutting off the healer could he successfully carry out the exchange battle tactic. It was worth sacrificing some high-level combatants for this. There was a certain chance of luring the Subduing Tree King out with this move. Although the bait was straight, the desires of the other party did not stop. It was a simple and effective plan.

Without any expression on his face, the Subduing Tree King continued to slam his elbow behind at Han Xiao's stomach. Shockwaves spread from their fight.

Some of the World Tree Roots in the surroundings blocked the focus fire of the fleets, while other roots landed heavy blows on the two of them, wanting to pull Han Xiao away from the Subduing Tree King.

In terms of strength, the Subduing Tree King was still stronger, and Han Xiao could not lock him down. However, just as he was about to break free, mechanical structures quickly spread out from the point of contact between Han Xiao and him, turning into a King Armor that wrapped around him.

"Take this move, inseparable lovers!"

Han Xiao's Mechanical Force flashed, and the two of them disappeared.

Swoosh!

The next moment, the two of them appeared out of thin air in a strange empty area behind the formation of the three Universal Civilizations, as if the fleet had deliberately left this empty space.

The moment the two of them appeared, the prepared fleets around them activated their protective shields and quickly formed a spherical barrier that covered the entire area. They then retreated immediately.

The Subduing Tree King frowned and finally broke free from Han Xiao's embrace, sending Han Xiao flying with a kick. He looked around and realized that there were hundreds of strange mechanical devices floating in the area.

Just as he was observing, hundreds of mechanical devices suddenly lit up, as if hundreds of wormholes had been opened. The insides of the tunnels were filled with blinding light, emitting frightening energy waves.

Han Xiao stopped flying and narrowed his eyes.

"A few hundred improved Keys of Destruction are enough for you and me!"

Before the battle began, Han Xiao had specifically instructed the three Universal Civilizations to set up this type of trap and placed the throne in it.

The three Universal Civilizations had set up many similar traps before the battle, and they had tried to form a combination technique with the mechanisms of different Universal Treasures. This trap was one of the examples, and it was also the plan that Han Xiao had suggested—to use the teleportation of the King mechanical suit and the destructive power of the Key of Destruction to form a lethal zone.

Advanced Mutually Assured Destruction!

Buzz!

The next moment, a blinding light shot out from hundreds of tunnels, instantly filling the entire area and drowning the two of them.

Chapter 1340: Troublesome

"Vicious…"

The Beyond Grade As who were fighting could not help splitting some attention to Han Xiao's situation.

They were also aware of the trap formed by hundreds of Keys of Destruction. Looking at the expanding light, they could not help but sweat for Han Xiao.

Black Star's mutually assured destruction strategy was known for its shamelessness, but the power of hundreds of Keys of Destruction was not something that the mechanical army could compare to. Furthermore, it was restricted to a small area, and its power was highly concentrated.

Not only was he ruthless to the enemy, but he was also ruthless to himself. Everyone felt that Black Star's methods were too crazy. Was he not afraid of blowing himself up‽

Various thoughts flashed through everyone's mind. However, before the power of the explosion reached its peak, the protective shield surrounding this area suddenly cracked.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Dozens of World Tree Roots appeared, crazily digesting the power of the explosion while slamming at the protective shield from the inside. Immediately after, a green meteor slammed into the cracks of the protective shield.

Crack!

The shield shook, and a hole was blasted open. The charred Subduing Tree King rushed out.

The next moment, Han Xiao's figure also flew out after the Subduing Tree King to stop him, but he was sent flying by the World Tree Roots.

At the same time, because the protective shield was shattered by the Subduing Tree King, the power of the Keys of Destruction expanded from the inside. The chain reaction energy in the area lost control and expanded rapidly. Fortunately, the three Universal Civilizations had already left a large, empty area around the trap to guard against such a situation. The nearest fleet had plenty of time to retreat, and they also fired long-range attacks at the Subduing Tree King.

The Subduing Tree King could not care about anything else. He gathered the roots of the World Tree and turned them into an armor of sorts. Then, he hurriedly escaped into the distance to avoid the expanding energy cluster behind him, afraid that he would be swallowed again. Han Xiao stopped and continued to chase after the Subduing Tree King.

As the two of them moved away from the energy cluster, they clashed and fought. Suddenly, a bright light flashed, and the expanding energy cluster completely exploded. The shockwave shot out in all directions and hit the two of them. The huge impact threw the two of them away, much faster than normal flying speed.

After rolling however many times, Han Xiao barely managed to stop himself. There was not a single part of his body that did not hurt, and his entire body was covered in charred wounds. It was obvious that he was heavily injured. The Subduing Tree King, who had fallen not far away, was in a similar state, as though he had shed a layer of skin.

"You sure can run fast." Han Xiao's veins were throbbing. He moved his arms and legs, and the charred wounds fell one after another. His wounds gradually recovered, and his health slowly rose.

The Subduing Tree King was not dead, so he would not foolishly stay in the trap and take damage. At the critical moment, he also exploded with all his might, shattering the protective shield and escaping from the explosion area. Han Xiao had originally stayed behind to stall the Subduing Tree King, but after the other party broke free from the locked area, there were no more chances.

Han Xiao had used the King's teleportation to arrive, so he naturally dispelled the Mechanical Deity Form. The Mechanical Deity's descent was not instantaneous, so there was not enough time. Furthermore, with just the attributes of his main body, he could not immobilize a Pugilist at the level of the Subduing Tree King and was thrown to the side.

The prerequisite of Mutually Assured Destruction was to immobilize the enemy, but why would the target obediently stay in the area of focus fire? The Subduing Tree King ran fast, and he had the World Tree Roots to protect him. He escaped before the Keys of Destruction completely exploded, so he did not take full damage. Even Han Xiao could only chase after him.

However, the power of this wave was too terrifying. Even though the Subduing Tree King had escaped in time, he was still heavily injured. His body was riddled with wounds, and dozens of the World Tree Roots suffered the most damage. They also withered, and the power of the World Tree flowing in them was severely depleted. Its color dimmed, and it looked listless.

The Subduing Tree King looked down at his heavy injuries. Without any emotion, he calmly said, "Not a bad attempt. I didn't expect you to have the courage to take such risks."

Looking up at Han Xiao's injuries, a look of regret flashed past the Subduing Tree King's eyes.

He had been too careless. If he had known that the other party would take such a risk, he would not have escaped just now. He might as well have played along with the other party and dragged this outsider down with him to eliminate this dangerous opponent.

The thoughts of the members of the World Tree were different from those of ordinary people. The Subduing Tree King did not feel glad that he had escaped death. Instead, he felt it was a pity that he had missed out on an excellent opportunity.

"It's a pity I didn't manage to kill that recovery-type Esper…"

The Subduing Tree King shook his head.

This outsider clearly had the upper hand in terms of strength, but he still chose to take the risk. His intentions were clear—he knew that he would not be able to take him down in a short period of time, so he was not willing to fight for too long. Thus, he tried to get rid of the halo of the entire army as soon as possible to reduce his losses… The Subduing Tree King was well aware of this.

However, even if he had to do it again, he would still launch a surprise attack on that recovery-type Esper. The other party had taken the initiative to lure him with such bait, so it was worth a try. As long as he could make the other party lose their healer forever, the death of all the high-level combatants, including himself, would be worth it.

All sorts of thoughts flashed through his mind, but the Subduing Tree King's movements did not stop. He turned around and fled in another direction, not wanting to continue fighting.

He had been brought to the enemy's main fleet and was surrounded. There was no way he would be able to win in a battle there. His priority was extending his survival time. Only by escaping back to his own fleet to receive protection and support would he be able to escape danger and continue providing the halo of the entire army.

"Run again!"

Seeing this, Han Xiao gritted his teeth and immediately gave chase. Along the way, he quickly returned to his Mechanical Deity form, and the two of them fought once more.

A Pugilist was not scary, but scary was a Pugilist who was not stubborn. If the Subduing Tree King had lost his cool a little and was a little rash, this would have been much easier.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

The battleships of the three Universal Civilizations were not idle either. They provided a huge amount of firepower support, and a continuous stream of light cannons blasted toward the dozens of World Tree Roots that the Subduing Tree King had extended from all directions.

Han Xiao did not want to be trapped alone in the enemy's camp, and the Subduing Tree King did not dare either. The size of this army was enough to put individual powerhouses in danger. Not only did the focus fire cause the World Tree Roots to shatter, but it also restrained the Subduing Tree King.

Furthermore, the Subduing Tree King was heavily injured, and his condition had plummeted. Although his recovery ability was not bad, while entangled with Han Xiao and countless fleets, his injuries did not show any signs of improving.

The other World Tree experts and fleets wanted to rush over to provide support, but they were all stopped by the three Universal Civilizations' troops on various battlefields. The two sides fought intensely.

…

Swoosh!

Blazing red light rays streaked across, severing two withered World Tree roots.

The Subduing Tree King, who was protected by the roots, could not dodge in time. Half of the sole of his foot was cut off, and the texture of the cut was like a broken piece of wood, slowly twisting and growing, as if it was going to grow the foot again.

"Looks like this is where I'll be buried."

Subduing Tree King observed the encirclement and frowned.

He had tried to break out of the encirclement for a long time, but he was still trapped in the main force of the three Universal Civilizations. Most of the World Tree Roots that he had summoned after transforming were also destroyed, and his body was slowly approaching its end. He was already unable to fight Han Xiao head on.

With the strength he gained after releasing the World Tree's power, the Subduing Tree King could hold on for longer. However, the Mutually Assured Destruction tactic was effective, and the victory was decided. If he had not been heavily injured in this wave, the Subduing Tree King would not have been defeated so quickly.

At this time, the space around him started to vibrate. The Mechanical Deity's palm spun, and all kinds of force fields covered the Subduing Tree King's body, trying to lock him in midair.

The Subduing Tree King's face tightened, and he activated the weakened Pugilist flames to struggle free.

"You want to capture me alive?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao did not respond and continued to increase the strength of the force field.

The World Tree had already arrived at his doorstep, and the rough coordinates had been exposed. He could use the Spacetime Amber to try to seal the World Tree powerhouse and see if he could restrain the revival ability of the World Tree.

The only problem was that the World Tree expert would not obediently accept the seal.

Sensing Han Xiao's intentions, the Subduing Tree King had a calm expression as he resisted the force field's restrictions and slowly said, "Your resistance is futile. We will invade your civilization sooner or later. We have failed this time, but there will still be countless times. You can't stop the World Tree's iron hooves forever… I will be waiting to fight you again."

Before Han Xiao could react, the Subduing Tree King self-destructed without hesitation!

Bang!

A violent shockwave swept out, creating a large number of electric arcs on the Mechanical Deity's shield.

The remaining roots of the World Tree collapsed one after another, turning into light fragments and disappearing as though they had never existed.

The World Tree had fought in the universe for many years, and they had met many civilizations that wanted to capture their high-level combatants. Their thoughts were basically the same. They believed that capturing the World Tree experts alive and not killing them would prevent their revival and reduce the resources of the other party in a war of attrition. This was not new to the World Tree experts at all.

Although the Subduing Tree King did not know what means the enemy had to capture him alive, there was no need for him to take this risk. Seeing that the situation was not right and that there was no way to escape, he directly self-destructed and did not give them a chance. In this respect, the experience of the World Tree members was too good. Unless the difference in strength was too great or they had no choice, the World Tree members would rarely allow themselves to enter a near-death state where they were at the mercy of others. When they were weak, they would consider self-destructing and return to the embrace of the Mother Tree.

"What a troublesome enemy. The Tree Kings are indeed not easy to deal with…"

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

The creation of the Spacetime Amber required time, and the other party had self-destructed to prevent himself from being trapped. He had no way to deal with this. Although he had the upper hand against the Subduing Tree King, he could not crush him easily.

In the past, his opponents were normal people. They would either completely lose their combat capability and be unable to move, or they would rather be sealed than die in battle. No one would easily give up their life and self-destruct, so the Spacetime Amber had succeeded multiple times.

However, those of the World Tree had a completely different mindset. They had always liked to fight with their lives on the line, and self-destruction was a common occurrence for them.

You want to control me? Dream on, I'll simply die!

This was very tricky.

In his previous life, although the Spacetime Amber had been snatched away by the World Tree experts, the three Universal Civilizations did not give up on capturing the other party's high-level combatants alive. However, most of them had failed, and the biggest obstacle was the World Tree Race's self-destruction attitude.

"No matter what, the Tree King won't be revived for quite some time. At least the halo of the entire army has been removed."

Han Xiao calmed himself down and looked at the battle.

With the death of the Subduing Tree King, the green light on all the World Tree members dimmed again, and they lost the halo enhancement. The pressure on the three Universal Civilizations decreased instantly, and the battle was finally back to normal.

"… I can't do anything to the Subduing Tree King, but the difference in strength between ordinary Beyond Grade As and me is too huge. I might have a chance to seal a few."

Han Xiao looked at the other World Tree experts who were fighting, and his eyes sparkled.

…

At the same time, in the World Tree territory, the Tree King Palace, the Heart Tree King slowly opened his eyes and looked at the Executive Officers who did not participate in the expedition.

"The Subduing Tree King has turned into a seed."

Hearing this, the faces of the Executive Officers present darkened.

Although they had expected this outcome before the battle, they were still shocked when it actually happened. After all, a Tree King represented their top combat strength. The meaning of dying in battle was not small.

At this time, the Heart Tree King stood up from his throne, summoned a root, and stepped on it, preparing to leave.

"Aren't you going to continue watching?" an Executive Officer asked.

"The outcome of the battle has been decided. It seems like the attack this time has failed. The effect of the exchange tactic is limited, but we managed to probe out a large number of the enemy's trump cards, as well as that extremely crucial recovery-type Esper. I've gained enough."

"Understood… Where are you going now?"

Heart Tree King glanced at them and shook his head with a smile.

"I'm going to water the Subduing Tree King and make him grow faster."

Chapter 1341: Victory

"Beautifully done!"

Bang!

Seeing the Subduing Tree King explode into fireworks, Simon suppressed his excitement, choosing to smash the table instead.

Black Star was reliable. He had gotten rid of the enemy and stabilized the situation.

Without the halo of the entire army, the sudden advancement of the World Tree fleet during this period caused a large number of their fleets to fall into a bad situation.

Simon saw an opportunity and quickly calculated for a few seconds before decisively speaking in the command channel.

"Attention, all units! Pressure them!"

The three Universal Civilizations received the news and immediately took action. They worked together and gradually suppressed the enemy fleet.

Many of the World Tree Race experts saw that the Subduing Tree King had died in battle, and there was a slight commotion. Due to the loss of the halo amplification, their combat strength had decreased, and the advantage they had obtained before was quickly recovered by the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations.

Without the Subduing Tree King holding him back, Han Xiao returned to the battlefield where the Beyond Grade As were. He attacked the other World Tree experts like a tiger entering a pack of wolves, quickly bringing an overwhelming victory.

Han Xiao's goal was to use the Spacetime Amber to seal the World Tree experts, but it did not go so smoothly. Before the Subduing Tree King self-destructed, he had already informed all the high-level combatants of the World Tree on the mental network. When the World Tree experts felt that they could not hold on any longer, they self-destructed without hesitation.

The World Tree had suspected that this was the home civilization of the intruder, so they naturally would not make such a low-level mistake. They did not send any foreign experts to participate in the battle, still guarding against the virtual purification that they had yet to figure out.

Even so, Han Xiao had the upper hand in terms of strength. After many attempts, he successfully managed to seal a target. Before the other party self-destructed, he beat him up with lightning speed and swallowed him in the amber.

However, this made the self-destruction of the other World Tree experts even more decisive. Some of them even hugged a Beyond Grade A and tried to blow up their opponents.

With the death of the Subduing Tree King, the balance of the high-level combatants completely shifted to the three Universal Civilizations' side. Balls of explosions lit up the battlefield.

Not long after, the last Holy Tree Emissary also self-destructed and died. Only then did the Beyond Grade As retreat from the battlefield and return to the formation behind the three Universal Civilizations. They stepped into the command ship, and almost everyone was injured.

Simon stepped forward and exhaled with respect.

"Thank you for your hard work. Take a rest first. However, Mechanics still have to provide technical support."

Han Xiao nodded. "Okay."

This battle was still underway, but it was time for the main fleet to act. The missions of these high-level combatants were basically completed.

"This victory is all thanks to you guys," Simon said. "We achieved a complete victory in the high-level combatants and killed a hundred Beyond Grade As on the World Tree. We will talk about this after the battle officially ends."

With that, he turned back to the command center and continued to control the flow of the battle.

The Beyond Grade As looked at each other and remained silent.

Because of Aurora and Black Star, they had only paid the price of six Beyond Grade As to wipe out a hundred Beyond Grade As from the World Tree. From the battle losses alone, it was a complete victory.

However, life was not a number. When they thought about how these six companions had been chatting with each other not too long ago, many Beyond Grade As felt sad.

The ones who were sacrificed this time were someone else, but the World Tree would always make a comeback. Any of those present could be the next to die.

A similar thought appeared in everyone's mind.

Although they hoped that they would be able to resurrect through Han Xiao's Sanctum, no one dared to guarantee when it would be their turn.

Many of them were filled with worry about the uncertain future.

Han Xiao turned around and took in everyone's expressions. He said, "Aurora, you did well this time. If not for you, we might have lost half of our total members."

Hearing this, everyone turned to look at Aurora, and gratitude flashed in their eyes.

No matter what, most of the people present had been saved by Aurora more than once today, and they owed her a favor.

"I only did my part."

Aurora took a deep breath and imitated Han Xiao's humility.

Her face was rather pale. This high intensity battle had drained her life force too much, and her milk was almost used up.

Hila felt her heart ache a little, but her face remained expressionless.

Han Xiao patted Aurora's shoulder, looked at everyone, and said, "This battle will take at least a few days. Everyone is injured. Go and rest for now."

Hearing this, no one declined, and they left with their own thoughts, leaving only the direct Beyond Grade As, Manison, Kasuyi, and the other important members of the association.

Manison looked at the four blocks of Spacetime Amber beside him. There were four World Tree powerhouses sealed inside.

"What do you plan to do with these four?"

"Seal them first and store them in the interception circle. I'll leave a Throne here to supervise it."

Han Xiao sighed.

He had succeeded four times in using the Spacetime Amber, all because of the huge difference in strength. It allowed him to forcefully control the target before sealing them with the Spacetime Amber. Thus, the four high-level combatants of the World Tree that he had captured were all ordinary Beyond Grade As, while there were dozens of similar failures. It was an accomplishment for him to have succeeded even four times. The Executive Officer of the World Tree, the Ancestral Spirits, and the Head of the Army were all extremely powerful, and they were extremely difficult to deal with. They had self-destructed too decisively, so he could not catch them at all.

The six Beyond Grade As who died on their side were mainly killed by the self-destruction tactics of the World Tree. The dead were ordinary or fragile Beyond Grade As who died on the spot. Even Aurora could not save them in time.

Although he had won the battle between high-level combatants, Han Xiao had also fully felt how difficult it was to deal with the World Tree experts. It was not just their strength that was an issue but also their synchronized mental network and fearless attitude.

Even though he had many advantages now, the battle-hardened World Tree was not easy to deal with. He had his own methods, and the other party had all kinds of countermeasures.

"Although the Spacetime Amber has already proven its characteristics, we still have to prevent the World Tree from cracking its principles. What is impossible for us might not be the case for the World Tree."

Manison nodded. He was not confident that the World Tree would be unable to crack the Spacetime Amber.

Han Xiao did not say anything and glanced at Hila, gesturing with his eyes.

Seeing this, Hila nodded slightly.

This was a secret signal between the two of them. Seeing Hila's reaction, Han Xiao knew that Hila had been using the Underworld to collect the souls of the deceased. She should have gained a lot, but it was not the time to check.

"World Tree…"

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the battle again, his eyes shining with an unknown light.

…

"Our high-level combatants have achieved a complete victory. Only six of them died, and Black Star even used the Spacetime Amber to capture four enemies…"

In the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations, the three leaders were currently receiving reports from the frontlines and discussing in low voices.

"Black Star is as strong as ever. Luckily, we have the association's help. Otherwise, our direct lineage would not have been able to deal with so many enemies." Louis shook his head.

"Only six people died in battle. Their results are better than I expected." Marbruce exhaled.

"After destroying this wave of attacks from the World Tree, their next wave shouldn't be so quick. They've bought us more time." The Pope also nodded.

Although the three of them hoped to damage the Beyond Grade As of the association, they were still united against a common enemy. Seeing that their losses were low, they were also happy.

"However… Hila's Underworld is collecting the souls of our soldiers. This is a problem," Louis said in a deep voice.

Marbruce lowered his voice. "Now is not the time to be calculative."

The existence of the Underworld was no longer a secret, and the three Universal Civilizations had known about it before the war. They knew that Hila might absorb the soldiers and talents that they had lost in the war, but in the current situation, they had no choice but to turn a blind eye.

This was akin to poaching. However, for a large number of soldiers that would have actually died in battle, entering the Underworld gave them a second lease of life. This was equivalent to reducing the losses of their war capital. Since this was a special situation, the three Universal Civilizations could only acquiesce.

The three of them were also worried that Hila would use the Underworld to take away the Beyond Grade As who had died in battle, but currently, not many Beyond Grade As were willing to become heroes who could not be free, with most of them choosing to believe in the Sanctum Revival.

No matter what, this was a hidden danger, but it was not the time to be calculative. The main problem was dealing with the World Tree Civilization, and the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations could do nothing about the Underworld.

…

The battle between the two fleets lasted a week, and the battlefront had already been stretched to the extreme.

The reinforcements from the three Universal Civilizations came in an endless stream, and the rest of the Beyond Grade As would attack together from time to time, gradually turning the tide of the battle in the three Universal Civilizations' favor.

The expedition army of the World Tree had been devoured by batches, and they had changed their tactics when the situation was not looking good. They no longer attacked head-on and split up in an attempt to create loopholes in the interception network with their large numbers.

At this stage of the war, this wave of attacks had already been declared a failure. To the three Universal Civilizations, the only thing left was to clean up the mess.

Although they had defeated the enemy with a small loss and won the battle, the upper echelons were not happy. The revival ability of the World Tree shrouded their hearts like dark clouds.

However, no matter how heavy their hearts were, the officers still had to focus on commanding the troops to clean up the mess.

Seeing that the battle had come to an end, the three Universal Civilizations finally sent the frontline battle report back to the galactic society, promoting this victory and boosting the hearts of the people.

Chapter 1342: If You Have Milk, You're a Mother

It was no secret that the three Universal Civilizations were resisting the first wave of an invasion. The Galactic Society had known about it the moment the three Universal Civilizations mobilized the various armies and the armed forces of the various civilizations. Because this battle was not broadcast live, no intelligence was sent back. After many days of fermenting, the countless galactic residents that were headed to the central region of the explored universe were on tenterhooks, afraid that they would see news of the three Universal Civilizations being defeated the next day.

While the entire galactic society was in a state of panic, the three Universal Civilizations' Foreign Affairs Departments, which had been silent for many days, finally reported the results of the battle to the galactic society and announced this great victory.

The three Universal Civilizations claimed that the attacks of the foreign enemies had been repelled, and they put up a more detailed battle report, announcing the damage ratio of many troops. Among which, the most eye-catching was the battle results of the high-level combatants. With just six people as the price, they had killed more than a hundred Beyond Grade As of the enemy. This result made countless people's eyes light up, and they were secretly shocked.

Although the three Universal Civilizations had won the battle, they had also lost a fleet of ten billion. Even so, it was still a commendable victory, and the losses were far lower than the enemy's. However, the battle statistics of Beyond Grade As were many times more outstanding, and they were the troops with the lowest casualty rate.

After successfully annihilating the expeditionary army, this great victory boosted the hearts of the people. Most of the frightened galactic residents heaved a sigh of relief, and the panic and fear in their hearts gradually faded. They were filled with excitement and joy.

The public opinion that was originally filled with all kinds of worries and panic changed, becoming a trend of praising the three Universal Civilizations. It was as if loyal supporters had sprouted everywhere overnight.

The shocking achievements of the Beyond Grade As were naturally popular topics discussed by the ordinary people, and they were almost unanimously praised. Many galactic residents praised them for their reliable individual strength, as though they had forgotten the hate speeches they used to attack the association. The association seemed to have gone from 'opposing class who abused their special rights as they wished' to become 'trustworthy guardians of the galactic society', and their image had a 180-degree change.

During internal conflicts, many galactic residents did not like the Beyond Grade As and did not stop complaining. However, when faced with a complete victory over the enemy, the galactic residents were proud of their superior combatants. Their long-standing hatred and resentment seemed to have been selectively forgotten, and their attitude changed very smoothly.

Of course, there were also those who were deeply rooted in resentment. However, they all cowered at the moment and did not dare to express their usual opinions. They shrunk their necks and silently accepted the protection. Right now, the enemy had yet to retreat, so they did not dare put down their chopsticks and curse.

However, for the majority of the galactic residents, when danger came, they would cheer for whoever protected them from invasion. Their unanimous feelings toward the outside temporarily suppressed the class conflict within.

…

"A great victory, is it…"

Dillon did not think so.

The huge virtual screen was showing the news reports of the three Universal Civilizations, and the room was filled with Revivors who had joined the association.

Due to the previous disagreements, many revivors did not respond to the call and did not participate in this battle. They stayed in the explored universe and did not know how intense the battle at the frontline was. They could only watch the battle reports through the news.

"Six people sacrificed in exchange for more than a hundred casualties. This shouldn't have happened. It seems like Aurora's ability has already reduced the casualties to a very low level." Beiger nodded.

"No matter how low their losses are, the six people who died in battle are still dead. There are also members of the association among them. They only lost their lives because they believed Black Star's nonsense. Serves them right!" Dillon curled his lips.

Everyone shook their heads, speechless.

How could such a fierce war not kill people? The sacrifice of those Beyond Grade As was unavoidable, but from an emotional perspective, everyone still felt that it was a pity.

"Don't say that. After all, they sacrificed themselves to fight against the enemy. Furthermore, with Black Star's sanctum reviving, they can still be resurrected." Beiger sighed.

"Humph, so what if they can be revived through the Sanctums? It's just one chance, and they wasted it. When they come back to life, they will have the same thoughts as us sooner or later," Dillon said with disdain.

Beiger had no way to refute that. He shook his head helplessly and said, "Don't we still have the Underworld to protect us?"

"Tsk, do you really like losing your freedom? I even suspect that Black Star is urging us to join the battle. His other goal is to let us die in battle and enter the Underworld, indirectly strengthening his forces. Humph, a bad guy!" Dillon snorted.

"Black Star shouldn't be such a person." Beiger shook his head.

"Are you very close to him? Can you guarantee what he's thinking?" Dillon demanded impatiently. "Whose side are you on? If you like speaking up for Black Star so much, why don't you just roll behind him? Why are you obediently accepting whatever sh*t he does?"

"What are you saying? Furthermore, Black Star doesn't need to sh*t…"

Beiger's mouth twitched, but he was not angry. He was already used to Dillon's foul mouth.

Dillon retracted his gaze and snorted. "This is only the first wave of attacks. The enemy will invade again, and more Beyond Grade As will die in battle. If we join the battle, we will end up like this sooner or later. It's not easy to obtain a new life, so I'm not willing to work for the three Universal Civilizations."

"Are you planning to watch the enemy invade?" Beiger frowned.

"Humph, I'm not going to get involved in this. If the three Universal Civilizations can win, I'll stay. If they can't, where can't I go in the universe? My Elven Holy Land is gone, and my consorts have been divided. What's there for me to miss?" Dillon scratched his nose.

"Okay, okay, you're good."

Beiger was speechless. He shook his head and walked out of the room. He hesitated for a moment before taking out his communicator and dialing Oathkeeper's number.

A few seconds later, the call connected, and Oathkeeper's face appeared on the screen.

"What is it?"

Beiger hesitated for a moment before saying, "Regarding Black Star's appeal, I would like to ask for your opinion."

He was actually a little confused as well. After all, Dillon was not completely unreasonable. For the Revivors, it was not a bad choice to be alone. However, Beiger still could not make up his mind, so he wanted to ask Oathkeeper for his opinion. Oathkeeper's persistence over the years had earned him the respect of all the Revivors. After all, he was once a comrade and an old friend of many years. He had a great position in their hearts and was more trustworthy than Black Star.

Oathkeeper also knew that the revivors did not respond to Han Xiao's call, so he immediately understood what Beiger was asking. He pondered for a moment and slowly spoke.

"I suggest you join the battle and give it your all."

"…"

Seeing that Beiger did not say anything, Oathkeeper continued. "I know you're worried about the risks, but Black Star has his own plans, and he does not treat you as sacrifices. The Underworld is not all of his trump cards, and he has prepared other paths of retreat for you. Furthermore, you guys have made a mistake. The compromise with the three Universal Civilizations does not mean that the battle between the Beyond Grade As has ended. Black Star is still working hard for this goal, and external enemies are an opportunity."

"I don't really understand." Beiger frowned.

"It's not convenient for me to explain this matter too clearly. If you're willing to believe me, I'll give you a piece of advice. Don't be afraid of death. Black Star will always have a way to make you open your eyes again." Oathkeeper shook his head.

Without Black Star's approval, it was not convenient for him to reveal the truth of the unlimited Sanctum Revivals. Furthermore, it would be suspicious if he told the truth.

Oathkeeper had heard about the plan from Han Xiao and knew that Black Star needed a Revivor who dared to die in battle as an example. If all the Revivors did not participate in the battle, Black Star would lack the 'material' to show the truth of the Sanctum Revival.

However, it was not suitable to directly tell the Revivors to die. After all, even if there was a Sanctum Revival, their strength would decrease after reviving. Not many people were willing to do so, and people's hearts were always fickle, so they could only urge them to join the battle. After all, as long as they went to the frontlines, Oathkeeper believed that Black Star would definitely be able to find a way to get the Revivors killed.

"…Let me think about it."

Beiger hung up the communication and pondered over Oathkeeper's hint. After pondering for a while, he made up his mind.

Oathkeeper's suggestion definitely had a reason. It was better to go to the frontline to take a look. Even if they were to participate in the battle, there was still Aurora on the battlefield, so the danger should not be that high.

…

In the large conference room that blocked the main base, many Beyond Grade As who were participating in the battle gathered. At the conference table were Simon and the other commanders, as well as the remote projections of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders.

After many days of fighting, this World Tree expedition team had been defeated, and the three Universal Civilizations were only left with the job of cleaning up the mess. The three leaders had arrived to reward these Beyond Grade As.

The direct Beyond Grade As had their own internal rewards, but the rewards for the association members were different. They were basically directly given material rewards. This was an agreement that Han Xiao had made with the three Universal Civilizations long ago, since the association would not provide high-level combatants for free.

"…Your contributions have been recorded. According to the agreement that His Excellency Black Star has made with us, we will compensate you accordingly. This is the list of resources we have reserved…"

Marbruce called out the virtual screen and opened a list interface. Various exchangeable items were displayed on it for everyone present.

Han Xiao took a look and nodded slightly. Many of the items there were strategic resources that were not open to the public under normal circumstances. This time, all of them were opened for exchange without hiding anything.

This method was basically the same as the players exchanging faction contribution points for equipment, but the difference was that many Beyond Grade As did not have an interface to display their contribution points.

At this moment, Louis pondered for a moment and said, "In order to express our sincerity, you can choose the different Universal Treasures in our inventory as remuneration based on your merits. It will be the same in the future."

Hearing this, the eyes of many Beyond Grade As lit up with joy.

Many people did not even have a single Universal Treasure, but now that they had a channel to acquire them, they were pleasantly surprised. Even those who had Universal Treasures did not mind having more of such equipment.

"Yo, you've invested a lot."

Han Xiao raised his brows.

Every Beyond Grade A participating in the battle would have at least one, and it was not a small number. Furthermore, they would be able to obtain the qualifications every time they fought in the future. Even if the three Universal Civilizations had a lot of Universal Treasures in their inventory, they would not be able to afford such a production. After all, Beyond Grade As could choose for themselves, and they would definitely start choosing from the best.

However, on second thought, Han Xiao understood the three Universal Civilizations' plan. In any case, they had to distribute Universal Treasures to the participants every time they fought, so they might as well give out their ownership rights to all of them. At the same time, they could also motivate the Beyond Grade As to fight. After all, if the Beyond Grade As were gone, there would be no point in keeping some Universal Treasures for their own use.

The other three Universal Civilizations might have another idea, which was to use the reward to attract the Revivors of the association to join the battle. Han Xiao knew what kind of sh*t they were brewing the moment they stuck their butts out.

However, there was no need to stop them. Han Xiao was also glad that the three Universal Civilizations were willing to bleed themselves. He could not possibly ask the other Beyond Grade As who had contributed to the war to reject this reward.

Everyone rubbed their palms and picked out the Universal Treasures they liked on the list.

However, there were also a few Beyond Grade As who made different choices. They surrounded Aurora and smiled kindly.

"We owe you a favor this time. Do you have any Universal Treasures you want? I can help you choose."

"Eh?" Aurora was stunned, waving her hands. "There's no need for that."

"There's no need to be modest. You deserve this."

Milizaus' magic power avatar revealed a loving smile. As a huge target, be it the enemy's hit rate or his own healer's hit rate, it was extremely high for him. This time, he was the happiest being healed by Aurora.

"Ah, I really don't have any needs." Aurora was helpless.

This was the truth. With a treasure like the Underworld and a boss that could mass produce Universal Treasures, why would she need to farm anything herself? She really did not need the Universal Treasures of the three Universal Civilizations.

The Beyond Grade As around looked at him with envy. This was understandable.

After all, this battle had already proved that if they wanted to survive on the battlefield, the healer was the most important. Some Beyond Grade As would rather give up the chance to acquire Universal Treasures to please Aurora.

Furthermore, this nanny's healing ability was limited. If he did not build a good relationship with her, the amount of milk he would receive after the battle would not be comparable to others.

Han Xiao glanced at Aurora, who was the center of attention.

"Tsk, so this is what it means to be a mother with milk…"

After cursing in his mind, Han Xiao looked at the list casually, but he did not find anything that could move his heart.

He had a deep foundation now, so he did not care too much about the Universal Treasures provided by the three Universal Civilizations.

The main storyline branch mission of this battle had been completed. Although it was a drop in the ocean to him, the EXP reward this time was very rich according to the players' standards. Countless army players had received a large amount of EXP, which was the biggest benefit to him.

The faster the players reached the maximum level, the quicker they would be able to spend their experience elsewhere, which would lead to his own experience reserves filling up.

Han Xiao thought to himself as his eyes sparkled.

After defeating the enemy this time, a large number of high-level combatants will need time to revive. With me here, the World Tree probably won't dare send an expert from another race over, so their next wave of attacks won't arrive so soon… Should I take this opportunity to go to the Sanctum?

The time flow in the Sanctums was different from in the main universe. The last time he entered the Third Sanctum, he had spent three months. Even if his authority in the First Sanctum was higher, he would spend quite a bit of time. Taking the chance while the World Tree did not invade, it would be good for him to enter a Sanctum. He would probably not miss out on any matters.

Han Xiao planned to enter the Sanctum this time not only to revive the six victims but also to revive many Beyond Grade As in history. For example, the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance. This was a deal that he had agreed to. When the World Tree revived the high-level combat units, he would naturally have to expand the size of his people.

It's a pity that the Revivors did not participate in this war, or I would have been able to reveal the truth of the Sanctum Revival… However, it's fine if I don't expose it now. The war is still in its early stages, and if I expose it too early, the three Universal Civilizations might have other thoughts. When the two sides are fighting so hard that they don't have extra energy to think about anything, maybe it will be the best time to expose it…

However, he still had to use Destiny's Child to monitor it and confirm that the World Tree would not take any further actions for the time being. Only then would he be able to enter the Sanctum with ease.

…

Meanwhile, in the Tree King Palace of the World Tree Civilization…

"The four high-level combatants have been captured alive. The mental network has been cut off. Although the World Tree connection still exists, we can no longer monitor their condition…"

Executive Two Leaf was expressionless as he reported the situation of the four World Tree powerhouses that were sealed by the Spacetime Amber.

The Heart Tree King narrowed his eyes and revealed an interested expression.

"Interesting. Does the enemy this time have such a method to capture us alive? It's not simple. Maybe it's a Space Wonder item… Can we track it?"

"Yes, the Mother Tree's connection power is still transmitted to the individual, but it is isolated by something unknown and cannot penetrate. It is unable to sense the state of those four people. Following the broken information state trajectory, we can confirm that the coordinates of those four people are near the expeditionary army battlefield."

"Hmm, try to take them back next time and see what caught them alive. Throw them into the mother tree for analysis." The Heart Tree King waved his hand.

"When will the next operation begin?" the executive asked.

"There's no hurry. The enemy's recovery-type Esper is very difficult to deal with, which is why the effect of this exchange is not good. However, no matter how poor the battle results are, it's still an exchange. The enemy has already lost a few high-level combatants, so we have the advantage."

The Heart Tree King rubbed the armrest and paused before continuing.

"Let's wait for the high-level combatants on our side to revive first. We need to plan how to get rid of that recovery-type Esper. If we don't kill this person, our strategy will be greatly reduced… If the method really doesn't work, then let's not waste time and just launch an all-out attack. As long as we attack their territory, the mother tree will be able to eat to its heart's content!"

Chapter 1343: Fertile Underworld

Not long after, the Beyond Grade As finished selecting the reward that they wanted. The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations gave them some more encouragement before ending the meeting.

The group walked out of the room and returned to their own activity room. At this time, Han Xiao clapped his hands twice, attracting everyone's attention.

"Everyone, I have something to announce. I might be carrying out the Sanctum Revival soon and bring back the six Beyond Grade As who died in this battle."

Everyone was stunned for a moment before becoming excited.

"So fast?" Kasuyi blinked in surprise.

He was someone who knew about the Sanctums and knew that opening a Sanctum was not easy. He had always thought that Han Xiao would wait for more people to die before pulling them back. This was more cost-effective. However, only six of them had died, and he was going to use the Sanctum Revival. This was out of his expectations.

"It's alright. This is part of the plan." Han Xiao waved his hands.

The intense battle this time made many Beyond Grade As tense. Using the Sanctum Revival to pull back the victims could boost their morale. After all, although the revival of the Beyond Grade As of history was shocking, it was better to let everyone witness the revival of the dead.

At the same time, this was also an opportunity for him to show his stance. The fact that he could not wait to revive the sacrificial victims would make most people feel at ease, and they would feel that they would receive the same treatment. After all, the other Beyond Grade As did not know the price of the Sanctum Revival, and the more relaxed Han Xiao acted, the more confident they would be.

"I don't think those six guys want to revive so quickly. Maybe they'll die again. Why don't we let them sleep a little longer?" Sun Hunter muttered softly.

Han Xiao turned to glance at him, and Sun Hunter immediately shut up.

Hearing this, many Beyond Grade As had strange expressions.

In the eyes of everyone, the Sanctum Revival only gave them one chance. It would be best for them if they could avoid some battles during the time of death, but from the perspective of others, they could not wait for the dead experts to come back and share the pressure.

There were also some Beyond Grade As who could not help but glance at Hila. If not for Black Star's reliable performance, they would have even thought that Black Star's goal of reviving the dead was to quickly bring these people who had used the Sanctum to the Underworld.

Han Xiao took in everyone's expressions and could naturally guess what they were thinking. "Anyway, it's settled. I'm not only going to revive the victims this time, but I'm also planning to revive some historical experts and expand the size of the high-level combatants to share more of the pressure."

"I see. That's not bad." Everyone nodded in agreement.

Beep beep beep…

At this time, Han Xiao's communicator rang. He took it out and saw that it was a call from Beiger.

Han Xiao picked up the call.

"Beiger, why are you looking for me?"

Beiger got straight to the point. "Black Star, the Revivors and I have decided to fight on the front line with you guys and respond to your call to participate in the war."

"Eh? Why so suddenly?" Han Xiao was stunned.

The Beyond Grade As around stopped talking and listened.

Due to the difference in their opinions, the Revivors did not participate in the war and watched them fight the enemy at the frontlines. Although they did not say anything, they naturally had some opinions about the Revivors. Even if they understood the mentality of the Revivors, they were still dissatisfied.

Although Black Star said that he would wait for the revivors to change their minds, in the eyes of everyone, the chances of the revivors responding to the call was too low. Therefore, everyone was very curious about why Beiger suddenly changed his attitude.

Could it be that the rewards from the three Universal Civilizations had attracted them? That should not be the case. These revivors had seen all kinds of good things. Furthermore, the reward had been distributed just earlier, so the news should not have been sent back. Could it be that the huge victory and extremely low losses had given the revivors confidence?

"Ahem, I've been thinking about it recently. Since we're all comrades of the Beyond Grade A united front, we need to advance and retreat together. We can't just watch you guys fight with your lives on the line. Furthermore, you're right, Black Star. We're all born in this galaxy, and it's not time to abandon our homeland. I've decided to do my part."

Han Xiao was skeptical. While these words sounded righteous, he did not believe them. He did not think that these old people would suddenly become hot-blooded.

Did Oathkeeper give him a hint?

Han Xiao put on a gratified expression and said with a smile, "You made the right choice. Like I said, no matter when you change your mind, you're welcome to fight alongside us."

"That's great." Kasuyi smiled.

Everyone also expressed their welcome. With Beiger's declaration, the dissatisfaction of the Beyond Grade As present toward the Revivors disappeared, and they felt much better.

This time, Han Xiao asked, "By the way, did Dylan say anything?"

"He said you sh*t… Ahem, he said he doesn't want to die," Beiger said helplessly. "Same old, same old. I don't think he will change his mind."

"Forget it then. Let's not bother with him for now."

Han Xiao shook his head. After understanding what had happened to Dylan, he could understand why Dylan was so determined not to help the three Universal Civilizations. After all, due to the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, this guy was in such a terrible state that it was beyond appalling.

After giving a few words of encouragement, Han Xiao hung up the call, walked out of the room, found a private location, and dialed Oathkeeper's number.

Very soon, Oathkeeper's face appeared on the screen. Han Xiao got straight to the point.

"Did you say something to Beiger?"

"Oh? Is he preparing to fight?" Oathkeeper nodded. "I did give him a hint…"

After Han Xiao heard that, he smiled and said, "You're quite good. Although I don't need the Revivors to be the 'material' to reveal the truth of the Sanctum Revival, I don't mind having more of them."

These revivors were not the only sources to reveal the truth of the Sanctum Revival. Han Xiao had long considered the possibility that these revivors would not participate in the battle, and he had already made many preparations. This time, the direct descendants who had entered the Sanctum Revival and brought back a portion of the advanced civilizations were actually a backup plan. After all, the direct descendants' mentality was different, and they would most likely continue to accept the orders of the civilization and risk their lives to enter the battlefield.

This way, when these revived direct descendants died in battle, he would have the materials to show the truth of the Sanctum Revival. He did not need the previous revivors.

Although Beiger had decided to join the battle, Han Xiao did not intend to change his plan. He still had to make more than one plan.

These thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind, and he asked the most important question.

"How's the collection of the Sanctum Keys?"

"Not bad. The resources given by the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance have made up for many materials. The First Sanctum key has already been collected, and the Third Sanctum key is almost complete as well. Other than the Sixth Sanctum, the other Sanctum keys have reached more than 75%…"

Oathkeeper sent the data, and Han Xiao could not help but smile.

Although there was only one complete Sanctum Key, it did not mean that the progress would be reduced to zero after it was used up. Other than some materials that were extremely difficult to obtain, most of the other materials were repeated. The three Universal Civilizations had quite a lot of them in their inventory and provided them in bulk.

Han Xiao looked at the list of materials. Even if he used up the First Sanctum key, his progress would only fall back to 70% to 80% at most. As long as he obtained a few more crucial rare materials, he would be able to obtain another key to the First Sanctum.

"Not bad, not bad…" Han Xiao muttered subconsciously.

Seeing that he was focusing on the list, Oathkeeper's eyes suddenly flashed.

Black Star was distracted. This was a good opportunity!

"Humph, work hard. On behalf of the organization…"

Click.

Without waiting for Oathkeeper to finish, Han Xiao decisively hung up the communication with a sneer.

Want to ambush me? Eat sh*t!

Beep beep beep…

The communicator rang.

Han Xiao moved his lips, took a deep breath, and carefully received the call. Just as he was about to speak, he suddenly saw that it was not Oathkeeper who appeared on the screen, so he stopped.

"Herberlon?"

"I received your battle report. This is unbelievable. How did you guys do it‽" The electronic image of Herberlon showed an exaggerated expression of surprise.

Herberlon did not participate in this battle. His body had not been fully adjusted, and he would definitely be recognized by the World Tree. Han Xiao was afraid of unexpected variables, so it was not convenient to let him participate in the first battle. He would only be at ease at sending Herberlon to battle when the information connection of both sides became irreversible.

"Are you referring to the damage to the high-level combatants?" Han Xiao rubbed his chin and teased. "If I have to say it, it can only be attributed to my wisdom and strength."

He only meant it as a joke, but he did not expect Herberlon to nod with a serious expression.

"Indeed. Without you, the three Universal Civilizations would not have such achievements."

Han Xiao opened his mouth but did not know what to say.

I didn't expect you to be such a bootlicker!

"I thought that even if you guys could defeat the World Tree, it would be a miserable victory. I didn't expect you guys to be so strong." Herberlon was a little excited.

Because the Karma Republic had lost too badly, Herberlon had a very deep trauma regarding the World Tree. However, the report of this great victory gave him confidence. He saw hope for this Universal Civilization in defeating the World Tree, and there was indeed a chance to take revenge by clinging on to this civilization. Thus, he was finally willing.

"If there are any tough battles in the future, you must use my strength." Herberlon's expression became solemn.

"…Alright, even if you don't tell me, I won't let you stay idle."

Han Xiao could only give him a few words of encouragement before hanging up.

As soon as he put away the communicator, footsteps sounded behind him.

Han Xiao turned around and saw Hila walking over.

"Do you have time now? Come with me to the Underworld." Hila had a cold expression on her face as she slowly said, "If you don't go now, those newly accepted Hero Spirits will probably rebel."

"Alright, let's go."

Han Xiao nodded, changed into his King suit, and disappeared.

…

Numerous newborn Hero Spirits stood on the pitch-black ground with blank expressions on their faces. Their memories were still fixed on the scene before their death, and the pain in their bodies seemed to have yet to disappear. Their vision blurred, and they arrived in this space.

"Where is this? Why am I here?"

"I… I should have been blown up. Why am I still alive?"

"Wait, what's wrong with my body? Why can't I feel anything‽"

The commotion quickly spread, and the countless Hero Spirit became more and more flustered. They questioned each other while observing the surroundings, wanting to understand the current situation.

These newborn Hero Spirits came from different civilizations and organizations. There were all kinds of species, and many of them were genuine soldiers. They were all vigilantly observing the Hero Spirits around them.

At this moment, streams of light suddenly gathered above everyone, condensing into Onicelu's figure. She had a warm smile on her face.

"Everyone, this is the Underworld. You have already sacrificed yourselves on the battlefield, but you have not died completely. Your souls have been brought here, reborn, and become the Hero Spirits of this place…"

The voice was transmitted to everyone's ears through the power of the Underworld. Countless newborn spirits looked up at Onicelu in shock.

"We really sacrificed ourselves. I thought it was just a dream."

"Only with permission can we leave the Underworld… So, we've lost our freedom and become slaves?"

Countless hero spirits were instantly in an uproar.

They had become someone else's slave without any mental preparation, and they could not accept it immediately. This feeling was like being forcefully sold. They had no freedom to reject and could only follow the arrangements of others.

Furthermore, the other party had taken their souls while they were dying in battle. The feeling it gave off was as though they were taking advantage of the situation… It was literally 'picking up corpses'!

Many people were furious.

"Let me out! No matter who you are, I will not be your slave!"

"Control my soul? Don't even think about it!"

The countless newborn hero spirits roared in unison, and their voices were extremely shocking, as if they were going to shatter the earth.

However, Onicelu's expression did not change. She only made a zipping motion with her fingers. The next second, the entire world fell silent. No matter how the newborn Hero Spirits roared, they could not make a sound.

Looking at the shocked and furious faces of the new Hero Spirits, Onicelu shook her head and explained, "In the Underworld, I am the absolute ruler. Your mobility is controlled by me. Furthermore, you have no combat power in your soul form state."

However, the more this was the case, the more furious the new Hero Spirits became. Unable to make a sound, they used their actions to indicate that they wanted to escape.

However, Onicelu only changed her hand gesture, and this area was isolated from the outside world, becoming a loop space. Once the newborn Hero Spirits crossed the border, they would return from the other side, never leaving.

Very soon, countless new Hero Spirits lost all hope and stopped trying to escape. They stared at Onicelu with rage.

Swoosh!

However, at this moment, two figures appeared out of thin air. They were Han Xiao and Hila.

Countless Hero Spirits immediately turned around and were stunned. No one present did not recognize Black Star.

"Hmm? What's going on here?" Han Xiao realized something was wrong the moment he arrived. He turned to look at Onicelu and asked, "Did you rob them of their voices?"

"Yes, because they were a little angry. I didn't have time to explain everything," Onicelu replied.

"It's alright, I'm already here. Release their seal." Han Xiao waved his hands.

Onicelu did as she was told, and the new Hero Spirits immediately returned to normal. However, they did not continue making a ruckus. All of them looked at Han Xiao with different expressions.

Han Xiao's reputation was extremely high. When they saw him appear, most of the new Hero Spirits quickly calmed down. They did not trust Onicelu, but they trusted Black Star.

"Oh, you're quite self-aware."

Han Xiao glanced at them and was instantly amused. He was so popular that just showing his face had stabilized their emotions.

At this moment, a newborn Hero Spirit loudly asked, "Black Star, were you the one who brought us here?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao looked down at him and realized that he was an officer of the dynasty. He shook his head, patted Hila beside him, and said, "Hila and Aurora are the masters of the Underworld. I asked them to use the Underworld to save the soldiers who were sacrificed in the war. This is how you guys came about."

Without waiting for the new Hero Spirits to question him, Han Xiao continued. "Only Beyond Grade As can enjoy the Sanctum Revival. If you do not meet the requirements, you will really die if you die in battle. However, all of you are precious talents of the Galactic Society, and I could not bear to see you all die so easily. The Underworld is my only way to save all of you, so I had no choice but to do so. Now that the enemies are watching, every bit of strength is extremely important. This is to protect our limited armed forces. The three Universal Civilizations are also aware of this, and they support this plan."

Although they would lose their freedom if they became Underworld Hero Spirits, it was better than sacrificing themselves. Here, they could still shine for the Galactic Society and return to the battlefield to fight the enemies.

"However, please understand that we have never thought of you as slaves. I hereby promise that when the war ends, if any of you are unwilling to stay in the Underworld, I can remove your Hero Spirit status and let you rest in peace."

After he finished speaking, the crowd became restless. The expressions of the new hero spirits changed, and their emotions were extremely complicated. Some were conflicted, some were glad, and some were relieved.

However, no matter what they thought, the anger in their hearts slowly dissipated and calmed down.

Onicelu was a stranger, so her words did not make sense. However, Black Star was someone that the entire Galactic Society knew, so his words were trustworthy.

Anyway, they were already there, and there was no way for them to resist, so they had no choice but to accept this reality. Furthermore, Black Star had promised them that they could choose to remove the Underworld's control in the future and not become slaves forever. Although they did not know if Black Star would keep his promise, they could only trust it.

Furthermore, after calming down, not many people really wanted to rest in peace. This kind of situation was better than dying completely.

Seeing the newborn Hero Spirits quiet down, Han Xiao turned to look at Hila and shrugged.

"Alright, my job is done. Make arrangements for these people."

He had only gone there to appease the newborn Hero Spirits. With his high reputation and Legendary Points in the explored universe, no one was more suitable for this job than him.

In other words, his position in the explored universe was comparable to the Fruit of Face, and he could stabilize the morale of the army.

"Alright." Hila did not waste her words. She turned around and communicated with the new Hero Spirits, talking in detail.

Han Xiao looked at the endless sea of people and exhaled.

War was indeed an opportunity for the rapid growth of the Underworld.

After looting so many Hero Spirits, he had stolen countless talents from the various large factions. Their value was extraordinary.

And if he wanted to make all of them work…

Han Xiao clicked his tongue, suddenly feeling a little worried about Aurora's breasts.

"Such an expenditure of milk. I feel like she'll become flat-chested in the future…"

Chapter 1344: Balance and Entry

A day later, in the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations…

"You plan to use the Sanctum Revival and recall our direct descendants‽"

Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope opened their eyes wide and stared at Han Xiao's remote projection in shock.

Han Xiao spread out his hands and said with a serious expression, "The World Tree has plenty of experts. Due to their special mechanism, their Beyond Grade As will not decrease, and they have been accumulating to their current size. Because of wars and other reasons, we have lost many Beyond Grade As. Although we managed to repel a wave of attacks from the World Tree this time, they did not bring out all their high-level combatants. We have to increase our Beyond Grade As to slowly reverse the disadvantage of individual strength."

The three leaders looked at each other in surprise.

When they signed the agreement, they did not make a condition that Black Star must revive the direct descendants. They knew that the Beyond Grade A Association was still wary of the three Universal Civilizations. Even if there were foreign enemies, Black Star might not awaken their direct descendants and increase his competitors' strength.

Thus, when Black Star took the initiative to mention this, the three of them were pleasantly surprised. Regardless of whether Black Star wanted to share the pressure of the association members or purely for the sake of the war, this method was beneficial to them.

The direct Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations, including the National Pillars at the level of Clotti and Oulou, were guardians of different eras. If they could summon all of them, it would be a huge supplement to the high-level combatants of the three Universal Civilizations.

"This is a wise choice. I'm glad to see that you're willing to consider the big picture."

Marbruce was full of praise.

Han Xiao paid his praise no mind. He raised his finger and said, "However, there is one condition. These resurrected direct descendants must join the frontlines."

"Of course." Louis nodded. He understood what Han Xiao meant. It was impossible for them to let the resurrected direct descendants sit back and watch the association members fight to the death.

"Alright, we have a consensus. Let's talk about the cost." Han Xiao put down his hands.

"Cost?"

"Do you think this is free?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Not at all, tell me the price."

The Pope shook his head.

Because Black Star's act of suddenly providing help was a little righteous, the three of them almost thought that it was free. However, they all came back to their senses now and knew that with Black Star's personality, it was impossible for him to let go of this opportunity to make a huge profit. Although both parties were currently in a partnership to resist the foreign enemy, the services that should be paid for would not be free. After all, they were only allies.

The three of them did not have any objections to this. Now was the time to beg for help. It was not easy for them to have the opportunity to revive their direct descendants. No matter how high the cost was, they had to pay it.

Han Xiao opened the virtual screen, made a list, and sent it to the three of them.

The three of them quickly browsed through the list. The list was filled with all kinds of resources, materials, and weapons. Although it was expensive, it was within an acceptable range.

"You want these things?"

"That's right. This is the price for the Sanctum Revival."

"Sure."

Marbruce agreed.

Han Xiao nodded. There were materials for the Sanctum Key in the list. He could use the three Universal Civilizations to gather materials and provide him with access to the Sanctum. This was equivalent to spending the three Universal Civilizations' money to increase his Sanctum authority.

"When do you plan to start?" Louis asked.

"Destiny's Child surveillance has already confirmed that the World Tree Civilization will not make any big movements in the near future. I will use the Sanctum Revival soon." Han Xiao nodded, then paused and said, "Also, when I use the Sanctum Revival, I will temporarily leave the main universe for about three months. During that time, I will be out of contact. During my absence, Hila will be in charge of relaying the information of Destiny's Child surveillance channels."

"Three months…" Their hearts sank.

If the World Tree did something during this period, without Black Star, there might be variables…

The three of them suddenly realized that they had unknowingly developed a certain amount of reliance on Black Star. Ever since they discovered the World Tree, Black Star's actions had given them most of their current advantages, and he had accumulated a lot of trust. He was a special consultant, and to a certain extent, the three of them treated Han Xiao as their backbone in dealing with the World Tree Civilization.

Without Black Star, they subconsciously felt less confident.

"If you're worried that the World Tree will send the Tree King again, you can let Wuornos participate in the battle. With his ability, it won't be a problem for him to stop a Tree King," Han Xiao said.

In his previous life, Wuornos did not participate in the war, and this time, he was still one of the few Beyond Grade As who had not been recruited. It was very strange. Han Xiao was also very curious why the Arcane Church did not send this b*stard out. Even if his main body did not go to war, he could have sent a few God Embodiments.

"There are some special reasons. It's not convenient for him to make a move." The Pope shook his head.

"What special reason is more important than the threat of the World Tree?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

When he fought with Han Xiao, he was full of energy, but when it was time to face the enemies, he had all kinds of excuses. Could it be that Wuornos was the type of person who was submissive to the outside world and domineering toward his side?

"…In any case, there are some reasons." The Pope kept his mouth shut and suddenly changed the topic. "By the way, can you unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter?"

"Wuornos is not participating in the battle and still wants me to unseal his weapon?"

"Even if we don't let him use it, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is still a powerful weapon against individual strengths."

"We'll see."

Han Xiao did not comment. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter could indeed increase the combat power of high-level combatants, but he did not intend to unseal it yet.

After a pause, he said, "I need to obtain some mediums related to the revival target. Which direct descendants do you want to revive? Give me their mediums in the next few days."

The three of them nodded.

They were also organizing people to study the Sanctums, and this was the first time they had heard that the Sanctum Revival required a medium. However, it made sense when they thought about it. If they did not need a medium, then even the Beyond Grade As of other unknown civilizations could be revived at will.

"One more thing," Han Xiao said. "This time, I will revive a portion of the direct members of the Super Star Cluster Alliance."

"Hmm?" The trio's expression changed slightly.

At this moment, the three of them thought of many things and subconsciously thought that this was Black Star's way of keeping them in check.

Resurrecting the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations was a threat to the Beyond Grade A Association. Thus, Black Star deliberately revived the direct descendants of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, forming a tripartite balance that hindered the three Universal Civilizations. This method could also explain the reason for reviving the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations. In consideration of the war situation, the three of them, as the beneficiaries of this reason, had no way of rebutting.

"Don't think too much about it. I just made a deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance in the past, and I don't intend to go against this deal," Han Xiao replied casually, ignoring the gazes of the three.

"…Of course." The three of them adjusted their mentality and regained their composure.

Many of the historical members of the Super Star Cluster Alliance had died in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, and the hatred between the two sides was deeply rooted. Once they revived, it would definitely be troublesome.

However, the Sanctum Revival was controlled by Black Star, so they could only accept this change. Furthermore, the three of them believed that as long as their own direct descendants revived, they would not have to worry about the Super Star Cluster Alliance causing trouble.

Both parties quickly came to an agreement. Just as Han Xiao was about to end the communication, he suddenly thought of something and asked, "By the way, how's the progress of the secondary dimension expedition team?"

"There were some losses, but we still did not find anything." Marbruce shook his head.

Han Xiao sighed.

The World Tree Civilization still did not know that they had sent out troops to search for their main body. The secondary dimension expedition team was the true game-changer of the three Universal Civilizations.

…

After meeting the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations, Han Xiao immediately went to the Super Star Cluster Alliance. At this time, all the leaders of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations were in the room, staring at Han Xiao.

"Black Star, we were just talking about you. The results of your battle are shocking."

"If we didn't know your capabilities, we would have thought that the enemy this time is very weak."

The leaders of the civilizations praised him.

"It wasn't too bad. It's mainly because the Beyond Grade As are working together," Han Xiao replied casually. He observed the expressions of the leaders of the civilizations present and quickly calculated.

Based on his understanding of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations, these people were most likely waiting for the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree to both suffer so that they could ascend. Thus, they might not be too happy to see such low losses.

He remembered that in his previous life, the Super Star Cluster Alliance even had a plan, which was to take the opportunity when the three Universal Civilizations were fighting the World Tree to leave the explored universe with their own civilization and escape in the middle of the war. They thought that the three Universal Civilizations would not have the energy to stop them and could only watch them leave.

However, after completely experiencing the perverted nature of the World Tree Civilization, the Super Star Cluster Alliance understood that it was like drinking poison to quench their thirst. In the end, they did not use this plan and wholeheartedly cooperated with the three Universal Civilizations to fight the enemy.

Han Xiao estimated that the Super Star Cluster Alliance most likely had similar thoughts at present. After being bullied by the three Universal Civilizations for so long, it was impossible for them to not have considered this route.

While he was thinking, the Star Arc Civilization leader knocked on the table and asked:

"Black Star, why did you contact us this time?"

Han Xiao composed himself and said, "I'm here to fulfill the agreement."

"Which agreement?"

"I promised to revive ten of your direct Beyond Grade As. Now is the time."

The moment he said that, the leaders of the civilizations were overjoyed.

After coming to an agreement, the Super Star Cluster Alliance quickly collected the revival fees and handed them all to Han Xiao. However, Black Star would decide when the revival would take place. They did not know how long Black Star would take, but they had already paid the deposit, so they could only wait patiently.

It was finally time!

This backup was worth it!

Indeed, everything came at the end of fawning!

The Star Arc Civilization leader suppressed his excitement and said, "Got it. What should we prepare?"

"I need some mediums…"

Han Xiao repeated his explanation to the three Universal Civilizations, and everyone nodded.

After explaining, Han Xiao looked at everyone's expressions, smiled, and said, "One more thing. I will still give you ten slots in the next revival. You will still need to buy them. You can discuss if you want to add more."

"Of course we accept," the Star Arc Civilization leader immediately said.

Ten slots were far from enough to revive all the Beyond Grade As in the history of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations. Since Black Star was willing to sell another ten slots, there was naturally no reason to reject him.

"You don't have to be in a hurry to bid. It won't be too late even after I bring these revivors back."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

The two of them exchanged a few more words before hanging up.

The leaders of the civilizations were the only ones left in the conference room, and their faces were finally filled with joy.

"When our direct descendants return, our plan will have a much higher chance. Black Star has done us a huge favor this time."

The Star Arc Civilization leader took a deep breath.

What they did not know was that Black Star only gave them ten slots each time, but the number of slots sold to the three Universal Civilizations was unlimited.

…

Two days later, somewhere in the Ancient Star Desert, the Holy Accord Organization's spaceship was hovering in the starry sky, preheating the equipment and preparing to open the Sanctum channel.

Han Xiao remained in the main ship, talking to Hila and the other upper echelons.

"While I'm using the Sanctum Revival, the army will be under your command. Preserve your strength… If the World Tree makes a move, Aurora, you will have to pay attention to your own safety. It'd be best to convince Manison, Kasuyi, and the others to be your bodyguards for the time being. The World Tree has lost quite a number of experts. They won't revive too quickly, so the intensity of the following battle shouldn't be too high…"

"Don't worry, I can protect myself now." Aurora nodded.

"However, just in case, if anything happens, you guys should evacuate. I've provided Herberlon with some Kings. Although he hasn't joined the battle yet, if there's any danger, he will use his Mechanical Force to teleport you guys away…"

After giving some instructions to the officers, Han Xiao hung up.

"If you're done, shall I begin?" Oathkeeper asked.

"Start." Han Xiao nodded.

As the order was passed down, rays of light shot out from the Holy Accord's spaceship and entered the key of the First Sanctum.

Very soon, a familiar scene appeared again. The six doors of light appeared, and only one of them was left, which turned into the passageway of the First Sanctum.

Han Xiao took a deep breath and charged into the Sanctum passageway.

The next moment, the door of light shrank rapidly, and a thin beam of light flashed past like when an old television was switched off.

Before all the onlookers, the Sanctum passageway disappeared along with Han Xiao.

Oathkeeper exhaled.

The annoying fellow is gone… I can finally experience what it feels like to be in charge again!

Chapter 1345: Plunder and Thoughts

The tunnel filled with endless streams of light seemed to be able to travel through time. Han Xiao's senses became hazy and blurry as if his mind had sunk into an old dream.

After an unknown period of time, his vision cleared up, and he regained consciousness.

He looked around and realized that he was in a boundless white world with countless light orbs floating around. He had a deep impression of this scene.

"Phew, I got in."

Han Xiao calmed his mind and made a grabbing motion at the collapsing tunnel.

A surge of energy emerged from his body and turned into a mark on his palm. The Sanctum channel immediately stabilized.

He retracted his palm and looked at it. This mark was formed by eight patterns. It was Lv. 8 clearance of the First Sanctum.

"I have to hurry…"

Han Xiao calmed himself down and immediately started to move. This was his second time entering the Sanctum, so he was already familiar with it.

The longer he stayed in the Sanctum, the more time would pass in the outside world. The last time he entered the Third Sanctum, he had wasted a lot of time testing the functions of the Sanctum. This time, there was no need. His actions had a purpose.

Han Xiao took out many mediums and called for the Sanctum to revive.

Beams of light gathered and condensed into a Sanctum revival mark in front of him, floating quietly.

He touched it, and the Sanctum revival mark fused into his palm, turning into a tattoo-like mark.

After checking the revival targets in the imprint, Han Xiao nodded. Without any delay, he started to touch the various Information Form light spheres to gather different information.

The information stored in the First Sanctum was closely related to mechanical technology, and it contained the high-level blueprints developed by countless generations of civilizations. Most of them were Universal Treasures meant for Mechanics. The value of this information to Han Xiao far exceeded the value of the Third Sanctum.

Han Xiao's authority level in the First Sanctum was higher than that in the Third Sanctum, and he could store more memory. He could take away more technological information in one go, so there was no reason for him to let go of such an opportunity.

The technologies of the final civilizations of various Iterations entered Han Xiao's mind one after another, slowly reaching the upper limit of his memory capacity.

"Finally full. The memory capacity of a rank 8 authority is quite high."

Han Xiao's plundering stopped, and he was rather excited.

This wave of plundering was a huge supplement to his technological foundation. He had obtained the trump card of technologies from final civilizations of multiple Iterations, which was enough for him to study for a long time. The number of blueprints in his inventory had increased tremendously.

The trump cards of these final civilizations were not simple, and they had complicated functions. Some of the technologies' strategic value was not much worse than the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device of the Federation of Light. Bringing these precious technologies out was equivalent to obtaining new trump cards against the World Tree Civilization, increasing the war capital of the Galactic Society.

After being happy for a while, Han Xiao suppressed his emotions. After doing these two things, his goal of opening the Sanctum was complete.

Looking around, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something. He used the Sanctum authority to summon the message board of the civilizations in the past Iterations.

The last time he entered the Third Sanctum, due to his authority, the message board was mostly empty. This time, his authority in the First Sanctum was higher, so he should be able to see more content. Han Xiao planned to take a look before he left.

The Sanctum mark released rays of light and quickly formed a screen-like message board, floating in front of Han Xiao.

Han Xiao browsed through it carefully and compared it with the contents of the Third Sanctum in his memories. Sure enough, he found that much of the empty content from the last time had become visible.

He continued reading, and his eyes paused on the record at the fifth last paragraph of the Celestial Star Alliance. He then looked at the last four paragraphs with the most empty content. Compared to what he had seen in the Third Sanctum, most of the last four paragraphs were still covered, but some new content was revealed.

The fourth last paragraph displayed the most content. In the large empty space, a few pieces of information appeared:

[… According to the results of the joint observation, the Great Reboot will take place after ███, we have learned our lesson from the previous Iteration and have formulated 'Information Form Stripping Plan'. We hope that the long relay will end in our hands… Our civilization is called ███, if the civilizations in the later Iterations ███… that means our plan███, please take a new route…]

"Is this the Iteration after the Celestial Star Alliance…"

Han Xiao pondered. It looked like a message from another civilization that did not manage to survive the Great Reboot.

Although his authority was not enough to show the name of this civilization, and he was unable to find the other party's information Form light spheres, he knew that the other party's plan to get through the Great Reboot was called the Information Form Stripping Plan.

"Information Form Stripping… sounds interesting."

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

Apart from this paragraph, the other information that appeared in the last four paragraphs were all bits and pieces of information. They were of no value, and the level-eight authority was not enough to fully check this part.

After browsing through the messages again and memorizing them, Han Xiao turned off the message board and flew toward the Sanctum channel.

The second day after Han Xiao entered the Sanctum.

Interception circle's main base, many Beyond Grade As were on standby. When there were no combat missions, they would do their own thing.

In the exclusive activity room, a portion of the Beyond Grade As were resting or having fun, chatting casually.

Kasuyi was playing cards with Secret Master, and a group of people was watching from the side.

"Black Star is already disconnected. I wonder how many troublesome fellows he'll bring back this time…"

Sun Hunter, who was the size of a finger, stood on the card table with his arms crossed and said in a low voice.

Kasuyi threw out a 'Kasuyi' card and smiled helplessly:

"This is indeed troublesome. After all, some of the historical Beyond Grade As have complicated relationships with us."

The first two batches of revived Beyond Grade As did not have much contact with the current Beyond Grade As, but the targets this time were different. Many of them were their 'acquaintances'.

"Ahem, to be honest, I'm not prepared to meet my ancestor," Milizaus had a headache.

He was the patriarch of the Starry Spiritual Dragon race, and Starry Spiritual Dragon was a branch bloodline left behind by a Beyond Grade A Magic Azure Dragon.

Milizaus was not the only one with such a story. The Beyond Grade As that Black Star was preparing to revive had a similar relationship with many of the people present.

If that was all, it would have been fine. However, many people had enmity between them. When they thought about how their enemy was about to be revived, many of them felt uneasy.

Initially, when people died, everything would be settled, and the hatred would be let go. However, now that the enemies had all come back to life, should they still pursue their past grudges ‽

This was especially so for the victims of the Tragedy of the Pinnacles represented by Dylan. Everyone felt that they definitely would not let this go.

"When this group of people is revived by Black Star, it would be nice if they didn't start a fight," Kant shook his head.

Hila, who was resting in the corner, said without opening her eyes:

"What's there to be afraid of? Black Star can revive them, and he can also stuff them back into their graves. If they cause trouble, I'm more than happy to send them to the Underworld."

Hearing this, everyone turned to look at her, speechless.

"That's true, but you saying this in front of us feels like you're warning us…"

Everyone curled their lips and looked away.

Humph, although they were sisters, Aurora was still cuter!

"Hila is right. At this time, we cannot waste a single soldier," Kasuyi chuckled.

After Han Xiao entered the Sanctum, Kasuyi and Hila became the backbone of the association. The former was the vice president, while Hila did not have enough reputation. However, Han Xiao had given her the intelligence channel of Destiny's Child, so Hila enjoyed a transcendent position for the time being.

"Speaking of which, although Black Star is shameless and cunning, he is still very hardworking when it comes to fighting for the benefits of the Beyond Grade As and protecting the safety of the Galactic Society," Sun Hunter smacked his lips and said.

"That's because you don't know him well. Cunning is just a means. I've always felt that Black Star is an idealist who plans far ahead for the peace of the universe. He has a noble ambition that transcends reality," As a veteran boot-licker, Beiger's tone was filled with respect.

"Forget it. Black Star is purely an opportunist, but his common interests are the same as ours. We're on the same side, but don't flatter him," Heber snorted.

The group began to heatedly discuss Black Star's character. Anyway, Han Xiao was not here, it was not convenient for them to roast him in front of him. But now, they could say whatever they wanted.

On the other side, Manison was alone in the observation deck of the main base, looking at the starry sky.

He was playing with a Rubik's cube-like polyhedron in his hands, which looked like some kind of mechanism. The complicated mechanical structure kept sliding and making cracking sounds.

This was a children's toy of the Mechanical Race, used to cultivate Mechanical Sense from a young age.

"Ancestor might be returning…"

Manison muttered to himself with mixed feelings.

He was the second Beyond Grade A born in the Mechanical Race, and he also had a distant ancestor. Although he had become an independent species after becoming a Beyond Grade A Super, this relationship could still be counted.

This was especially so since Manison was the only leader of the Mechanical Race and treated the Mechanical Race as an important asset. If the ancestor of the Mechanical Race returned and wanted to become the leader of the Mechanical Race again, who would the Mechanical Race listen to? Two tigers cannot share one mountain, would his position be affected?

It was a pity that the Sanctum Revival target was decided by Black Star. As long as he found the medium, he would be free to choose the revival target.

Manison could not control Han Xiao's thoughts. He even suspected that Black Star did it on purpose.

At this moment, Clotti and Oulou were also conflicted.

The two of them were waiting at the dock of the base, watching the giant starships enter the port.

Oulou lit a cigarette and exhaled a light blue cloud. He slowly said: "The direct descendants of the past are about to revive. Are you nervous?"

"Why should I be nervous?" Clotti was expressionless.

"Hey, don't tell me you don't have any psychological trauma toward them," Oulou sneered.

Clotti said nothing.

He was now a direct descendant of the dynasty with the highest position, but he was still a junior in front of the previous generation.

Clotti did not become the National Pillar of the dynasty as soon as he became a Beyond Grade A Super. Before he grew up, there was still the National Pillar of the previous generation that supported the dynasty's prestige.

At the same time, the direct line of descent had an inheritance relationship. Due to the strength of his Esper Ability, Clotti was the focus of the dynasty's training. The previous National Pillar was his special training instructor and could be considered half a teacher, leaving him with an indelible impression.

If Gaud had not been killed, he would have received Clotti's special training, carrying on the inheritance.

"Although Black Star's goal is for the sake of the war…" Oulou took another puff of his cigarette and shook his head: "However, this kind of action will probably cause many people to enter a situation they never imagined."

Clotti shook his head.

Facing the many seniors who were about to be revived, the entire Beyond Grade A group had their own thoughts.

Chapter 1346: Lerbo Space Protection Belt

In the blink of an eye, more than a month had passed.

The military mobilization of the various Star Fields in the explored universe continued, especially in the Flickering World. Under the construction of the engineering fleets and various planet modification packages, the various war facilities in the large war zones were quickly completed. Military factories were active all day, and countless starships of various models were sent out every day.

The three Universal Civilizations were also in full swing, recruiting a large number of Supers from the various races to join the army. At the same time, they summoned back the vast number of reserve soldiers who had once served in the army and gave them further military training in the various military bases to replenish the military strength gap between various military posts. They also carried out mandatory basic military training among the galactic residents to expand their flow of troops.

The war mobilization speed of the interstellar era was beyond the imagination of ordinary people. Under the unification of the three Universal Civilizations, the war machines of the explored universe operated at high efficiency. All kinds of resources were being thrown into the corresponding gaps to be used efficiently.

The construction of the intercepting circle on the frontline was also progressing rapidly. Although the World Tree Civilization had failed in their assault, they did not stop harassing in small groups and had exchanged fire with the intercepting troops many times. As the space stabilization anchor orbit set by the three Universal Civilizations was expanding further and further away, the World Tree Civilization's jump point was also constantly moving backward, further away from the intercepting circle.

As a result, the World Tree also treated the destruction of the space stabilization anchor orbit as an important battle target. It sent its vanguard troops to attack the space stabilization anchor orbit in different routes many times, unsealing the different jump points, and sending reconnaissance troops to this coordinate.

Due to the World Tree reconnaissance troops constantly splitting up, the overall structure of the space stabilization anchor orbit was like a three-dimensional tree model with many divergences, extending continuously. Countless streams of light representing both fleets jumped between the 'tree branches', colliding from time to time and erupting into local battles.

In the three Universal Civilizations' interception circle's main base, high-intensity energy sources that represented the battle points kept appearing on the General Surveillance Strategic Radar. The World Tree fleet would occasionally succeed, destroying the branches of the space stabilization anchor many times. They needed to be repaired and troops needed to be sent to pursue the new batch of reconnaissance troops that were put on these jump points by the World Tree.

As the interception circle and space stabilization anchor orbit continued to expand, the number of openings left for the enemy would also increase. This was unavoidable, but the three Universal Civilizations could still deal with the current defensive line.

"The harassment of the World Tree is endless. Although this is an effective method, it will take a very long time. They must have made multiple preparations. They should be preparing a new wave of attacks to create a huge gap in our defense line, removing our control over the intercepting circle."

In the conference room at the interception circle's main base, Simon was discussing with the commanders and staff sergeants.

In the past month that Black Star was not around, there had been small conflicts between the two sides, but there were no large-scale battles. The overall situation was quite stable, and the number of times a Beyond Grade A group was dispatched could be counted on one hand.

Hila was in charge of the surveillance channels of Destiny's Child, and there was no news of the World Tree making a big move. Both sides were in a stalemate for the time being with both sides attacking and defending. The enemy did not make much progress.

Simon and the others naturally understood that the World Tree would not continue to tangle with them like this. In the past few days, he had an intense tactical intuition and felt that there would be some changes soon.

"According to the data, the frequency of the World Tree attacking the Space Stabilization Anchor orbit has decreased by 37% in the past five days, and the number of reconnaissance troops has increased by 73%. Furthermore, we have discovered that the World Tree Civilization has left behind a large number of topological space directional marks near the anchor orbit. We speculate that the World Tree Civilization is trying to bring super long-range weapons at the jump points that are not covered in the orbit, destroying the various branches of the orbit remotely."

Simon pressed his hands on the command platform with a solemn expression.

Another commander nodded and said: "The anti-over-the-horizon radar is in an activated state. If the World Tree adopts this plan, the dynasty's super long-range anti-particle base cannon, the federation's Psionic Planetary Obliteration Beams, and the church's Soul Sniper Beam can lock onto the source of the attack and carry out the counterattack mission."

"I'm just afraid that the World Tree will set up the Lerbo Space Protection Belt. That would not be good."

Simon shook his head.

Beyond-visual-range warfare was also the main form of interstellar warfare. In this regard, the three Universal Civilizations were strong on offense but weak on defense. However, the World Tree Civilization was different. According to the intelligence provided by Black Star, the World Tree Civilization had a Universal Treasure-level special defense weapon that could be used in beyond-visual-range warfare. It was called the 'Lerbo Space Protection Belt'.

This kind of defense technology had a similar effect to the Psionic Seal Ring. It was like a portable miniaturized version, distorting the universe constants of an area, preventing the over-the-horizon strikes from penetrating it.

However, this restriction went both ways. The external energy attacks could not pass through, and the attacks from the inside would also be blocked. Therefore, it was difficult for the fleet that opened the Lerbo Space Protection Belt to attack from the outside. Because the Lerbo Space Protection Belt could not move along with the spaceship after it was opened, it was not used in battle. It was usually used to protect some important facilities.

Only physical weapons such as interstellar missiles and starships' close-range assault could ignore the effects of the Lerbo Space Protection Belt. Other energy weapons were basically useless. However, the majority of super long-range weapons were energy weapons, so this technology was often used in beyond-visual-range warfare. The protective belt would be retracted when firing and opened when the firing was stopped. This way, it was very difficult to be put at a disadvantage in beyond-visual-range warfare.

While the upper echelons were discussing, the entire surveillance radars that covered all the space stabilization anchors suddenly issued an alarm. Hundreds of red lines representing high-energy attacks suddenly broke into the edge of the radar and quickly hit different branches of the orbit.

The 3D radar model in front of everyone reacted, and hundreds of red ripples appeared. The destruction report of the orbit was quickly sent back.

"It's confirmed to be over-the-horizon strikes. The World Tree really used this method."

Simon's expression froze. Speak of the devil. He had just mentioned over-the-horizon strikes when the World Tree's attack wave arrived. His recent intuition had come true.

The jump point of the World Tree's super long-range weapon was located outside the range of the radar.

"Analyze the attack trajectory and counterattack," Simon ordered.

The anti-over-the-horizon radar started to work, quickly analyzing the curvature, angle, and other factors of the enemy's hundreds of attacks.

Over-the-horizon strikes did not usually move in a straight line. Under various universe environmental factors, the attack trajectory would show different deviations. For example, a sniper needed to calculate the wind direction, distance, trajectory, gravity, and other conditions. It was the same for over-the-horizon strikes. More parameters needed to be calculated, and the calculation model was very complicated. The reverse lock was to reverse engineer these factors and obtain the coordinates of the source of the attack.

Very soon, the final result was sent to the three Universal Civilizations' super long-range weapons through quantum communication.

Crack!

A huge planetary fortress stretched out rows of enormous cannons. The base slowly turned, and the barrels turned as though they were aimed at empty space. The actual super long-range sight had already locked onto the space coordinates calculated by the artificial intelligence.

Immediately after, the cannon barrels started to light up from its base, and dark blue particles rapidly gathered from all directions, accumulating energy in the muzzle and releasing a dazzling light. When the power was accumulated to its peak, the color turned from blue to red, suddenly releasing huge energy beams, disappearing into the vast starry sky in the blink of an eye.

However, this round of counterattack was like a stone sinking into the ocean, there was no response.

Simon and the others waited for a while. However, the second wave of attack from the World Tree came, and hundreds of orbital branches were destroyed. The source of the attack was exactly the same.

"The counterattack did not seem to have any effect. Maybe you were right. They used that defensive technology…" One of the commanders looked at Simon and secretly cursed.

"Continue firing. Do not stop," Simon frowned.

The weapons of the three Universal Civilizations began to fire continuously. Although they could not observe the effects of the attacks, the enemies' attacks had stopped.

"Even if the World Tree has set up the Lerbo Space Protection Belt, our frequency of firepower is enough to suppress them and prevent them from taking back the protective belt. This way, they won't be able to continue attacking us," one of the staff officers said.

Simon knocked on the table and shook his head. "This is just a temporary plan. If we want to solve it once and for all, we'll have to send out fleets to attack them on the spot and destroy their artillery bases… Call some Beyond Grade As to move out and try to take over the Lerbo Space Protection Belt."

Not long after, the Beyond Grade As on standby in the base were summoned to the conference room. After hearing Simon's explanation, they quickly understood the situation.

Kasuyi stroked his chin and asked:

"Not only do we have to destroy the enemy's artillery base, but we also have to confiscate their special equipment. Then, it will be up to Manison or Kant, how many people do we need?"

"It's best if there are ten Beyond Grade As or more. Bring a batch of Thrones along," Simon nodded.

"Isn't ten a little too much? We probably won't meet any World Tree experts on this trip." Sun Hunter turned to look at Hila. "Can your surveillance channels see the situation of this artillery base?"

"No." Hila shook her head.

The World Tree did not use Oracles for this stronghold, and Destiny's Child could not spy on the other party's personnel. Therefore, everyone knew almost nothing about the situation of this base. Currently, they only knew the location calculated by the anti-over-the-horizon radar.

"This is just to be safe," Simon explained. "The other party might not have built this base just to bombard from afar, they might also use it as an outpost. We can't sit back and watch the World Tree build a bridgehead. We have to take the initiative to attack and keep pushing their formation further away."

The group discussed for a while and quickly decided that Kant would lead nine Beyond Grade As, including those from the association and direct line descents in the campaign.

Since they estimated that there were no World Tree experts among the targets, Aurora did not follow them and remained at the main base.

Very soon, Kant and the others formed an expedition team and arrived at the edge of the radar through the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, heading toward the World Tree's temporary base.

...

The three Universal Civilizations' armed fleets only arrived at their destination after a few days.

Outside the window, a group of galactic bases was floating in the area, surrounded by a hazy glowing space. It was the Lerbo Space Protection Belt.

Over-the-horizon light beams kept shooting from the back of this fleet. This was the firepower suppression that the three Universal Civilizations had been maintaining for several days. However, the moment they entered the Lerbo Space Protection Belt, the speed of the energy beams instantly became like a tortoise crawling. At the same time, the beams of light rapidly shrunk until they dissipated. All of its power was obliterated, as though they had entered an energy restriction zone.

"This is the place. The target is clear." Kant's Lord's Avatar's electronic eyes flashed, sending the image back to the main base.

At the same time, the battleships of the three Universal Civilizations shot out interstellar missiles one after another, dragging their exhaust flames into the Lerbo Space Protection Belt. The physical missiles were not affected at all, and they headed straight for the temporary bases at the center.

However, the next moment, the armor on the surface of the bases slid, and rows of turrets rose up. A metal storm suddenly appeared, forming a concentrated barrage. All the galactic missiles were destroyed halfway, and a series of fireworks exploded.

Energy weapons were ineffective, and physical missiles could not penetrate the barrage.

"This is a problem. It seems like we have to charge in and let the fleet pass through the Lerbo Space Protection Belt. Only then will we be able to attack their bases," the fleet commander said in the channel.

The Lerbo Space Protection Belt was unable to isolate the quantum communication network. Kant opened his quantum network vision and tried to hack into the bases to seize control, but he was blocked by the firewall.

"There's a force protecting their firewall. I can't enter."

Kant retracted his vision and hesitated.

"It feels like a trap."

"Hmm, there is indeed something fishy. Assault team two and three, go in and take a look."

The fleet commander waved his hands and ordered a group of assault battleships to approach the enemy's bases. Most of the fleets stayed around the flagship and did not move. After all, the enemy had opened the Lerbo Space Protection Belt and the weapons could not attack them.

Beep! Beep! Beep!

However, at this moment, the radar on the spaceship suddenly issued an ear-piercing alarm.

Hundreds of large-caliber Planetary Obliteration Beams suddenly shot over from another direction, heading straight for the armed fleet.

"There's a problem! Defend!"

Kant's expression changed, and his mechanical army rushed out to form layers of shields. At the same time, the armed fleet also activated its own shield.

The next moment, hundreds of light beams shot over, blasting the protective shield until it was on the verge of collapse. Electric arcs shot out, and cracks appeared.

This wave of over-the-horizon strikes destroyed a small portion of the fleet before they were blocked. However, before the situation could stabilize, a large number of over-the-horizon strikes came from all directions, causing the fleets to retreat in defeat.

The image was transmitted back to the main base's conference room, and the expressions of Simon and the others changed slightly.

Manison knocked on the metal chin of the Lord's Avatar and said:

"It seems like the World Tree has built camps outside of our radar range, covering each other within over-the-horizon strikes range and guarding each other. I'm afraid the goal is not just to build an outpost but also to use the Lerbo Space Protection Belt to build a firepower coverage area like us and wear down our military strength…"

"Do you have any suggestions?" Simon asked.

"If Black Star's surveillance channels can't get the coordinates of these bases, then as long as the bases don't open fire, they will be invisible to us. However, the Lerbo Space Protection Belt is too difficult to deal with, and long-range attacks have almost no effect. If we use our troops to fill in the gaps, we will fall right into the enemy's trap. This isn't easy."

Manison slowly shook his head.

The three Universal Civilizations did indeed have plenty of Universal Treasures, but the World Tree had conquered one civilization after another, and its foundation was even more astonishing. It also had many strategic weapons and could not be underestimated.

Upon hearing this, Simon's expression turned grave. He could not make up his mind. He pursed his lips and sighed.

'It's a pity that Black Star, the special consultant, isn't here. If he was, I could have asked for his opinion…'

Chapter 1347: Deadlock

Black Star's opinion was an important reference for the three Universal Civilizations to carry out their decisions. It was as easy as reading a walk-through to fight a monster, allowing the upper echelons of the three Universal Civilizations to fully experience the joy of sucking up to someone powerful.

However, he could not contact Black Star now. He could only think of a way and act according to the situation.

Simon composed himself and said slowly:

"Therefore, there are two key points that need to be resolved. One is to locate the various camps, and the other is to use an efficient method to break through the Lerbo Space Protection Belt and destroy the enemy's artillery bases."

"If we can't find anything from Destiny's Child's surveillance, we can either passively wait for their bases to launch attacks and analyze the source of the attack, or wait for our control range to slowly cover it…"

A staff sergeant said.

Hearing this, the church commander shook his head and said:

"As long as the World Tree's beyond-visual-range encampment exists, it will continuously keep destroying our space anchoring orbits—monitoring the base station, and other facilities—stopping us from expanding our control range. In areas that we have yet to cover, the World Tree can expand the size of the camp at will, and there will be no end to it. These resources are just a drop of water in the ocean to them, and they are using an extremely low cost to form a tug-of-war with us, obstructing our movements… So, from the looks of it, we can only wait for the other party to make a move, then lock onto them. This is very passive."

"How about a large-scale search using reconnaissance ships?"

"The area to be covered is too large. This method is like finding a needle in a haystack. Furthermore, the other party will surely send out a large number of patrol fleets near the camp area. It won't work easily."

"What about mysticism?"

Upon hearing this, Secret Master interrupted and said: "The World Tree has a targeted defense in this area, we can't use mysticism to locate it."

Everyone discussed for a while but could not come up with any effective countermeasures. They had no choice but to temporarily put aside the problem of positioning and discuss how to attack.

"Compared to positioning, destroying the base is not difficult," this time, the dynasty commander spoke. "We can use the Spacetime Splicing Technology to let the small fleet carry high energy bombs directly through the Lerbo Space Protection Belt and blow up the enemy's base."

"Spacetime Splicing Technology… is indeed feasible."

Simon pondered for a few seconds before nodding.

The three Universal Civilizations had communicated with each other during the war mobilization phase, and they had briefly introduced most of their trump cards to facilitate dispatch. Therefore, the upper echelons of the federation and church all knew that the dynasty had the Spacetime Splicing Technology.

In terms of attacking the camps, everyone had the same opinion. The Spacetime Splicing Technology was extremely suitable for this kind of tactic. Compared to sending the army to take the brunt of the firepower, this was clearly a method with a lower consumption rate. They would only have to pay for a few hundred battleships at most, as well as a group of dispensable suicide squads. It was mainly to be safe and to switch to manual control under unexpected circumstances.

Everyone knew who the suicide squad was.

"Let the Immortals of our army carry out the Spacetime Splicing Operation. This is a job they love," Aurora said while blinking.

"Sure."

Simon had no objections. After pausing for a moment, he added: "The suicide squad better choose low pollution bombs, and they have to be powerful enough. Otherwise, they won't even be able to blow up the base's shield."

After deciding on the method of attack, the group returned to the topic of positioning. There had to be a solution.

"It's not impossible to passively wait for the enemy to attack, but if we can't block the enemy's attacks, our losses will only continue to increase. We need to find a way to protect the various branches of the space anchor."

"With all due respect, it's almost impossible to protect all the Orbit Branches under the over-the-horizon strikes of the enemy whose scale is unknown. After all, there are too many branches, and the number is still increasing. We don't have the Lerbo Space Protection Belt, so we can only try to eliminate the topological space directional marks left behind by the enemy's small troops," an officer said helplessly.

"The enemy is in the dark while we're out in the open, so we can't deal with them for the time being. However, if we can seize and analyze the Lerbo Space Protection Belt, we can also have the same defensive capabilities as the other party and mitigate our passive situation," Simon said. "Therefore, apart from the Spacetime Splicing daring attack, we still have to send official troops based on the situation."

The Spacetime Splicing Technology could only send them to their deaths. They could not obtain the spoils of war, and they had to rely on their high-level combatants.

Currently, the few pieces of good news were that the targets of the World Tree's over-the-horizon strikes were limited. They could either target the topological space directional marks left behind by the reconnaissance troops or take the targets near the base, unable to accurately attack other locations. This meant that every camp was a bait, and the three Universal Civilizations' fleets would only be exposed to the attack range when the fleets attack. Therefore, they were not too worried about being hit by the over-the-horizon strikes.

Kant's army quickly retreated, losing quite a lot of manpower. Most of the exterior armor of the remaining battleships had traces of damage, but they had not completed their mission nor were they able to destroy the World Tree camps.

The only reward was that when they received the other side's over-the-horizon strikes, the artificial intelligence analyzed the locations of the new camps, giving new targets to the three Universal Civilizations.

Not long after, the second fleet set off and split up toward these bases. They were all equipped with the improved Spacetime Splicing Device by the dynasty which would only activate when they arrived at their destination.

The crew members were all temporarily enlisted army players. They did not convey the tragic feeling of a hero leaving and never coming back. The atmosphere of every battleship was very relaxed, and many of the players had happy expressions on their faces. They did not look like a group of death squads, but like they were on a holiday.

"I didn't expect such a suicidal mission to be so rewarding. Luckily, I got it."

"We can complete the mission just by dying, this is too easy."

"How comfortable. If I can come a few more times, wouldn't it be like farming experience points?"

Hearing the excited discussions of the players around him, Frenzied Sword felt very happy.

The players were the designated members of the suicide squad, and only the players could accept this mission. The mission briefly introduced the combat mission of the Spacetime Splicing Force, and the players were shocked to realize that this mission was actually not difficult for them at all. However, the mission reward was so high that even the credit for destroying the enemy base would be given to them.

This meant that he did not have to do anything at all. As long as he sent himself to death, the experience would come flowing in. It was extremely easy and was the same as farming experience!

According to the forums, this combat mission was very important, and it was actually very difficult. It was equivalent to a death mission for normal soldiers. However, their natural advantage happened to counter this difficulty, so they could obtain a high reward that did not seem to match the difficulty at all.

Not many players were willing to miss such a good opportunity. Due to the limited number of slots available, many players almost fought over it, and only a very small number of people obtained the chance to go on the expedition.

Amidst the excited atmosphere of the players, the various fleets arrived at different World Tree camps. Without a word, they activated the Spacetime Splicing Device and moved toward the base.

All kinds of long-range attacks came one after another, shattering the fleet. However, the next moment, the fleet returned to normal and continued to jump forward. Very soon, they entered the Lerbo Space Protection Belt and were unaffected.

When the Spacetime Splicing Army was halfway there, the World Tree camps realized that this was an unknown spacetime technology through their space radar. They quickly stopped their regular attacks and used spacetime methods to target the Spacetime Splicing Army.

The Spacetime Splicing Technology was not unsolvable, and its nemesis was the spacetime technology. Back then, the dynasty had also used the same method to crack this technology from the Kunde Race. The World Tree camps' response was very effective, and the frame skip of the Spacetime Splicing Technology began to decrease.

However, after many years of improvements by the Crimson Dynasty—although the Spacetime Splicing Technology was still restrained by the spacetime methods—its resistance had already greatly increased, and it could last for a longer time. The Spacetime Splicing Technology Team, which was equipped with high-energy bombs, resisted the attacks of the World Tree camps and stubbornly passed through the Lerbo Spacetime Protection Belt, exploding among the camps.

Amidst the shock waves, dazzling energy clusters lit up in the universe one after another, engulfing the entire encampment.

At the same time, in the temporary base of the Black Star Army, white light flashed, and the army players who acted as a suicide squad were revived in the stronghold.

Frenzied Sword opened the interface, looked at the mission that had been completed, and smiled.

"Nice, nice. After eating this reward, my level should be higher than the players in the first tier… I wonder if this kind of mission is a one-time thing. I really hope it comes a few more times."

With the assault of the Spacetime Splicing Technology, the three Universal Civilizations were able to effectively attack the World Tree's camps.

The World Tree did not have a good solution for this kind of black technology. They could only continue to carry out their original strategy and continuously destroy the anchoring orbit of the three Universal Civilizations, while the three Universal Civilizations continued to send people to destroy the exposed camps.

As the Spacetime Splicing Force was not afraid of conventional attacks, the World Tree reduced the over-the-horizon strikes at the incoming fleet, not wanting to expose the locations of more camps without reason. Using this advantage, the three Universal Civilizations secretly sent out a wave of normal fleets led by high-level combatants, mixed in with the Spacetime Splicing Force, and successfully broke through a camp. They seized a Lerbo Space Protection Belt and hurriedly sent it back to the interception circle's main base for analysis.

At the enormous frontline research institute, the generator of the Lerbo Space Protection Belt was suspended in a vacuum bubble. A large number of mechanical needles were inserted into the structure of the device, continuously testing the parameters and derivation principles. Countless technicians were busy in front of different instruments.

Simon and the other high-ranked officers were also paying attention to the progress of the analysis at the research institute. The remote projection stood on the ground, showing the image of the Lerbo Space Protection Belt midair.

"It was originally just an attempt, I didn't expect to obtain this device in reality. The expedition team was almost wiped out."

"If we can analyze this technology, not only will we be able to deal with the enemy's over-the-horizon strikes, but our interception circle will also be harder to break."

Just as they were rejoicing, the lights of the research institute suddenly turned into a blinding blood-red color, and a buzzing alarm sounded.

"Warning! Warning! Detected unknown data trying to infiltrate the firewall…"

The technicians present were shocked and quickly checked the source of the problem.

"What's going on?" Simon's expression changed.

"Reporting, this device seized from the frontline seems to be carrying some kind of highly latent data virus. It is invading the firewall on its own and trying to obtain information from our database…" the research team leader hastily replied.

"Where's the investigation report? Why didn't we find this virus before?" Simon asked.

"This… All the tests were passed… We can only explain that this unknown virus escaped our detection," The research team leader gritted his teeth.

At this time, the frequency of the alarm increased once again. Many technicians were sweating and shouting.

"Level 1 firewall has been broken! Level 2 firewall has been broken!"

"Too fast! This virus is invading too quickly!"

"Requesting immediate activation of main artificial intelligence to suppress it!"

Simon hurriedly looked at the screen of the technicians and saw that this unknown virus had broken through the layers of the firewall and was about to officially enter the interception circle base's quantum network.

However, at this moment, streams of silver data suddenly appeared and wrapped around the unknown virus. It was as if the white blood cells had swallowed a virus. No matter how hard the virus tried, it could not break free from the blockage of the silver data and slowed down.

A large amount of silver data appeared once again and condensed into Manison's virtual body with a calm expression.

"Mechanic Emperor!" Simon's eyes lit up.

"I sensed the fluctuations in the network. It seems like there's something wrong here… Is this the virus of the World Tree?"

Manison extended his hand and grabbed the struggling unknown virus.

Upon seeing this, Simon immediately asked: "How's the situation?"

"This thing is a virus-type artificial intelligence, not just data."

Manison replied calmly.

This time, the unknown virus suddenly exploded and disappeared. The alarm at the research institute immediately stopped, and the lights returned to normal.

"You destroyed him?" Simon was stunned.

"No, he realized that he could not break through my blockade, so he disintegrated on his own… If I'm not wrong, this artificial intelligence is a member of the World Tree, and he can also enjoy the revival of the World Tree. He has an innate advantage in the quantum network, and most firewalls can't stop him."

Manison narrowed his eyes.

"I see…" Simon pondered for a few seconds before his expression relaxed. "Luckily, you're here this time. Otherwise, even if we could get rid of him, we would have leaked some information. "

The three Universal Civilizations could also have eliminated this artificial intelligence virus by utilizing more artificial intelligence computing power, but they were a step too late. If not for Manison's high-speed reaction, the enemy's artificial intelligence virus might have invaded the quantum network and shared information with the World Tree.

Due to the lack of intelligence, the previous attack had failed. Thus, the World Tree had used more methods to gather information about the three Universal Civilizations. So naturally, there was no lack of information warfare.

"Black Star isn't here. Leave this to me."

Manison calmly replied and deactivated the virtual body.

Upon hearing this, Simon exhaled.

Currently, when the strongest Mechanic in the galaxy was mentioned, everyone's first thought was Black Star, which caused the Mechanic Emperor's presence to decrease.

However, he could not underestimate the Mechanic Emperor just because of Black Star's strength. After all, he was at the peak of the Mechanic class from the previous generation, and his strength was still there. If the conflict of ideals was not mentioned, Simon still believed in the Mechanic Emperor's abilities.

Although they had temporarily lost Black Star's help, the three Universal Civilizations were still able to fight the World Tree back and forth with the foundation laid by Han Xiao.

Both sides used all kinds of Universal Treasures and special technologies to restrain each other, temporarily unable to do anything to each other.

The World Tree would occasionally send out some foreign experts to test the waters. Due to Black Star's existence, the World Tree had already turned these foreign experts into cannon fodder. Since they could not be used on the battlefield, they might as well use them to harass and exhaust the enemy.

However, because Han Xiao had entered the Sanctum, the foreign experts of the World Tree did not receive Virtual Purification and could only be killed by the Beyond Grade As of the explored universe.

However, even without Black Star's support, the Beyond Grade As were still able to hold their own and did not cause any trouble.

The two sides fought back and forth, while silently building up their strength.

After two months, Han Xiao returned from the Sanctum.

Chapter 1348: Return and Technology Treasure

In the vast starry sky, a golden spark suddenly flashed and expanded into a vortex, spitting Han Xiao out. Then, the Sanctum passageway disappeared.

Han Xiao quickly regained his senses.

"Although this is only my second experience, this feeling is quite incredible…"

Han Xiao muttered to himself. He quickly adjusted his thoughts and looked down. The Sanctum mark had already disappeared and the interface could be opened again. The notification of entering the First Sanctum popped up.

Every time he entered a different Sanctum, his authority would be increased by one. He had calculated it before entering, and only then did his authority in the First Sanctum reach level eight.

After organizing his thoughts, Han Xiao stored the technological information from the First Sanctum in his memory palace. He then took out his communicator and looked at it.

"The last time I entered the Third Sanctum, I was there for more than three months. This time, only about two months have passed. The higher the authority, the closer the convergence of time flow. In such a short time, there shouldn't be any problems with the war… right?"

Han Xiao immediately called Simon's number. After two rings, the call was picked up.

Simon appeared on the screen with a look of surprise.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you're finally back!"

Hmm? This tone of impatient expectancy sounds like the reaction of someone meeting their savior when they're in trouble… Could something bad have happened?

Could it be that they need me to turn the tide? It can't be that coincidental, right ‽

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat and a bunch of thoughts flashed through his mind. He asked, "I'd only disappeared for about two months. Did something happen on your side?"

"Although there are some changes, we can still handle it." Through the screen, Simon could not feel Han Xiao's mentality. He smiled and said, "Now that you're back, we have more confidence."

After hearing Simon's explanation, Han Xiao knew that he had misunderstood.

His teammates were still quite strong. Losing him for a few months would not affect them much. He was relieved. He felt as if he had found his backbone again and could finally rely on others.

That was right. With the foundation from before, the three Universal Civilizations would not be so weak, he was worrying too much.

After hearing the current situation, Han Xiao stroked his chin and said:

"So, the World Tree has built a beyond-visual-range encampment and is firing at us. The construction of the interception circle and space anchoring orbit is meeting huge resistance… If we want to destroy the enemy's strategy, we have to start from finding their positions, right?"

"That is the situation. However, we are currently in a passive position. Only when the other party fires, will we be able to lock onto them. The other conventional detection methods have all been blocked…" Simon explained.

"Hmm… The World Tree chose to build camps at a jump point further away from our territory. This is indeed difficult to handle…"

"You don't have any ideas either?" Although Simon did not have much hope, he could not help but feel discouraged when he saw that even Black Star did not seem to have any ideas.

Because Han Xiao had always been very reliable, the three Universal Civilizations' officers had already put a 'know-it-all' halo on him in their hearts. For him to encounter a problem that he could not solve, although they would not have any problems with it logically, they more or less felt a little depressed.

"I'm not sure yet. Let me take a look at the situation first."

Han Xiao did not give a definite response.

Facing the situation that Simon had mentioned, his brain was working rapidly, sifting through one plan after another, while also looking for any technology that could be used in this area… Not to mention, the information that he had obtained from the First Sanctum this time did indeed mention a special detection technology that was suitable for this situation. It came from an advanced civilization of past Iteration, and it was especially used in beyond-visual-range warfare against enemies whose coordinates were unknown.

According to the data, this civilization's specialty was in beyond-visual-range warfare. Even without the aid of wormholes and stargates, they could accurately strike targets across multiple Star Fields.

The First Sanctum contained countless mechanical technologies. He had only dug out a small part of them this time, but it was still an enormous treasure trove of technology. It was not that he wanted to get rid of the old, but it was far more comprehensive than Jayz's treasure.

With the experience and accumulation of many different civilizations of past Iterations, he was able to deal with all kinds of situations and had a targeted solution to many battle tactics. This was an advantage that Jayz's treasure could not provide.

Originally, the World Tree Civilization had devoured the accumulation of many civilizations, so they had a certain advantage on the battlefield. This information was enough to close the gap between the two sides and even gain an advantage.

To the three Universal Civilizations, this wave of technological information was like a timely gift, a priceless treasure!

This way, even if the revival mechanism and resource conversion of the World Tree was impossible to solve, the three Universal Civilizations would be able to last longer and buy more time for the secondary dimension expedition team.

"With this batch of technological information, I have a higher chance of dealing with the World Tree Civilization… It's a pity that none of the past Iterations have met an opponent like the World Tree. It would have been great if they had a targeted device."

Han Xiao was overjoyed but also a little regretful.

After this trip to the Sanctum, he made a discovery. Every Sanctum stored different types of information. The First Sanctum mainly focused on machinery, but he did not find any Information Form technology.

If the five Super classes corresponded to one Sanctum, he guessed that the additional Sixth Sanctum would contain information related to the Information Form, which was the best weapon against the World Tree.

However, the Sixth Sanctum Key was too difficult to synthesize, and it was completely different from the other five Sanctums. Han Xiao had never even heard the names of some of the materials.

While he was thinking, Simon spoke again.

"Sanctum Revival succeeded?"

"Hmm, there is one final step left. I need to gather the other Beyond Grade As to hold the fort and prevent any trouble."

Han Xiao nodded. He could not help but think about the revival of the World Tree.

According to his previous life experiences, the revival speed of most of the World Tree powerhouses varied from two to eight months. The revival time of peak Beyond Grade As usually fluctuated between five to eight months, and the revival time of the Tree King was different.

"That's good. Come to the main base. I'll gather everyone and wait for you." Simon was overjoyed.

"Okay, I'll be there later."

Han Xiao hung up and called Oathkeeper.

This time, it rang for thirty seconds before the call was reluctantly picked up.

"You're back," Oathkeeper appeared on the screen, expressionless.

"…Why do you look so unhappy?"

"I'm very happy."

This sentence, coupled with your dead fish face and flat tone, is not convincing at all!

Han Xiao thought to himself and said helplessly:

"Alright, I'm just informing you that I'm back. There are many direct descendants among the targets of this revival, so I can't send them to the Holy Accord."

"Oh."

"…If you have nothing to say, I'm hanging up."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He ended the communication, changed into the King, and disappeared.

On the other side, at the Holy Accord's base.

Oathkeeper, who was sitting before the card table, put down his communicator. He turned around and saw the members of the Holy Accord staring at him with burning eyes.

"Black Star is back ‽"

"Finally, another batch of people will be revived. There might be some of my enemies among them."

"Hahahaha, these people can't join the Holy Accord. If we let them join the battle, we don't have to go out."

"Letting those direct descendants die on the battlefield will indirectly avenge us. Black Star is amazing!"

In the room, many revivors had intense reactions. They threw down the cards in their hands, and the atmosphere was jubilant.

Seeing this, Oathkeeper's hand tightened around the card, and his heart was filled with jealousy.

Boss's experience card had expired again…

...

In the conference room at the interception circle's main base, everyone gathered and surrounded the throne. A beam of light flashed, and Han Xiao, who was wearing the King, teleported over.

"The president is back!" "Army Commander!" "Your Excellency Black Star!"

Upon seeing Han Xiao, everyone greeted him.

"Thank you for your hard work during my absence."

Han Xiao put away the King, smiled, and waved his hands. He had the style of a leader, and everyone present was used to it.

"When will we complete the Sanctum Revival?" Simon walked up and asked.

Hearing this, most of the Beyond Grade As looked at Han Xiao curiously. Most of them only knew about the Sanctum Revival but had never seen how it was carried out.

"There's no hurry. Let me take a look at the current situation."

Han Xiao shook his head and walked straight to the command station. He pulled up the surveillance and the battle reports from the past few days and quickly browsed through them.

Seeing this, the others did not rush him and followed behind him, not disturbing Han Xiao's observation.

However, this scene gave many people a strange feeling. For some reason, they felt as though their work was being reviewed by the leader.

After a while, Han Xiao looked at Simon and said:

"I'm clear about the situation. I have an idea that might be able to restrain the World Tree's strategy of the beyond-visual-range encampment."

"You really have a way ‽"

Simon froze.

"Just a moment ago, you said that you were not confident. Now, after seeing the situation, you have already thought of a countermeasure. So fast ‽"

"I have a special detection technology that might be able to solve the positioning problem…" Han Xiao took out the information of the technology from his memories and hid the details of the technology. He gave a rough outline of the theory and effect, showing the group.

Simon quickly finished reading the information, and his expression became even more surprised.

"If this technology is real, not only will we be able to solve the current tug-of-war, but we will also be able to change the direction of our future decisions. This will bring more new tactics and expand our tactical portfolio!"

The Beyond Grade As also took a look at the technical introduction. The Mechanics among them were shocked and could not help but size Han Xiao up.

Compared to the others, the experts were more shocked. One look and they knew that as long as they followed the blueprints and created the real thing, it would definitely be a Universal Treasure-level device. Just this technology alone was enough to change the way an advanced civilization fought!

Not only did Black Star's combat capability improve rapidly, but even his research and development capabilities had reached such a level? When did he develop such strategic detection technology ‽

Han Xiao looked around and nodded.

"Of course it's true. I can share a portion of the technology and let the three Universal Civilizations build the framework for the military factories. I'll be in charge of the core, splitting up the work to increase efficiency."

He did not plan to hide some of the technologies that would be helpful in the war. He only held onto the core technology, while the three Universal Civilizations provided resources to build the other aspects, increasing the three Universal Civilizations' capital to fight the World Tree.

"Good! As expected of the special consultant. I will ask the three leaders!"

Simon immediately became excited.

Black Star had just returned, but he had already proposed a solution to the problem that had troubled them for two months. Not only was he extraordinarily intelligent, but he also had achievements in strategic technology… Black Star was indeed reliable as ever!

Looking at everyone's surprised expressions, Han Xiao remained calm and did not take credit for it.

Strictly speaking, this was not his own ability but the strength of the advanced civilizations of the past Iterations. He was just standing on the shoulders of the giants and had grasped the information difference. He had nothing to be proud of.

Putting away his thoughts, Han Xiao waved his hands and said with a solemn tone:

"Let's put this aside for now and choose a place for me to use the Sanctum Revival. This time, it won't be like the past. For sure, there would be many people among this batch of Revivors who won't accept us requesting them to participate in the war. I don't wish for any accidents. All Beyond Grade As, follow me!"

"Okay!"

Everyone's expression turned serious as they agreed.

Chapter 1349: Revival and Declaration

On a man-made planet in the Flickering World, the silver land laid out by engineering alloys was boundless and covered the entire planet. There were no buildings on the ground yet and the entire planet was a round silver sphere with only the most basic geological modification.

Over a hundred Beyond Grade As were in the middle of the vast silver plain, their eyes focused on Han Xiao's back.

To reduce any unexpected factors, the three Universal Civilizations chose a planet in their territory as the venue for the Sanctum Revival, and many Beyond Grade As followed Han Xiao to use the teleportation device.

The three Universal Civilizations did not deploy any fleets in the outer space of the planet. They only deployed Space Stabilization Anchors, as well as hidden super-visory weapons in further locations. They used long-range equipment to observe the situation from afar, so the outer space of the planet looked empty without any armed forces.

This was Han Xiao's suggestion. All Beyond Grade As had tempers and if they were forced to negotiate with someone the moment they woke up, they would surely be unhappy. So it might not be beneficial for both sides to come into contact right away. This time, the three Universal Civilizations had a favor to ask. The other parties were also famous historical figures. They were all people with high statuses, so it was not suitable for them to put on such a tough attitude right from the start. On the contrary, having communication among Beyond Grade As would be no problem at all.

If physical persuasion was needed, Han Xiao and a group of Beyond Grade As would be enough. Only the strong would be respected. This was the unspoken rule among Beyond Grade As. If military forces were to interfere, it might have the opposite effect.

"Then I shall begin."

Han Xiao looked back and saw everyone nodding in agreement. He then looked away and activated the Sanctum Revival Brand on the back of his hand.

A golden light suddenly blossomed and shot out like a silk thread, condensing into glowing objects on the plains in front of everyone. They slowly solidified and turned into various life forms. The energy fluctuations resonated with each other as if a storm had appeared out of thin air, blowing everyone's hair and clothes.

All the Beyond Grade As stared at the scene, afraid to miss anything.

"They're alive!"

"So this is how the resurrections are done. It's not what I expected. I thought there would be an incubation process or something similar."

"Speaking of which, what is this principle? It looks so magical."

A series of surprised whispers came from behind him, but Han Xiao pretended not to hear them. He carefully observed the revivals.

Direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations, direct descendants of the Super Star Cluster, neutral Beyond Grade As… The organization of the Revivors this time is more complicated than the previous two, and the conflicts are probably more intense.

Han Xiao was mentally prepared.

At this moment, the revivors finally woke up from their daze and looked at each other in shock, sizing up the unknown environment and people around them.

"What's going on?"

"Illusion? Dream? Virtual world? What did the Federation of Light do to me?"

"Hmm? It's you! I crushed your head with my own hands. How are you still alive ‽"

After the group of Revivors had seen the situation around them, the scene gradually became chaotic. A gaseous flame emerged from their bodies, and their energy quickly entered an unstable active state. They entered combat mode, and many people who had enmity with each other started to move. As for some neutral people who did not understand the situation, they frowned and quietly retreated to the side. Their visual organs spun around, as they observed the situation.

Just as Han Xiao was about to speak, a tall male life form looked over and stared at Han Xiao and the others. He slowly spoke out.

"If I'm not wrong, all of us are dead. Did you resurrect us?"

He was wearing a gorgeous Divine Official robe, and his voice was solemn and ancient. It had a calming aura that quickly suppressed the chaos in the entire venue, attracting the attention of all the revivors present to him. Following his line of sight, they locked onto Han Xiao and the others.

Are you trying to steal my lines?

Han Xiao looked at him carefully, and his consciousness filtered through the database. Very soon, he found the information of this man who spoke.

Hilbert Mueller was a direct Esper of the Arcane Church, a peak Beyond Grade A Super. His ability was related to space, and he was once the pillar of the Arcane Church. He had a senior and aloof status as the previous master of the Arcane Church, before Wuornos!

This was because Wuornos' ability was more suitable for the Arcane Church. After Wuornos grew up, the Arcane Church changed the owner of the national weapon, and Hilbert left his position as the pillar of the Arcane Church. He went out to explore the secondary dimensions. He disappeared during a long-distance exploration, and his fate was left unknown.

From the looks of it now, this guy had crossed the line of life and death. The universe was so big, and the dangers were endless. Han Xiao did not know what he had encountered in the secondary dimension, but he could exclude the possibility of the Celestial Star Alliance. Han Xiao had once learned the appearance and name of the first three batches of 'outsiders' from Jayz. Those people were not in his revival choice for the time being.

Various thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind, but he nodded and replied.

"That's right. I believe you all still have your memories. You've all died long ago and become history. It's the year 783 of the Galaxy Calendar, and many years have passed. I used a method called the Sanctum Revival to wake you all up…"

"It really is revival…"

"Unbelievable. There's such a thing?"

"I thought someone uploaded my remaining consciousness into the virtual world."

The Revivors started to quiet down and were surprised.

They had never thought of this before. At least when they died, not many of them thought that they would again wake up one day.

A female Dynasty human wearing a military uniform narrowed her eyes and asked Han Xiao,

"Then who are you?"

"You can call me Black Star, the only ruler of the Sanctum Revival, the consultant of the three Universal Civilizations, and the current Beyond Grade A president." Han Xiao introduced himself and added with a smile, "I was once an ally of the dynasty, so we could be considered to have some relationship, Your Excellency Reeve."

"So, you're one of us?"

Reeve's expression softened.

She was one of the pillars of the dynasty, a peak Beyond Grade A Mage. Her nickname was 'Demonic Empress', and her combat strength was outstanding.

Hearing Han Xiao's title, it sounded like he was on the side of the three Universal Civilizations. At the same time, Han Xiao claimed to be an ally of the Dynasty, so Reeve felt that he was not an enemy.

She turned around to observe the Beyond Grade As behind Han Xiao. Suddenly, her gaze stopped on Clotti, and a surprised smile appeared on her face.

"Isn't this Little Darkie? You're still alive?!"

Everyone looked over and saw the usually cold Clotti's face twitching slightly. He quietly shuffled his feet as if he wanted to hide himself in the crowd.

"Hey, Clotti! Don't pretend you don't know me. I saw you. Where are you trying to hide?"

Reeve had her hands on her waist. Her voice was rough, as though like a lion roaring.

Han Xiao could not help but rub his buzzing ears. He felt that this woman and Sun Hunter had a lot in common, they either remained quiet or shouted at the top of their voices.

"…We meet again."

A rare look of reluctance flashed across Clotti's face, but he still forced himself to respond.

In terms of seniority, Reeves could be said to be his senior. She had taught him, together with the other National Pillars, for some time. When Clotti was still weak, she had left a deep psychological shadow in his heart and could be considered half a teacher.

What made Clotti's scalp tingle the most was that Reeve would flirt with him, making moves towards him on purpose.

Speaking of which, Reeve could be considered a seductive beauty. If it was under normal circumstances, he would not have avoided her, but the problem was… this guy was a postnatal transgender. She was not like Lotus Swordsman, who had no choice in the say of her gender. Furthermore, it was not a decision made when Reeve was weak, but a decision made after she became a Beyond Grade A Super. The reason was weird; put in Reeve's words, "once you get tired of being a man, try being a woman"!

Although the Galactic Era was open and the change of sex was widely accepted, Clotti had never liked the new trend. He could still accept it if they got along normally, but being teased made him feel a chill down his spine. He really could not accept it. This mentality was probably…

I treat you as a brother, but you actually want to sleep with me?!

"Ahem, everyone, now is not the time for small talk."

Han Xiao quickly interrupted their conversation. He had yet to finish his business. If he allowed these people—who were related to each other—to start recognizing and chatting everyone up, when would he be done with his business?

"Hmm, that's true. Let's not talk about anything else. You resurrected us for a certain purpose. What exactly is going on?"

The revived person from the Federation of Light also spoke up. This was a Psychic, the direct descendent who was a predecessor of Oulou.

The ones asking questions were mainly the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations, who gathered together on their own. The rest of the revivors looked at the communication between the two sides and quietly obtained information. As for the ten direct descendants of the Super Star Cluster, they hid at the side and maintained a high level of vigilance.

Hearing this question, everyone's mental states perked up. This was what they were most wary of. They were afraid that the revival was done with bad intentions at play.

"Resurrecting isn't just my idea. The three Universal Civilizations and the entire Galactic Society have the same idea as all the Beyond Grade As present." Han Xiao paused and said with a deep voice, "Our hometown has met with a huge crisis, where a foreign Universal Civilization is invading our world. Their strength is beyond imagination and extremely powerful. The war has already broken out, and we need everyone's strength!"

A Universe-level war?!

All the expressions changed.

That was true. If not for this level of danger, there would not have been a need to go through so much trouble to revive so many historical Beyond Grade As. However, from a personal point of view, most of the revivors were unhappy about being used by others.

The revivors looked at the hundreds of Beyond Grade As in front of them and finally understood the situation. The joy of reviving was gone, and they were filled with anger.

"If we're not willing, what will happen? Will you force us?" A neutral Beyond Grade A frowned and said with dissatisfaction.

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "That's not the case. We will try our best to convince everyone that everything is voluntary and we will not force you to participate in the battle."

The Revivors were individuals with free thoughts after all, not slaves. Forcing them was not an option, not only because of their complex identities but also because of the feelings of the other Beyond Grade As.

Using a gun to force the Revivors to compromise would cause many repercussions. One of them was to make the other Beyond Grade As feel the same way. They were worried that they would receive the same treatment after reviving, so it was hard to say how many more association members would be willing to participate in the battle.

Surely there would not be many Revivors who would agree with him through verbal persuasion alone. Furthermore, force was an indispensable part of it. It was difficult for both parties, and Han Xiao had no choice but to grasp the problem. This was even more difficult to deal with than the previous two revivals. Han Xiao had long prepared himself for this hurdle.

This time, a Beyond Grade A with a medium built spoke out.

"We need to ask the upper echelons for their opinion. Can you give us a communicator?"

Han Xiao looked at him and recognized him as a direct member of the Super Star Cluster. His name was Mablo, and he had outstanding combat strength as well. It was a pity that he had died in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles.

"Sure, take it."

Han Xiao did not reject this request. He took out a communicator and threw it at Mablo.

This was the condition of his deal with the Super Star Cluster. With the rich experience of the Super Star Cluster being persecuted, they would surely suspect that the three Universal Civilizations might secretly do something to their high-level combatants during the war, and thus would not allow the experts who had finally revived to participate in the war. Han Xiao did not expect all the revived members of the Super Star Cluster to participate either.

Mablo took the communicator, nodded slightly, and led the other nine members of the Super Star Cluster to contact their upper echelons.

For a moment, the majority of the Revivors fell silent. They exchanged looks among their acquaintances and hesitated to speak.

This time, Reeve let out a breath and said slowly, "Since the Dynasty is in trouble, I will not shirk my duty. Isn't it just a war? As long as the Dynasty gives the order, I am willing to contribute my strength."

"Yeah, me too."

"I was already a dead man to begin with. If the Federation needs my strength to fight the foreign enemies, there's no harm in burning myself again."

With Reeve taking the lead, many direct members of the three Universal Civilizations agreed and expressed their support.

Seeing this, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

The support from most of the direct members of the civilizations was within his expectations. High-level combatants who had undergone long-term patriotic education from the three Universal Civilizations were naturally reliable and willing to contribute to the explored universe.

However, since it involved a second life, things were obviously not going to go so smoothly. While many of the direct descendants expressed their stance, voices of dissent came from the crowd as well.

"Black Star, I'm sorry, but we don't want to continue fighting."

Han Xiao and the others looked over, and their expressions changed.

The person who spoke was not a historical expert, but a member of the association who had died on the battlefield not long ago. His name was Garoze, and he had briefly interacted with Han Xiao before.

The other members of the association who had died also followed beside Garoze. They had reached a consensus and mustered their courage to meet Han Xiao's eyes.

As expected, even the Beyond Grade As who were willing to participate in the battle did not want to take the risk after dying once…

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. Although he was not surprised, he still shook his head and sighed.

However, before he could respond, another Revivor objected.

"I'm sorry, but I don't plan to participate in this war either."

Han Xiao turned around, his gaze startled.

The person who spoke was none other than Hilbert. He was the first direct member of the three Universal Civilizations to reject this conscription.

Reeve looked at him in surprise. "What are you…"

Before she could finish, Hilbert waved his hand and interrupted her.

"I've already sacrificed my life for the three Universal Civilizations and fulfilled my duty. Even if I'm a direct descendant, the Church can't keep asking me to contribute. Even the upper echelons have a choice to retire. Furthermore, I died once, so everything was wiped out. Now that I finally have a second chance, I can't keep working for them forever."

As soon as he said that, many of the direct members of the civilization who were still in dilemma were stunned. They felt that he had spoken the truth and nodded in agreement.

Even the direct descendants of the civilizations who had already expressed their stand were shaken by these words.

The direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations originally wanted to persuade him, but after hearing this, they were speechless.

"This doesn't look good…"

Looking at this scene, the heads of the three Universal Civilizations who were monitoring remotely through the equipment all felt their hearts tighten.

Chapter 1350: Conflict

"This guy…"

Looking at the broadcast on the virtual screen, the Pope's eyes darkened.

Most of the direct descendants were stubborn. From the perspective of the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations, reviving the direct descendants and having them continue working for the three Universal Civilizations was natural. They wished they had the eternal loyalty of the direct descendants, but people's hearts change. Especially after experiencing death once, even the direct descendants were not an exception.

After sacrificing one lifetime for the civilization, they felt that they were even and did not want to be commanded anymore. To the three of them, Hilbert's idea was human nature, but the understanding was not in line with their current interests.

If it was during peaceful times, the three of them would not have minded if the other party wanted to retire. They would even have given him a title of merit, showing the glory that Hilbert had once served the civilization, to increase the loyalty of the other direct descendants. However, the situation was different now, and with Black Star agreeing to the terms of reviving, the three of them were in a difficult position.

After Hilbert finished speaking, the atmosphere fell silent again.

Hilbert looked around, then looked at Han Xiao and asked, "What do you think?"

Han Xiao did not reply immediately. Instead, he looked at Kasuyi with a meaningful look.

Kasuyi was stunned. "Hmm? Why are you looking at me?"

"Nothing, I'm just looking."

Han Xiao looked away.

Tsk, the Arcane Church is indeed full of traitors…

Although Hilbert's act of expressing his desires could not exactly be considered traitorous, it affected the mentality of the other Revivors, and in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders, he was probably no different from a traitor.

Various thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He smiled and nodded.

"Your request is quite reasonable. Indeed, no one says that one has to work forever after becoming a direct descendant of a civilization. Even ordinary people have the privilege to retire. As someone who died for the civilization, you naturally have the right to do so."

"So you have no objections?"

Hilbert raised an eyebrow.

"I personally understand, but I don't have the final say in this matter. The three Universal Civilizations bought the quota for your Sanctum Revivals from me, and they have paid the deposit. If the three Universal Civilizations wish to reduce the quota, I can cancel it."

Han Xiao spread out his hands and continued, "In times of war, every resource has to be put to use. If you don't show your usefulness, I guess they won't be willing to pay."

"In that case, take my life back."

Hilbert opened his arms with a calm expression.

Seeing this, everyone looked at Han Xiao and Hilbert with complicated emotions.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Was this guy really willing to give up the second life that he had painstakingly obtained? That was impossible. This was just a method of retreating in order to advance. He was certain that the three Universal Civilizations would not kill him, or else in the eyes of the other Revivors, it would be no different from a forced threat. This would go against their original intentions, causing more Beyond Grade As to waver, further damaging the loyalty of some of the direct descendants, making them feel like they were forever enslaved.

Just as Han Xiao was about to speak, he suddenly received a message from the three Universal Civilizations' leaders. He looked at it and shook his head.

"Heh, you can rest assured. The three Universal Civilizations have just expressed that they will still pay for your revival and will not take back your life."

The three Universal Civilizations reacted quickly, unwilling to damage the loyalty of more direct descendants.

"That's good." Hilbert lowered his arm without changing his expression as if he had already expected this.

Immediately after, he turned around and pointed at some of the revived direct descendants who had agreed with him.

"Since you did not reject our request and did not force us to join the battle, we should be able to leave?"

Han Xiao smiled and said slowly:

"You're mistaken. You can't leave on your own. You can only follow us."

Hearing this, the faces of many revivors changed slightly.

Hilbert narrowed his eyes. "You mean to put us under house arrest?"

"You can think of it this way. All of you have been dead for a long time and have just revived. You don't know much about the current galactic society. At the same time, the composition of the organizations is quite complicated. Because the current war situation is tense, in order to reduce unexpected factors, we will conduct unified supervision. None of you can move freely before you get permission."

Han Xiao's expression did not change, but his tone was firm.

This was a plan that had been devised long ago. Even if he did not force all these revivors to participate in the battle, he would not allow them to move freely. Otherwise, there would be no need for him to bring so many Beyond Grade As over.

This time, Garoze and the others could not help but say:

"Us too?"

Han Xiao looked at them and said with an expressionless face, "All of you died in battle against the World Tree. Of course, you don't have to receive such treatment. Come over."

In reality, he did not want to let these people go either, but he had to take care of the thoughts of the association members behind him. He still had to give differential treatment.

With his current position, he had no choice but to mediate and balance the thoughts of all parties. It was human nature to seek benefits and avoid harm. He couldn't make people from different sides give up fighting for their own benefits.

Garoze and the others heaved a sigh of relief. Under the gazes of both parties, they left the position of the Revivors and stood among the Beyond Grade As behind Han Xiao. As long as they obtained the benefits they wanted, they naturally had no intention of standing on the same side as these Revivors.

The Beyond Grade As glanced at Garoze, not having any intention of looking down on him.

Hilbert did not speak, but the neutral Revivors did.

"How long is the house arrest?" a dark gold-skinned Revivor asked in a deep voice. His aura was even more oppressive than Hilbert's.

Everyone looked over, and their hearts skipped a beat.

Nilfgadi, the first Divine Throne Mechanic in history, the founder of the Machinery Faith!

All the Mechanics with the Machinery Faith bonuses were enjoying his protection. To a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, he was like the founder.

Han Xiao nodded and explained.

"Your Excellency Nilfgadi, there is no fixed time limit for the house arrest. Everything will be done according to the specific circumstances. Everyone will have to go through a long one-on-one screening. You will only be allowed to leave after we make sure nothing unexpected will happen."

Hearing this, another neutral Beyond Grade A sneered.

"The criteria for the screening are decided by you guys. You can say whatever you want. I'm very curious, will our house arrest continue indefinitely if we don't agree to participate in the war?"

Han Xiao turned around.

The person who spoke was called Aegon Vardnadze, nicknamed 'Flowing Flame'. He was a peak Beyond Grade A and a shapeshift type Esper. He was from the same era as Dylan and was also an influential figure who had died in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles. At this moment, he looked at Han Xiao and the others with undisguised hostility.

Right then, a bunch of powerful people were revived. There were all kinds of extraordinary people.

"Of course not."

Han Xiao replied casually.

The direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations, the direct descendants of the Super Star Cluster, as well as the Beyond Grade As whose deaths had nothing to do with the three Universal Civilizations. Even if these people were not willing to participate in the battle, they would not do anything too extreme. However, the people who died at the hands of the three Universal Civilizations or the Tragedy of the Pinnacles were completely different. Their hatred was deep, and this was a thorn that was difficult to deal with.

Aegon Vardnadze coldly glanced at Hilbert and the rest of the revived direct descendants and said indifferently, "You received payment to revive these direct descendants, but you voluntarily revived us neutral Beyond Grade As, right?"

"You can say that." Han Xiao nodded.

"Heh, I thank you for letting me live, and I owe you a favor. However, if you want to use this favor to hold me hostage to fight the enemies of the three Universal Civilizations, that's impossible!"

Aegon Vardnadze stood with his arms crossed, and streams of red light flowed around his body. The temperature of the area rose rapidly as he said with a firm tone:

"I'm telling you clearly that I will not accept the three Universal Civilizations' house arrest. This is the same as being prisoned. They will never let us victims of the Tragedy of the Pinnacles go. I'm leaving right now. Who wants to leave with me?"

Rumble!

As soon as he said that, many Beyond Grade As who had died in the Tragedy of the Pinnacles burst out with their auras and echoed with their actions. Some neutral Beyond Grade As who were not willing to be placed under house arrest also stood up, wanting to use the strength of the group to leave this place.

A huge energy wave spread out, and the alloy ground trembled, with depressions appearing one after another.

The direct members of the three Universal Civilizations, the direct members of the Super Star Cluster, and some neutral Beyond Grade As immediately retreated to the side. They did not plan to help any side and decided to watch the show and act according to the situation.

The direct members of the Super Star Cluster who had retreated to the side communicated telepathically.

"We're not going to attack? This is a good opportunity to break out."

"I just contacted the upper echelons. They told us not to act rashly and listen to their arrangements for the time being."

Mablo paused and looked at Han Xiao in surprise.

"Also, the upper echelons specifically told me not to mess with that Black Star fellow… I will die."

At the same time, the aura of Aegon Vardnadze and the others rose rapidly, and the atmosphere became tense.

Seeing this, Han Xiao's smile gradually disappeared.

"We won't force you to take part in the battle, but it's a must for you to be grounded. There's no room for negotiation. You're all seniors with high statuses, and I don't wish to use force. However, if you make things difficult for me, I can only make you suffer a little. Don't choose the hard way."

With that, the Beyond Grade As behind him spread out and formed a semi-circle around Aegon Vardnadze and the others.

"Humph, that's more like it." Aegon Vardnadze's aura was boiling as he shouted, "You want to solve the problem with just words? You're dreaming. Either you back off obediently or use your fists to make me give in. This is the rule between Beyond Grade As. If you want to stop me, you can give it a try!"

Bang!

Raging flames gushed out, using energy as fuel, as though it would never go out. The alloys on the ground melted instantly!

Aegon Vardnadze's body changed in an instant. His body expanded and turned into a strange giant-like creature. He looked like the demon in some religious artworks that had walked out of hell, and his body was covered in flames.

The next moment, his four limbs suddenly stomped on the ground, and his entire body shot toward the outer space of the planet like a meteor. He was extremely fast, trying to break through the encirclement.

This was a signal. The many Revivors who stood with him showed their abilities and attacked the Beyond Grade As around them. The energy storm exploded, instantly opening up the chaotic battlefield. The ground shattered under the collision of the Beyond Grade As' abilities, creating huge craters in the blink of an eye. Looking from outer space, it was like the planet had been ruthlessly smashed by an awl, shattering a part of its shell.

"Take him down!"

Han Xiao remained where he was and waved his hand.

Although there were a few powerful individuals among the group, Kakasu and Manison were not to be trifled with. With the help of Clotti, Oulou, and many other direct descendants, they were more than enough to suppress Aegon Vardnadze and the others. There was no need for him to fight personally.

As expected, just as Aegon Vardnadze rushed into outer space, a huge silver Mechanical Deity quickly appeared, and the visual effect almost covered the entire sky. It looked down on the planet from outer space and slammed down, instantly smashing Aegon Vardnadze back to the ground.

Bang!

The alloy ground caved in, twisted, and shattered. Aegon Vardnadze crashed down like a meteor, creating a ring-shaped valley.

What a good Buddha Palm technique!

Han Xiao's eyelids twitched.

On the other side, Kasuyi's eyes flashed and an endless amount of psychic energy gushed out, filling every inch of space. There was almost no place to hide and the continuous mental explosions shook and distorted the movement of many escaping Revivors.

The other revivors did not interfere. They retreated to the edge of the battlefield and only received a little bit of psychic shockwave. They were also shocked and felt a sharp pain in their brains.

"These later generations' Beyond Grade As are not simple…"

"Just one-third of them can stop them. I don't think they can escape."

"The leader, Black Star, has yet to make his move. His strength should not be too far off."

Many of the Revivors who were watching the show whispered among themselves. They were also using this opportunity to observe the strength of the Beyond Grade As of this era.

They had just revived and lost their weapons. Most of them were not at their peak state, especially the Mechanics. If this group of Beyond Grade As was so powerful that they did not see a chance to escape, they would accept the house arrest.

Manison and Kasuyi led a group of association members to fight with Aegon Vardnadze and the others for a while, quickly defeating the weakened Revivors one after another. However, there were a large number of opponents, and there were peak Beyond Grade As as well. Many of the association members were also injured.

Aegon Vardnadze, whose body was covered in wounds, avoided Manison's psionic cannon and collided with the 'Desolate Beast' Mercer. He received a few punches in exchange for injuries, and his sharp claws slammed into Mercer's chest. The concentrated flames entered Mercer's body through a skill and exploded.

Boom!

The flames expanded, and Mercer shot out from the smoke and landed on the ground. His momentum did not decrease, and he plowed out a valley. Black smoke was coming out of his body as if he was burnt inside out, and his injuries were not light.

However, at this moment, Aurora raised her hand and shot out a wave of life energy, hitting Mercer. His charred skin fell off one after another, and new flesh grew out. His injuries disappeared at a speed visible to the naked eye.

"Recovery Esper!"

Aegon Vardnadze's expression changed. Suddenly, he had a flash of insight. He changed his direction and charged toward Aurora.

After the intense battle, he had already realized that it was impossible for him to forcefully break out of the encirclement. Since he could not break through Manison and Kasuyi's blockade, he already had the intention to give in. However, when he saw Aurora's ability, he suddenly had an idea.

Since the three Universal Civilizations were resisting a foreign enemy, recovery-type Espers would surely have a strategic significance to the high-level combatants. If he could get to the recovery-type Esper class and use her as a hostage to negotiate with them, he might be able to successfully leave!

Aegon Vardnadze made up his mind.

One last try!

Just as he changed targets, the Beyond Grade As on the association's side were all furious.

Aurora was their support to fight against the World Tree, and she was a strategic weapon that could maintain the advantage of high-level combatants. However, this guy wanted to put their only healer in danger to escape?!

Even the direct Beyond Grade As, such as Clotti, who did not make a move, could not hold back any longer. They turned into streams of light and charged toward Aegon Vardnadze.

This scene was like poking a hornet's nest. Aegon Vardnadze was shocked, but he did not stop. Instead, he increased his speed and believed that this move would work.

The revivors were also shocked. They were about to continue watching the show, but at this moment, a powerful shockwave swept out!

Buzz!

Han Xiao's figure appeared in front of Aegon Vardnadze like teleportation. The next moment, the black Mechanical Deity rose from the ground and said coldly:

"I know that you have a grudge with the three Universal Civilizations, so it's not a problem for you to vent your anger. However, if you wish to attack our important strategic figure, you're courting death!"

Han Xiao did not hesitate at all. He opened his palm, and a strong restraining force field was applied on Aegon Vardnadze, temporarily freezing him in midair. Then, the army of soldiers separated from the Mechanical Deity and fired at him.

Wave after wave of attacks rained down on Aegon Vardnadze without holding back. No matter how Aegon Vardnadze tried to escape, the mechanical army chased after and bombarded him.

"I surrender! Stop attacking!"

Aegon Vardnadze hurriedly admitted defeat, but Han Xiao ignored him.

The Beyond Grade As who were rushing over stopped in their tracks and the revivors who were watching the battle were also shocked. How could they not see that this was killing intent?

Regardless of how Aegon Vardnadze surrendered or retaliated in despair, Han Xiao ignored all of them. He chased him for a long time before finally blasting him to death, leaving only an incomplete body falling from the sky.

The battle of breaking the encirclement had long stopped, and everyone could only watch as Han Xiao killed Aegon Vardnadze. No matter how Aegon Vardnadze fought back, he could not escape Black Star's control. The difference in strength was completely overwhelming.

Just as the revivors were surprised by Black Star's killing move, Hila grabbed Aegon Vardnadze's corpse, pulled out a soul, and threw it into the Underworld, attracting everyone's attention.

Seeing that everyone was looking at her, Hila did not mind and snorted.

"Black Star can give all of you a new life, but he can also take your lives. If you continue to be so shameless, I'll send all of you to hell!"

Chapter 1351: No One Believes

"Underworld?"

Hearing the word, a commotion broke out among the revivors. Because the era was different, their reactions were also different.

Some people knew what the Underworld was, and they looked at Hila with shock and doubt. Some were confused and did not know what this meant. After asking around, they finally understood the significance of the Underworld. Their expressions changed, and they felt a strong sense of fear.

Nilfgadi, who had been watching the show, frowned and looked at Hila.

"Speaking of which, that recovery-type Esper's ability is very familiar. What's your relationship with Nerkese and Eros?"

He was also a Primordial One, and he had been in the same era as the two sisters of the Underworld. From the start, he felt that Hila and Aurora's abilities had a familiar aura.

Hila looked down at him and said calmly, "Both of them died long ago. We inherited [Dawn of Life] and [Power of the Dead] respectively, as well as the Underworld that they left behind."

"So that's how it is…" Nilfgadi nodded slowly and did not say anything else.

Seeing that he had no other questions, Hila ignored him and looked at everyone.

"Black Star has already given you enough face. Don't push your luck. As I said before, if you don't want to live, you can continue to make a fuss. Let's see if we can send all of you to the Underworld!"

"Hila! Everyone here is a senior. Watch your words." Han Xiao put up an act of scolding.

"Humph." Hila threw away the remains of Aegon Vardnadze and retreated into the crowd.

Listening to the two of them singing a duet, some of the revivors had ugly expressions on their faces, but they did not dare do anything extreme.

The threat of the Underworld was not small. Compared to entering the Underworld, house arrest seemed more acceptable…

Furthermore, the overwhelming strength that Black Star had displayed by playing Aegon Vardnadze like a game and killing him made many of the revivors wary.

However, although Aegon Vardnadze was killed, most of the revivors did not feel sympathetic. They had seen the entire process, so they naturally knew that it was not Black Star who started it, but Aegon Vardnadze who brought it upon himself.

On the other hand, the Beyond Grade As on Han Xiao's side did not feel disgusted. Instead, they felt happy. It was Aegon Vardnadze's fault for being so daring. Even if Black Star had not made a move, many people would still have wanted to kill him.

Killing people to establish his prestige would easily make people think that he was forcing the revivors to do something. To prevent such repercussions, Han Xiao originally did not want to kill anyone. However, Aegon Vardnadze courting death was a special case. To be able to make both sides think that he deserved to die was simply amazing.

Just as he had been worrying about how to establish his prestige, Aegon Vardnadze sent him an excellent opportunity without causing any backlash. He was a great person who had given him timely help. He would feel bad if he did not ask the eight Underworld brothers to take care of him!

Seeing that the revivors had stopped the commotion, Han Xiao knew that this act of killing the chicken to warn the monkeys had worked.

However, this was not enough. His main goal was not to put them under house arrest but to convince them to join the war willingly.

Han Xiao took a deep breath and said:

"Inviting all of you to participate in the war is not asking you to contribute for free. This is also a deal. I believe that all of you will be satisfied with this price."

Hearing this, many of the revivors looked interested.

"Oh? What's the reward?"

Hilbert asked curiously.

Han Xiao smiled and went for the strong approach as planned.

"As long as you choose to participate in the battle, no matter how many times you die in battle, I will wake you up again. If there comes a day when we expel the foreign enemies, the participants will forever enjoy the right to revive in the Sanctum and obtain a permanent safety guarantee. However, if you do not participate in the battle this time, there will not be another chance to exchange for it in the future. This is my offer."

The revivors present were stunned for a moment before their hearts skipped a beat.

If that was the case, they would have nothing to worry about. Using the battle in exchange for the right to be revived in the Sanctum would be an extremely profitable deal!

Furthermore, there was also [Dawn of Life] 's current ability user. Their survival on the battlefield was guaranteed, and it would not be so easy to die. It was worth a try!

The only problem was whether Black Star would keep his word.

Observing everyone's reaction, Han Xiao smiled and said, "Don't doubt my sincerity. The Sanctum Revival is not difficult for me. Reviving you guys is just a piece of cake."

Reeve could not help but question, "You mean the Sanctum Revival can be used nonstop? Is there no limit?"

"Hehe, there really isn't. Don't worry, no matter how many times you die, the Sanctum Revival can still take effect."

Han Xiao replied with a smile. When he introduced the situation earlier, he did not repeat the lie that the Sanctum Revival could only be done once, so this batch of revivors did not know.

As soon as he said that, the surrounding association members could not help but look at him. Although they did not have any expression on their faces, they were sighing in their hearts…

Black Star's ability to lie through his teeth was getting better and better!

Many of the association members believed that the Sanctum Revival only had one chance. The lie had been told for so long that they treated it as the truth. They did not believe that Han Xiao was going back on his words. In their eyes, this was just a lie that Black Star had made up to trick these Revivors into joining the battle.

However, no one intended to expose the 'truth'. Tricking more revivors into joining the battle was in their interest, and this lie was ineffective on 'insiders' like them.

This split the difference between the current Beyond Grade As and the revivors. Many of the association members believed that they would not fall for it even after they revived. Thus, there was a difference in treatment, and it would not hurt the interests of their group. Therefore, no one planned to expose Han Xiao's' lie '. Even Garoze and the others who had just revived chose to remain silent. Instead, they felt that Black Star had made a good move.

Looking at the revivors' excited faces, many association members laughed in their hearts. They could not help but feel a sense of superiority as if they had grasped the truth.

At the same time, Kasuyi glanced at his companions around him and knew that no one was taking it seriously. His mouth could not help but twitch.

As someone who knew the truth, he naturally knew that Han Xiao was telling the truth. However, this group of Beyond Grade As had already been fooled by Black Star, and no one believed him!

Kasuyi did not know whether to laugh or cry.

'Forget it, it's not a big problem. When Black Star proves it with his actions, they will know which is the truth…'

He was not worried that Black Star's plan would fail. The members of the three Universal Civilizations and the association would most likely hide the 'truth' for their own benefit. As for the revivors, they would be under unified surveillance and would not be able to freely come into contact with information from the outside world. The three Universal Civilizations would naturally filter out any information that might reveal the 'truth'.

Even if the truth could not be hidden, and the Revivors knew the 'truth', there would still be some direct descent revivors who would voluntarily sacrifice themselves. As long as a group of people died in the battle and the revivals were successfully carried out, everyone would understand what Han Xiao said today was true, and the situation would immediately return to normal, continuing to rush forward.

'There are many backup plans, and everything is under control. Black Star is still very steady…'

Kasuyi secretly praised.

On the other side, many revivors were shaken by Han Xiao's conditions.

Hilbert's eyes flashed.

"If what you said is true, this deal is worth it. I can work for the civilization again and fight against the foreign enemies."

"It's alright. You guys have plenty of time to consider."

Han Xiao smiled.

As he spoke, he waved his hand, and a spaceship landed on the ground. The hatch opened, inviting everyone to board it.

Many of the revivors had already accepted Han Xiao's words, and they obediently boarded the spaceship.

Everyone boarded the starship and quickly set off for the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Point that the three Universal Civilizations had set up nearby.

The cabin was peaceful, and there were no tense confrontations. Many of the current Beyond Grade As had finally formed a relationship with the Revivors, and many of them had reunited after a long time.

Seeing this peaceful scene, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

'The initial negotiations have been completed, and I've finally mobilized the enthusiasm of these Revivors to participate in the battle… I wonder how many Beyond Grade As outside of the Revivors believe my words.'

Han Xiao could not help but smile.

The war had already broken out, and the Sanctum Revival's unlimited usage was bound to be revealed sooner or later. He did not intend to hide it forever, using this reason to convince these revivors that it was a plan that he had devised long ago, and he was not afraid of the three Universal Civilizations finding out.

However, the lies from before were too deeply rooted in the hearts of the people. Han Xiao believed that the three Universal Civilizations and the association members would most likely be skeptical of his words. As long as he did not prove it with his actions, these people would be more likely to believe that the Sanctum Revival was only limited to once.

However, although Han Xiao planned to reveal the fact that there was no limit to the Sanctum Revival, he did not intend to tell the truth completely. He had long prepared what he would say to the three Universal Civilizations after the truth was exposed.

Beep beep beep…

Just as he was thinking, his communicator suddenly rang. Han Xiao took it out to take a look. As expected, it was an invitation from the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations.

Without hesitation, he entered the quantum network and initiated a remote projection.

Turning around, he found himself in the office of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders, facing the three of them.

"It's been hard on you, Black Star. You've already stabilized these revivors." Marbruce nodded. "Thank you for thinking about the big picture. You brought back so many high-level combatants. This will make up for many disadvantages."

"Don't just thank me verbally." Han Xiao chuckled.

"Don't worry, we have already prepared substantial remuneration." Marbruce paused and suddenly asked, "By the way, we also provided Gaud's medium, but why didn't he revive?"

"I'm not sure. Either the medium is wrong, or this guy isn't dead and is hiding somewhere."

Han Xiao's expression did not change. This kind of problem was easily solved, and it did not affect him at all.

"So he's not dead… I got it."

Marbruce glanced at Han Xiao and did not intend to continue investigating.

At this time, the Pope interrupted and slowly asked:

"Black Star, you just said that Sanctum Revival does not have a limit. Is it real or fake?"

"What do you think?" Han Xiao asked.

"…I think this is just an excuse you used to stabilize the revivors." The Pope spread out his hands. "But there are no absolutes in this world. Maybe this is the truth."

The other two also stared at Han Xiao with curiosity.

Han Xiao shrugged and said casually:

"It doesn't matter which way you believe it. When the situation gets to that point, we'll know if it's true or not. Before that, I suggest that you take what I just said as a lie and consider the worst possible outcome. There will be no mistakes if you do that."

Without waiting for a response, Han Xiao continued.

"Your top priority now is to detain these revivors and ensure that they can't come into contact with the truth. Otherwise, I won't be able to do anything if they retreat."

"…You're right."

The three of them looked at each other, suppressed their doubts, and nodded at the same time.

They were more inclined to believe that the so-called 'Unlimited Sanctum Revival' was a lie that Han Xiao used to fool the Revivors.

With Black Star's personality, how could he reveal such a trump card so easily? It was most likely a lie!

Anyway, it was common for Black Star to lie through his teeth, and they were already used to it. They did not panic at all and even wanted to laugh.

Chapter 1352: Ancestor-Descendent and Detected

Pa.

Han Xiao deactivated the remote projection, and his vision returned to his body. He shook his head and smiled.

After conversing with the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations, it seemed like they did not believe his words and were more inclined to believe that the Sanctum Revival was only limited to one time.

However, now that things had come to this, Han Xiao did not care if the three Universal Civilizations believed him or not. The reason he had once said that the Sanctum Revival would only be limited to one time was first — to make it easier to control the Revivors of the Holy Accord, reduce their ambitions and reduce the possibility of the Holy Accord being exposed. Secondly, it was to deal with the three Universal Civilizations that were targeting the Beyond Grade As back then and hide their trump cards, making the three Universal Civilizations feel as if they could still control their lives. Thirdly, it was to stall for time and wait for Oathkeeper to gather a new set of Sanctum keys.

Right now, both sides were in the same boat. The World Tree Civilization was the main problem, and the three Universal Civilizations could not do much without his help. Under the current situation, no matter how much the three Universal Civilizations feared the Beyond Grade As, they had to rely on their strength. Han Xiao did not mind showing his cards; unfortunately, they did not believe him for the time being.

"A monopoly-type business, so easy to speak out."

Han Xiao chuckled, put away the communicator, and returned to the cabin. He was prepared to showcase his traditional skills to cozy up to these new Revivors.

Swoosh!

The alloy hatch slid open automatically. Han Xiao walked into the hall and looked around.

The various Beyond Grade As in the room had formed a few small groups. The direct members of their respective organizations sat together, and the neutral Beyond Grade As sat together according to their generations. Occasionally, some lone wanderers would sit alone in the corner, and the people who wanted to find out information and liked to make friends would wander among the groups. Everyone was on the same level, so they had quite a lot of common topics. The atmosphere was quite lively.

As soon as Han Xiao entered, he realized that the revivors of the various groups were looking at him with curiosity and surprise.

This time, Nilfgadi walked over and sized Han Xiao up. "So, you're the strongest Mechanic of this generation. When I recover, let's have a talk."

Han Xiao raised his brows and smiled. "Alright, you're welcome anytime."

He roughly knew why these revivors were looking at him like that. Most likely, when he was talking to the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations remotely, these revivors had heard about his life from the other Beyond Grade As and were surprised by his achievements.

The way he saw it, the reason why Nilfgadi suggested sparring was not just to exchange feelings. It was most likely because he wanted to regain the position as the main deity for the Machinery Faith.

Han Xiao knew what Nilfgadi was thinking. If they were to continue to remain dead, there would be nothing wrong with leaving the inheritance to future generations. However, now that the corpse had come back to life, they planned to snatch the 'inheritance' back. They did not want others to continue occupying the foundation they had built. After all, it belonged to them.

Looking around, Han Xiao estimated that there was more than one person who had such a mentality. He had long expected such a conflict of interest to arise between them and the current Beyond Grade As.

"Hehe, I've become Manison from back then, I have become the challenged."

Han Xiao smiled at himself.

Aegon Vardnadze did not make him display his full strength, which was why Nilfgadi still had the confidence to spar with him. However, he had no equipment at the moment, so this was not the time.

Nilfgadi nodded and said a few polite words before walking to the side and returning to the Primordial Ones.

This time, one of the neutral Beyond Grade As spoke to Han Xiao.

"By the way, you said that you're the current head of the Beyond Grade A Association. Does your association still recruit people?"

Han Xiao looked over and smiled at the speaker.

"Of course, our association always welcomes new members. If you don't wish to fight alone, joining the association is the best choice. This is the profit union of the current Beyond Grade As, and we have always been willing to help new members build their own organizations. However, this is a time of war, so we won't go into this for now…"

As he spoke, Han Xiao turned to look at Hilbert and the others.

"Also, we welcome those who are not willing to work for the three Universal Civilizations. If you feel uncomfortable staying with the three Universal Civilizations, the association will be your choice."

"Hey!" Oulou yelled with dissatisfaction.

How dare you try to steal our people!

This feeling was like an honest man seeing a well-built playboy asking his girlfriend for WeChat.

"Don't joke around like that." Clotti's face was expressionless, and his aura was cold. As the National Pillar, he could not be indifferent to Han Xiao's poaching.

On the side, Reeve stared at Clotti and exclaimed in surprise, "Little Kaka, you've grown quite a bit over the years."

Clotti's serious and tense expression immediately collapsed. He was not used to putting on airs in front of these seniors.

Kasuyi, who was not far away, almost thought that he was being called. He suddenly recalled some bad memories and glared at Han Xiao's back with resentment.

Hilbert did not respond directly. He shook his head and said, "Thank you for your invitation, but we'll talk about this some other time."

He did not want to continue working hard, but that did not mean that he would not want the retirement benefits of the three Universal Civilizations. After all, he had exchanged his life for merits.

Han Xiao smiled and did not mind. He walked around the various groups and briefly communicated with them.

After chatting for a while, the spaceship finally reached the location of the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. It entered the circular area and activated the device. With a flash of light, it was quickly transported to the main base.

The three Universal Civilizations had already made preparations. They welcomed the many Revivors to their temporary residence. To prevent any accidents, most Beyond Grade As accompanied them.

Han Xiao did not follow them but went to the Underworld with Hila.

Everyone chatted on the way to their temporary residence.

At the back of the team, Manison and Nilfgadi walked side by side, maintaining their silence.

After a while, Nilfgadi finally spoke.

"You're the leader of this generation of the Mechanical Race?"

"Hmm," Manison replied.

"Not bad. I didn't expect such a powerful person like you to appear among my descendants." Nilfgadi nodded with satisfaction.

Manison ignored him and did not reply.

Not only was Nilfgadi the first Divine Throne Mechanic and the founder of the Machinery Faith, but he was also the ancestor of the Mechanical Race.

Due to certain reasons, Manison was not interested in acknowledging the ancestor. His interactions with Nilfgadi were limited. Nilfgadi had already died even before he became a Beyond Grade A. Furthermore, after he became a Beyond Grade A, his race evolved and became a new species. From the perspective of genes, the two could no longer be considered the same species.

After sighing for a while, Nilfgadi patted Manison's Lord's Avatar's shoulder and asked, "How is the Mechanical Race now?"

"You'll know when you get back. Anyway, it isn't bad." Manison was too lazy to report to him.

"That's good." Nilfgadi nodded and said, "I'll have to trouble you to announce my return to the entire Mechanical Race. Tell them that their ancestor has returned."

With that said, Nilfgadi sped up and left Manison's side.

Manison looked at his back, raised his hand, and brushed away the shoulder that was patted by Nilfgadi as if he was removing dust.

'If this was in the past, I would think of ways to kill you for sure…'

Manison snorted coldly in his heart.

Although Nilfgadi did not have any intention of taking back the position of Mechanical Race leader, with one more ancestor, their power would surely be divided.

The Mechanical Race was his important base, and he did not want to see anyone interfere with his interests, not even his ancestor.

You want to take the cake with your seniority?

Dream on!

You want to step on my head? Do you think you're Black Star?

However, Manison was much more restrained now. Although he was not willing to give up his benefits, he did not plan to do anything to Nilfgadi. At most, he would just send him to create a new Mechanical Race.

In any case, after so many years of reproduction, the old Mechanical Race was already in his grasp. Just the name of his ancestor alone would not be able to shake his foundation as the leader.

On the other side, Milizaus was also with the ancestor of the Starry Spiritual Dragon Race, but the atmosphere was completely different.

"Old man, is what you said true? Do you really have a way to reduce my size while maintaining full combat power ‽" Milizaus was shocked.

"Heh, this is my unique secret skill. You can only use it if you have my bloodline. However, after you became a Beyond Grade A, you diluted my bloodline and turned it into a new species. This won't do! Later, I'll put in a few hundred tons of dragon blood. You can use magic to smelt it and fuse it into your body to increase the density of your bloodline. Let me examine you properly the next time you come. I'll help you adjust this secret skill and tailor it for you."

A small blue dragon that was about ten meters long was lying on Milizaus' enormous body. Its body was beautiful, and its crystal-like blue dragon scales sparkled brightly. The golden dragon's horns were like jade, and they looked like a crown. There were thick gray whiskers on both sides of its head.

'Dragon Mage' Marsebo Demeliter was originally a blue dragon with a mutated bloodline. After advancing to Beyond Grade A, he had sublimated his genes and had astonishing magical talent. He had created countless Dragon Spells, and the Starry Spiritual Dragon was just one of the branches of his bloodline.

Currently, many of the Dragon Spells that Milizaus used were the legacy of Marsebo. Putting his actual combat ability aside, Milizaus was still inferior to him in terms of magic research and development.

The way Mages and Mechanics ate resources was different. Milizaus did not care who ruled the race. As soon as he saw his erudite ancestor, he came over to exchange experiences. It just so happened that the two dragons had straightforward personalities, so they chatted quite happily. Marsebo did not hide anything and expressed that he could solve Milizaus' biggest problem.

In fact, there were quite a number of spells that could shrink one's size, but the body structure of different races was different, and the spell models required were also different. This was the magic theory that emphasized the usability of spells. As for Milizaus—who had a special Beyond Grade A powerful dragon body—although there were some rare spells that could shrink his body, they would reduce his combat power by a certain percentage—like the Bone Shrinking Technique. Therefore, he would only be at his peak state when he released his entire body.

However, the secret skill that Marsebo mentioned did not have such negative effects. Instead, it could increase the density of one's body, strengthen one's defense and resistance, and increase one's combat power instead of decreasing it. It was a Dragon Spell that could only be used under certain conditions.

Milizaus was pleasantly surprised, and he continued to question Marsebo. Marsebo was very generous, saying as long as you want to learn, I will teach you. After all, I am your ancestor.

Once he learned this secret skill, he would no longer have to be a target for others. His combat strength would increase tremendously. Thinking of this future, Milizaus felt his heart burn with passion.

He could finally escape the fate of being a meat shield!

Such a promising profession should be left to Black Star!

It was worth it to get to know this ancestor!

...

Underworld Dimension.

Han Xiao and Hila teleported over to check on Aegon Vardnadze.

Aegon Vardnadze had already turned into a Hero Spirit, and he was surrounded by the eight brothers.

Seeing Han Xiao arrive, Aegon Vardnadze's eyes bulged, and he said angrily, "You actually killed me, you…"

"Shut up. Without me, you would still be a dead man. You don't even have the right to be killed. You went too far. This is your punishment."

Han Xiao interrupted him expressionlessly.

Hila turned to look at the eight brothers and asked, "Have you helped him figure out his situation?"

"I've already told him about the situation in the Underworld, but it seems like he has yet to accept reality."

Sorokin shrugged.

Hearing this, Aegon Vardnadze turned around and glared at Hila.

"Don't even think about making me your slave. I will never serve you!"

"Oh." Hila remained indifferent.

Han Xiao crossed his arms and said casually, "It's better to live than to die. You have to think carefully. Although you are being controlled by others, in a sense, this is an immortal body."

"Death is better than losing freedom!"

Aegon Vardnadze held his head high.

Han Xiao clapped his hands and turned to look at Hila. "Lock him up alone. Let him out when he changes his mind."

"Alright, I can adjust Hero Spirit's sense of time and make it feel like years."

Without hesitation, Hila used her Underworld authority and locked Aegon Vardnadze up without waiting for him to speak.

Seeing this, the eight Underworld Brothers clicked their tongues in sympathy.

Hero Spirits' senses were all controlled by the controller of the Underworld, and they could simulate all kinds of experiences. They would surely suffer if they offended the authorities.

"From now on, there will be nine Hero Spirit Kings in the Underworld. They are at least peak Beyond Grade As, and their strength is only slightly weaker than Sorokin's. We have gained another powerhouse."

Han Xiao nodded. He did not doubt that Aegon Vardnadze would submit to his fate because he had no other choice.

If this guy was really that tough, he would not have begged for mercy when he was beaten up.

If Aegon Vardnadze was obedient, he would at most be placed under house arrest for a while. However, Han Xiao did not have any psychological burden in locking him up in the Underworld. He would have to pay the corresponding price for causing the disturbance.

You chose it yourself, hero!

On the other side, Sorokin was in a good mood.

Finally, there was another newcomer. This way, he would not be the youngest…

Happy!

...

At the same time, in the World Tree territory.

Roots extended out from the space, continuously sending out new fleets.

Heart Tree King sat on his throne and looked at the scene before him.

"How's the situation now?"

"Other than some high-level combatants who are still in the process of reviving, the battleships and soldiers that were lost in the previous battle were all replenished by the mother tree. Some troops have been reassembled, and there are already 230 billion battleships being sent to the secondary dimension world, searching for the territory of the other civilization there…"

The executive officer at the side reported the current situation.

"Hmm." The Heart Tree King nodded calmly.

The main universe's offensive route was blocked, and the World Tree began to make multiple preparations, planning to start from the secondary dimension and invade through another route.

However, the World Tree did not give up on attacking the intercepting circle. It had been gathering more troops, and at the same time, letting the advance troops exhaust the three Universal Civilizations' forces and push the jump point forward.

"The other party is currently in a stalemate with our beyond-visual-range encampment. Their expansion has been obstructed and is almost at a standstill. The effect of this plan is very obvious. I estimate that before we launch our next attack, the jump point would be able to remain in this area and will not be pushed further," another World Tree executive said.

"Not bad."

Heart Tree King praised and suddenly paused.

"Have you found the source of the information leak? How did they know about our strategic deployment?"

"Hmm, we have an idea. It seems to be related to foreseers."

An executive took out a report and explained:

"According to the data, 93.4% of the exposed tactical deployments have one thing in common. All of them were foreseen by the Information Form Foreseers. We have reason to suspect that the strategic deployment was leaked to the other party because of this. As for what methods the other party used, we don't know for the time being. Currently, all foresight has been stopped, and we are currently investigating the details of the abilities of all the Information Form Foreseers, the awakening situation, and the origin to find the source of the leak…"

The three Universal Civilizations had discovered many tactical deployments, so the World Tree naturally noticed the anomaly.

Although they did not know the abilities of Destiny's Child, through data analysis, the World Tree Civilization still found the reason for the leakage of information. Even if they could not cure the root cause, they could at least deal with the symptoms.

Heart Tree King patted the armrest and said slowly:

"It's good that you've found the reason. However, don't seal off the other party's intelligence channels. When needed, this channel will come in handy. It might catch them off guard."

Chapter 1353: Migration and Invitation to Fight

Under the deliberate publicity of the three Universal Civilizations, the news of Black Star using the Sanctum Revival to wake up many more Beyond Grade As spread like wildfire within a few days and spread to the troops stationed in the intercepting circle, boosting their morale.

Beyond Grade As were not only high-level combatants, but they were also the spiritual pillars of many soldiers during times of war. The more strong individuals in the army, the more confident the soldiers would be.

The relevant information was also specially sent back to the galactic society, which also excited a large number of people and various powers.

In the past, many galactic residents hated the Sanctum Revival deeply, thinking it was because of the confidence in Beyond Grade As and that they were on opposing sides. However, now that the Beyond Grade As had gone on to fight against the foreign enemies and become the strength to protect the galactic society, the attitude of these galactic residents also changed. They were full of praise about the Sanctum Revival and wished for more Beyond Grade As to revive and guarantee their safety.

Even during the war, the Wayne Card distributors did not miss the opportunity to do business. They had launched a new 'Revivor' card series. It had synergistic effects when it appeared together with some Character Summon Cards and Force Cards that it had special relationships with, and had different reactions. They were like hidden Easter eggs.

The reactions of the various organizations were not one-sided excitement like the people's. They secretly assessed the impact of this matter on themselves, especially those organizations that had ties with these historical Beyond Grade As.

In a certain branch of the Machinery Faith.

In the spacious hall of the temple, bishops dressed in the Mechanical Holy Official robes of different styles gathered together and discussed in low voices with excitement.

"The original deity has returned. We should worship his honorific name again!"

"Who would have thought that one day, I would be able to see the living Nilfgadi."

The bishops were excited.

As the Mechanical Deity who was worshiped first, Nilfgadi had a special position in the Machinery Faith.

Because only the living Mechanical Deity could receive feedback from the believers, the dead Mechanical Deities only had commemorative significance, becoming the 'old deities' that were rarely mentioned.

However, Nilfgadi was an exception. Every time there was a prayer ceremony, the Machinery Faith believers would chant his honorific name. This was a treatment that other Mechanical Deities did not receive.

Now that Nilfgadi was alive again, they could resume making offerings to him.

However, the Machinery Faith was an extremely realistic group of believers, and they only believed in the strong. Although Nilfgadi's position was special, it would not immediately shake Black Star's current position unless he could prove that his mechanical skill was stronger.

Furthermore, the Sanctum Revival was brought about by Black Star. The various archbishops present thought about this and reached a consensus.

"Although the original deity has a different meaning to us, he was brought back by Black Star. His current position should not be above Black Star's."

"That's right. It was Black Star who awakened all the old deities and revived the glory of the Church. Because of this, we should give Black Star a new honorific name and separate him from the other Mechanical Deities, allowing him to enjoy a unique position."

"Since Nilfgadi is the original deity, why not call Black Star the revival deity?"

"This doesn't feel okay. In my opinion, whether the old deities awaken or not is completely controlled by Black Star. Why don't we call him the Old Ones' Dominator?"

"Why does it feel a little weird… Let's change it. I think the title 'Immortal Black, Holy Lord of the Church, Guardian of the Door of the Old Deities, and Adjudicator of Life and Death' isn't bad."

"That's too long. Those who don't know would think there are four people."

"What's wrong with it? Tell me if it's nice or not!"

The group of bishops had a heated argument over Black Star's new honorific name, but they could not convince each other. In the end, they had even started fighting.

...

Central Galaxy, on a modified planet.

A transport fleet with the Black Star Army insignia slowly entered the port, and under the guidance of the artificial intelligence robot at the port, large rectangular transport ships stopped at different docks.

The hatch opened one after another, and groups of Black Star Army soldiers walked out. They stood in formation, took out their indicator lights, and commanded. Large batches of Planet Aquamarine citizens swarmed out, forming a long line. They stepped on the dock and headed toward the designated settlement.

The army warriors maintained order. Although there was a slight commotion in the crowd, it was still in order. However, the constant left and right looks revealed the nervousness and curiosity in most people's hearts.

In the command room of the transport ship, Bennett looked down at the migrating crowd on the dock with a complicated expression.

During the early stages of the war, he had responded to Black Star's call and organized a long-distance migration for all the citizens of Planet Aquamarine. At that time, it naturally attracted a large number of objections. Many people were not willing to migrate, and they met with a lot of resistance when executing the plan.

To most people, their mother planet held an unforgettable emotion. No matter how far they wandered in the universe, their mother planet was their spiritual home. There were too many examples of people willing to live and die with their mother planet in the face of a disaster.

However, these problems were all forcefully suppressed by Bennett. Regardless of whether they were willing or not, they were all packed up and sent to the transport fleet.

Since the various Star Fields were undergoing major migration, the current transportation efficiency was limited. The transport fleet had also been traveling for a long time. Bennett emphasized the need to do this along the way, and with his emotional reasoning, he finally suppressed most of the dissatisfaction. The people of Planet Aquamarine could only helplessly accept reality and worry about the future.

Although this was only a temporary refuge, they did not know if this was the last time they would see their mother planet.

If the World Tree successfully invaded, the Flickering World would be the first to bear the brunt, and the Shattered Star Ring was adjacent to the Flickering World. It was very likely to become the second main battlefield, and one day the news of the destruction of their mother planet would be known countless light-years away.

"I wonder if I'll have the chance to go back in the future…"

Bennett sighed with mixed feelings.

At this moment, a faint female voice sounded from the side.

"This is your new home."

"Thank you, Your Excellency Ames," Bennett turned around and thanked her.

"Hmm, I'll leave this place to you. I'll leave Floating Dragon behind as your guard."

Ames nodded and walked out of the cabin.

She had not been stationed at the frontline at the moment, and she originally had the thought to go participate. However, Black Star had asked her to escort Planet Aquamarine's migration troops, so she had been delayed.

In reality, Ames knew that Black Star's request was to protect her in disguise, but the escort journey would end sooner or later and it would be time for her to head to the frontlines.

Furthermore, she wanted to see with her own eyes what kind of existence the nightmare was that had forced Black Star to keep going for so many years.

...

Interception circle base, Revivors' area.

In the vast space, streams of light were constantly colliding with each other, creating a shocking energy wave. Many of the current Beyond Grade As were fighting with different Revivors.

Han Xiao and his other comrades, who did not make a move, stood at the side and watched the battle. From time to time, they would use various methods to neutralize the shockwaves.

The people who had just revived were not in their peak state. They had been undergoing restorative training during this period and the older Mechanics and Mages still had to learn the new theories and technologies that had been developed over the years. They were very busy.

Because the Beyond Grade As guarding the intercepting circle had nothing to do, sparring became their main task. They had been helping the Revivors recover their strength and frequently sparred.

Although most of the knowledge banks of the Revivors were behind the times, some of the lost skills were brought back by the Revivors. They were not stingy with their teachings, which indirectly increased the average strength of the current Beyond Grade As.

Among them, Milizaus was the one with the greatest increase in strength. He had finally managed to compress his body as he wished. He had just learned the Dragon Secret Skill taught by his ancestor, and he was already able to compress his mothership-sized body to about three hundred meters long. This alone was enough to make him overjoyed. His combat strength had increased significantly.

According to him, as long as he could master this secret skill, he should be able to shrink his dragon body to a dozen meters long at most, and its density would increase exponentially, just like the difference between stone and steel.

"In the past, Milizaus had high HP, average defense, and basically zero evasion. When he completes this transformation, not only would his defense increase tremendously, but his evasion rate would also return to normal. His flexibility would also increase by half a level."

Han Xiao estimated.

After watching the spar for a while, he opened the interface and scanned the forums.

Thanks to the World Tree's beyond-visual-range encampment strategy, the players had been carrying out missions with extremely rich rewards. More than half of the IDs on the level leaderboards had changed. The players who had been lucky enough to obtain missions to die had all gone up.

The current first place was six levels higher than the first place two months ago, reaching level 173. It was only seven levels away from the current version limit of level 180. This leveling rate was quite fast for the players.

However, only a small number of people managed to snatch the suicide mission, and this good opportunity would disappear very soon. Han Xiao had already provided the blueprints for the special detection equipment, and the three Universal Civilizations had sent a batch of semi-finished products over, waiting for him to complete the most important core steps.

As long as they had the finished product for the detection device, the three Universal Civilizations would be able to utilize it on the battlefield very quickly. They would be able to get rid of the World Tree's beyond-visual-range encampment in one go. This way, the players would only be able to participate in a large-scale spacetime splicing self-destruction operation once more, and they would no longer be able to enjoy such a high-quality catalyst that stimulates their growth so fast.

"I wonder what new plans the World Tree Civilization will come up with after this strategy is broken… Speaking of which, it seems like Destiny's Child has not gained much recently?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin thoughtfully.

According to Hila's report, the frequency of Destiny's Child taking effect had decreased significantly compared to the beginning. Furthermore, the information obtained from the surveillance was mostly unimportant and did not provide much help with the current situation.

This sign was a signal in Han Xiao's eyes. Either the World Tree Civilization felt that the effect of the foresight method was ordinary and stopped using it on a large scale, or the World Tree Civilization realized the reason for the leak and took precautions.

"Hmm… The World Tree still sensed it? It's faster than I expected."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Although the surveillance channels of Destiny's Child were hidden, through the analysis of the battle, he could sense that some of the actions made by the three Universal Civilizations were as if they had received information beforehand, so he naturally suspected the possibility of the information being leaked.

Although it was difficult to find the mechanism of Destiny's Child, through the relevant data screening, the World Tree had a high chance of discovering that the foreseers were the source of the leak. The three Universal Civilizations could do this too, but their reaction speed would be slower.

Han Xiao had never been certain that Destiny's Child could keep on concealing the leak from the World Tree. After all, this was not something that could not be solved. He would not believe that this low-risk intelligence channel would always be reliable, but the longer he hid it, the better.

"If the World Tree realized this, they might use this intelligence channel to send misleading information to us… It seems that any information obtained from Destiny's Child will have to be filtered."

Han Xiao pondered.

Just as he was pondering, the sparring session also came to an end. They all stopped when they reached a certain point and focused on communication.

After watching the entire process, Kasuyi sighed.

"As expected of the elites of the past generations."

"They're all people with great luck. The concentration of luck outside is almost beyond the standard. It's more balanced here." Secret Master nodded.

"Seeing them alive and kicking, I'm deeply gratified. These people are the epitome of the evolutionary history of our civilization, the essence accumulated over generations." Not far away, Oulou acted as if he was giving pointers.

"…But we're still better." Manison glanced at him.

Civilizations continued to develop, the experience was passed down, and techniques were innovated from generation to generation. Of course, they would not be inferior to the past. Currently, among the Beyond Grade As, the combat power of the current generation was superior—especially with Black Star, who had broken the record.

"You guys are so noisy."

Han Xiao looked at them helplessly. They were just watching the battle. He did not know why they were acting out so much.

He retracted his gaze and turned to look at the many revivors who were returning to the battleship in groups. Suddenly, he had an idea.

After hesitating for two seconds, Han Xiao opened the communication channel and smiled.

"Seeing you guys having a good time, my hands are a little itchy too. Who's interested in playing with me? I promise to be gentle."

Chapter 1354: The Trouble of the Strong Is the Increase in Difficulty of Harvesting Benefits

As soon as he said that, the Beyond Grade As in the cabin could not help but look at him with surprise. The Revivors who were boarding the ship were also stunned.

"What are you trying to do?" Kasuyi was surprised.

"It's just a spar. Why are you putting on such an expression? Stop making a fuss."

Looking at their expressions, Han Xiao felt helpless.

The current Beyond Grade As knew his abilities very well. Even if he wanted to spar with someone, not many would be willing to respond. All of them were very smart and protected their benefits very well.

Furthermore, he had a special position now, and his every move was being watched. It would make people think too much, and it was not convenient for him to fight with his own people.

However, the newly awakened Revivors did not have a deep enough impression of him. They might agree to it, and there might be a chance to trigger the Beyond Grade A Challenge. It was worth trying.

Many revivors' expressions changed, and they immediately thought of something else.

Black Star, as the president of a Beyond Grade A Association, actually took the initiative to challenge them. Could it be that he was afraid that they would not be willing to be placed under house arrest and had some thoughts, so he wanted to teach them a lesson and make them behave?

As they thought about it, the lively communication channel became silent instantly.

Seeing that no one was speaking, Han Xiao coughed and asked, "Why are you all so reserved? Does no one want to play with me?"

Reserved your head! you definitely have an ulterior motive…

Many Beyond Grade As rolled their eyes inwardly.

When Aegon Vardnadze was killed, they witnessed the tip of Black Star's strength. Although they had just revived, they still cared about their face. Why would they want to get beaten up for no reason?

If they could defeat Black Star, they would be able to increase their prestige. However, they had yet to recover to their peak state, and they knew that not many people had the confidence to defeat the most outstanding Beyond Grade A representative in this era.

Although Nilfgadi had agreed to spar in the future, he did not even have a single group of mechanical troops right now, so he had no intention of standing out.

Even after waiting more than ten seconds, no one had responded.

Seeing that no one was speaking, Aurora broke the silence of the channel and said softly, "Erm… don't worry about getting hurt. I will treat you."

Hila snorted and took a few steps forward. "If your hands are itchy, I can spar with you. Why are you looking for someone else?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao looked back at the two sisters.

Finally, there's someone who upholds my prestige. The two of you still love me…

Kasuyi laughed and also tried to smooth things over. "Alright, alright, Black Star doesn't have any bad intentions, there's no need to be so wary. If you are not willing, then forget it."

"Tsk, you make it sound like I'm taking advantage of their weakness. Forget it, let's talk when you guys are at your peak."

Seeing that no one was paying attention to his invitation, Han Xiao had no choice but to find a way out, thinking it was getting more and more difficult to gain benefits.

Just as he was about to change the topic and dismiss everyone, a deep voice sounded in the channel.

"There's no need to wait for the future. I'll be your opponent!"

Han Xiao's eyes lit up, and he quickly turned around. He saw a burly creature with a fist clenched.

Pugilist!

He's here, he's here, he's here with a headstrong attitude!

The revivors all turned around and stared at the guy in shock.

"Kher, do you really think you're his match?" someone could not help but ask.

"Humph, I still have this bit of self-awareness. However, facing difficulties head-on is my martial path! Not daring to fight even when there is no danger to my life will only damage my belief in martial arts. Since I met an expert, I can use it to train myself!"

Kher's face was cold, and his battle intent soared.

Han Xiao was touched.

As expected of a Pugilist, they never let him down!

Seeing this, many of the revivors were speechless. He knew that Black Star probably wanted to establish his dominance, but he still rushed forward. Only a Pugilist would do something like that.

Everyone silently distanced themselves from Kher, afraid that they would be infected with simpleton disease.

"Since you've agreed, let's spar."

Han Xiao could not wait to fly out of the cabin, afraid that this kid would go back on his word.

Kher was just an ordinary neutral Beyond Grade A. Even though he was not an expert, he was still a Beyond Grade A. No matter how small the benefits to gain from him, Han Xiao would still take it; in any case, he was not picky. And just because he was an ordinary Beyond Grade A did not mean that he did not have good abilities. After all, he, himself, had many Molding Talents that were drawn from ordinary Supers.

"Wait a minute, what are the stakes in our sparring?" Kher asked again.

"What do you want?"

"If I can beat you, you will remove my house arrest and give me freedom," said Kher in a low, muffled voice.

This time, even Han Xiao, who knew the habits of a Pugilist, was surprised, and everyone was stunned.

No way, no way, do you really think you have the upper hand against a peak Beyond Grade A ‽

If you want to fight head-on, we can still accept you using a strong enemy to train yourself, but do you really think you have a chance to win? You're overestimating yourself!

As if noticing the confusion of Han Xiao and his companions, Kher said with a deep voice:

"Although the chance isn't high, setting up a goal can stimulate my potential and allow me to unleash greater strength! The difference between our strength is too great, so I need to use all external factors to strengthen my combat strength!"

"You're really… pure."

Han Xiao did not know what to say.

Everyone returned to the spaceship to watch the battle.

On the battlefield, Kher's body was filled with flames, and he was ready to fight. He faced Han Xiao from afar, and his aura locked onto Han Xiao.

The aura of a Pugilist was not bad, but the difference in strength was too huge. Han Xiao had already tried his best to feel it, but he really could not feel any sense of danger. In his eyes, it was like a little kitten brandishing its claws at him. It was not fierce at all, but rather cute.

Han Xiao looked at the interface, and the related Beyond Grade A Challenge mission successfully popped up. With so many Beyond Grade As watching, their influence had naturally reached the standard to trigger the mission.

The mission form was still to last for a sufficient amount of time. The reward for the highest level of drawing abilities required him to last for a total of twenty minutes. Of course, this requirement was not difficult for him at all. On the contrary, he doubted if Kher could last that long in his hands…

"Therefore, the difficulty this time lies in how I'm going to go easy for twenty minutes… Kakasu is good at this, so I have to use that as a reference."

Han Xiao's face twitched.

Is it me or Kher who is doing the challenge mission?

"I'm coming!"

Kher's aura reached its peak, and he suddenly let out a low roar. The flames on his body expanded, and he pushed his palms continuously. The continuous Shockwave Blasts moved like a yellow chain.

Han Xiao's body did not move, and Floating Cannons appeared behind his back like a halo of light. it shot out dense beams of light, destroying all the incoming Shockwave Blasts.

Seeing this, Kher's body shook, and he suddenly split into dozens of flaming clones and they charged at Han Xiao from all directions. He did not rush forward but instead held his palms together to accumulate power.

Han Xiao clenched his fists and punched both sides. The powerful force field activated by the mechanical suit swept past, instantly destroying all the clones that were approaching.

At this time, Kher had already completed his rapid accumulation. A dazzling Pugilist aura lit up between his hands, and he suddenly pushed forward.

A bright yellow Pugilist light wave surrounded by a sharp aura shot toward Han Xiao like a rapidly extending lightsaber. Accompanying the surging energy was a loud shout from Kher in the communication channel.

"Ha! Galaxy Splitting Fist—Third Style!"

Hearing the shameless name, Han Xiao felt that even the Pugilist light waves had become stronger.

This was the real deal! Shouting the name of the move during the attack indeed had a bonus effect!

The corners of Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He suppressed the burning desire to ridicule and raised his hand to summon a psionic shield.

The next moment, a bright yellow Pugilist light wave crashed into the rippling blue psionic shield and a dazzling light wheel exploded.

The shockwave dissipated. Han Xiao was unshaken and the psionic shield flickered a few times before stabilizing again.

Kher's expression changed. He said solemnly:

"You actually used such a tight defense. As expected, this move can't break your defense. This won't be simple!"

Han Xiao: "…"

I only took out a basic shield. Since when did it become a tight defense? Don't take the liberty to give me more screen time!

Seeing that Kher was going to continue spewing bullshit, Han Xiao's face twitched. He simply opened the secondary dimensional army box. He did not have the heart to summon a large group to bully others, so he only pulled out an Apostle Weapon that was covered in other weapons.

"Heaven-Suppressing Banner, go deal with him."

The Heaven-Suppressing Banner nodded—picked up the accompanying shield and heavy axe—and headed straight for Kher with the exhaust flames shooting out of its thrusters. The man and the machine immediately tangled together and fought at close range.

Han Xiao did not interfere. He stood by the side and watched the Heaven-Suppressing Banner fight Kher alone while silently counting the time.

With the enhancement of his Mechanical Force bonuses, the Apostle Weapons could already fight against high-level Beyond Grade As, and fighting against ordinary Beyond Grade As was no problem at all.

The two sides fought intensely, and Han Xiao finally reached the end of the twenty minutes. Seeing that the mission reward on the highest level was in a completed state, he immediately acted and knocked Kher down easily. With such a huge difference in strength, there was no suspense in this battle.

"Alright, you have satisfied your desire. You should practice more… Who else wants to spar with me?"

Han Xiao did not go all out, using his control method to immobilize Kher. He turned to look at the spaceships watching the battle.

The channel was silent. The revivors curled their lips but did not respond.

They had thought that Black Star would defeat Kher with lightning speed, but they had fought for twenty minutes. However, they knew that Black Star was deliberately giving Kher a chance to show off. To him, this was not even a warm-up.

Many of the revivors thought about it and felt that they understood. Black Star probably felt that the gap between him and Kher was too big, and defeating him in one go would not have any effect. Furthermore, it would seem like he was using too much strength to bully the weak. Thus, he decided to use a different method to show others that even one Apostle Weapon of his could fight an ordinary Beyond Grade A head-on, indirectly showing his strength.

A portion of them felt that they had seen the truth. Although they felt that they had seen through Black Star's schemes, they had to admit that Black Star's performance had indeed deepened their impression of him being unfathomable. If a single Apostle Weapon could fight against an ordinary Beyond Grade A, then wouldn't Black Star—who had dozens of Apostle Weapons—be equal to tens of Beyond Grade As? How terrifying!

"…Since no one is interested in fighting, let's go back."

Han Xiao waited for a while. Seeing that no one spoke, he knew that he would not be able to get another fool. He released his control over Kher and returned to the spaceship.

Kher rubbed his sore shoulders, but he was not discouraged. Instead, he felt that after this round of torture, his endurance had increased, and his belief in martial arts had become firmer. His brain circuit was indeed different from ordinary people.

With this incident, everyone returned to the main base without saying a word. They then dispersed and returned to their respective areas.

Han Xiao changed into King and teleported back to the army base in the Flickering World. He looked for Feidin and Nero to get some luck before returning to his room to conclude the mission.

Feidin, Nero, Karlot, and other potential officers who had yet to reach Beyond Grade A were not dispatched to the frontlines for the time being and were still in training. Naturally, he had some selfish motives. If he allowed the Beyond Grade A seeds to suffer a large number of casualties on the frontlines, it would not be worth it. The current situation had not reached the point where they needed to fill the gaps with people's lives.

"I hope I can get something suitable this time. Although Kher is a little rash, he still has some good abilities…"

Han Xiao had seen Kher's attributes before, and it was like a prize pool to him. He rubbed his hands and chose to conclude the mission.

The next moment, the interface showed that the mission was completed. Han Xiao skipped the basic reward and looked at the notification at the bottom.

[You have received a reward: Draw one of Kher's Ability/Talent]

Note: Kher is a Pugilist. Parts of abilities have been adjusted to your class.

Randomizing… complete!

Please select one of the five options below as the reward.

[Iron Headbutt - First Style] - Ability: Hit the target with the firm head .+25% Attack Power, Defense of the head increased temporarily +250%. There is a chance to cause [Concussion], [Dizziness], and other debuffs to yourself or the enemy. Cooldown: 14s.

[Crow Cluster Cannon] - Ability: For the next 5 seconds,+120% Ranged Attack Speed, -30% Attack Power, and 3-5% chance of obtaining the [Homing] attribute for every Ranged Attack. Cooldown: 35s

[Unyielding Challenger] - Talent: When facing enemies with a higher level than you, all attributes increased by 3% to 15% depending on the level difference.

[Chain Attack Amplification] - Talent: Damage increases with chain attacks, up to 12%.

[Azure Dragon Bind] - Ability: Enemies will be restricted at close range, rooting both parties. The duration of the target's escape depends on the difference in Strength and Endurance. The minimum duration of control is 2s.

Chapter 1355: Pangon's Choice, New Offensive

"Iron Headbutt… And it's only just the first style. Could there be an entire set of moves?"

Looking at the notification on the interface, Han Xiao's mouth twitched, and he could not take his eyes off the first option.

He had always thought that being headstrong was just an adjective to describe a Pugilist's personality, but he did not expect it to be an actual skill.

Han Xiao looked down and saw the other options. After pondering for a while, he came to a decision.

Both talents were not bad, but he did not really want them. As his level increased, the effect of [Undefeated Challenger] kept decreasing. With his current level, he would not have many chances to trigger it. Furthermore, since he keeps leveling up, this talent would only become more and more useless. As for [Chain Strike Amplification]—it was practical and his mechanical army could easily max out the Chain Combo, but the bonuses provided were a little low. His current strength base was very strong, and he did not lack such ordinary passive bonuses.

In comparison, Han Xiao currently wanted some abilities with special tactical effects that would be more effective in battle.

[Crow Cluster Cannon] could increase the explosive power of concentrated fire, and its range was much higher than [Combo Attack Amplification]. However, from Han Xiao's perspective, his damage was already high. What he lacked was a guaranteed hit rate.

Han Xiao was also not too inclined toward the other skill [Azure Dragon Bind]. After all, the restriction of only being able to activate it at close range was quite a setback, and he could not move either side after using it. However, he had his eyes on it precisely because of the rare ability of two-second crowd control.

This was only the effect of Lv.1. If he could reach the maximum level, coupled with some of his talents that could increase the level of his skills, he would be able to extend the minimum duration of this control skill.

You have received new skill [Azure Dragon Bind]!

"Not to mention, it sounds pretty good. It's much better than a name like Iron Headbutt…."

Han Xiao clicked his tongue and opened his attribute interface. He quickly found a new golden skill and continuously leveled up. Although he was trying to reach level 360 and did not want to waste his experience, the consumption of leveling up a skill to the maximum would not affect his overall plan.

Very quickly, [Azure Dragon Bind] went from Lv.1 to Lv.10, and the minimum control time reached 2.6 seconds. At the same time, it provided additional Strength and Endurance, increasing the difficulty of the target breaking free.

After all, Han Xiao had not added any Strength attribute, so it was only average for his level. However, his Endurance was still passable. He was now focusing on Endurance, adding part of his Attribute Points to Endurance every time he successfully forged a Universal Treasure.

"This expert here finally has a locking skill. If I had this skill before, Subduing Tree King would not have been able to break free so easily."

Han Xiao rubbed his chest in glee. Just as he was about to find someone to test his skills, his communicator suddenly rang. It was a call from Ames. She said that she was coming to the frontline and told Han Xiao to activate the King to pick her up.

Seeing Ames's firm attitude, Han Xiao did not force her to stay behind and brought her back to the base.

Furthermore, he could use Ames to test out his new move and see how the actual combat effect would be.

...

Central Galaxy, desolate universe belt.

A small fleet was slowly cruising through the boundless space, seemingly without any destination.

In the command room of the main ship, a group of operators wearing all kinds of armor were piloting a spaceship. From afar, they looked like a group of space pirates.

At the front of the command center stood a few intimidating guys wearing hooded robes.

"Due to the invasion of foreign enemies, the armies of the three Universal Civilizations have entered the various Star Fields at the border. Hinterland is currently empty. Furthermore, a large number of galactic residents are currently hiding in the Central Galaxy. This is a good opportunity…" a hooded man said softly.

Hearing this, the other hooded men stirred slightly. The hooded man standing at the front let out a long breath and slowly spoke.

"Forget it, let's not move now."

"Why? This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity!" The other person's voice was filled with excitement and confusion.

"I said no means no!"

The hooded man at the front raised his head slightly, revealing his face under the hood. It was the mysterious Pangon. These hooded men were the Avengers who left the Holy Accord.

"Pangon, are you feeling compassion?" a Beyond Grade A coldly said. "You're backing off because of the enemy invasion? Are you not willing to affect the so-called 'big picture'? Don't forget that our goal is to take revenge on the three Universal Civilizations. We want to wipe out the entire civilization. The enemy is our help from the heavens, and there would be no better time to destroy their rule and give us a chance to fight them with as few losses as possible. Otherwise, do you really think just the few of us can shake the foundation of the three Universal Civilizations!"

"Are you teaching me how to do things?"

Pangon's expression was equally cold.

This person was not afraid at all. He glared back and said with a deep voice, "Then why do you think we should let go of this opportunity? If our paths are different, it's better to disband early and go our separate ways."

The others also trained their gazes at Pangon.

Their civilization had been destroyed by the three Universal Civilizations in the exploration era, and they had a deep-rooted hatred for each other. They had already put their lives on the line for revenge. The World Tree's invasion made them happy instead of shocked, thinking that the heavens were helping them.

Pangon paused, took out a thick handmade cigarette, lit it, and took a puff. The smoke filled the air with silence.

"Speak!" His teammate demanded coldly.

Pangon glanced at him, tapped the ash off his cigarette, and slowly said, "The Great Relocation Plan should have been the time when the galactic pirates were rampant. But the militaries of the various civilizations are escorting their citizens to the Central Galaxy to take refuge, and the number of galactic residents wandering outside is decreasing… This makes it harder and harder for the galactic pirates to live. Not only is there barely any prey, but the remaining are also being wiped out by the military…"

"What are you trying to say?"

"What I'm saying is, even if we want to seize this opportunity to shake the rule of the three Universal Civilizations, we don't have enough manpower. We might as well take this opportunity to consolidate the galactic pirates and obtain sufficient armed forces. Otherwise, even if we go to the hinterlands of the three Universal Civilizations to cause trouble, we won't be able to."

Pangon paused and analyzed calmly.

"Furthermore, if we obstruct the three Universal Civilizations' plan, Black Star will surely come and kill us. Do you really want to see him?"

Hearing this, fear flashed in everyone's eyes, and they fell silent.

Pangon glanced at them and continued smoking, no longer bothering to speak.

This was both sincere and an excuse. In all fairness, although the invasion of foreign enemies was a good opportunity to shake the three Universal Civilizations, Pangon did not wish to use this opportunity. One reason was because of Black Star's threat, and the other was because of the Holy Accord.

After all, this was the hometown of Oathkeeper and his many Holy Accord companions. The fact that he was able to revive meant that he owed the Holy Accord a huge favor. At the same time, he also obtained his freedom. Now that some old friends were fighting against foreign enemies, he was not willing to drag his friends down.

Although he had decided to devote his life to revenge, he did not want to lose his loyalty.

The invasion of foreign enemies might be the only chance to destroy the three Universal Civilizations, but Pangon did not regret abandoning this route. He firmly believed that there would be another way.

...

The three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree were still engaged in a tug-of-war on the frontlines. After a while, as the first batch of special observation devices was released, the stalemate between the two sides was finally broken.

The beyond visual range detection technology from the Ultimate Civilization of a previous iteration broke through the camouflage of the World Tree strongholds one after another and marked the entire camp on the radar. It was almost like they had poked through the fog of war and finally got back the initiative.

The entire intercepting command center was in high spirits, and they immediately organized a large number of players to form the Spacetime Splicing Army. They split up into tens of thousands of troops and headed toward all the camps in an attempt to wipe out all the enemy strongholds.

The beyond visual range camps that were helping each other were quickly destroyed, and the hidden strongholds were caught off guard. Under the players' fearless Spacetime Splicing Charge, the World Tree's camps were destroyed one after another. The large number of 'nails' that the World Tree planted near the intercepting circle were removed.

After more than half a month of intense battle, the World Tree finally gave up on their Over-the-horizon camp tactic that had lost its effect. It no longer sent out new strongholds, allowing the three Universal Civilizations to clear the obstacles in expanding the intercepting circle and anchoring the orbit.

Without any obstruction, the speed of the space anchor's expansion was quickly thawed and it flowed out quickly, continuing to push the World Tree's jump point away from the intercepting circle.

In the next few months, the frequency of the clashes between the two armies increased, and the battle became more intense.

During this time, the World Tree launched two more assaults, and the fleet was tens of billions in size, triggering two large-scale battles.

The two battles had been fought by the army, and the World Tree did not send out any high-level combatants. It was purely to exhaust the three Universal Civilizations' forces. It seemed like before they find a way to restrain Aurora, the World Tree would not allow their advanced combatants to participate in the battle. Furthermore, the experts who died the last time had not all revived, so they could not enter the battlefield.

Although the World Tree replenishment fleet and combatants would also consume resources, due to the World Tree's characteristics—their resource utilization, resource development, resource regeneration, and resource reserves far exceeded the three Universal Civilizations. They had a huge advantage, and with both sides quickly mobilizing their troops, the World Tree planned to fight the three Universal Civilizations to exhaust their national strength.

Many Beyond Grade As had participated in these two large-scale battles. With Aurora's help and the fact that the World Tree did not send any Beyond Grade As, the two battles had not been so dangerous, and no one had died yet.

Within a few months, Han Xiao had also provided some of the war technology that The First Sanctum had stored. He had manufactured the products in batches and allocated them to multiple troops, which had a significant effect on the army. This reduced the damage of the three Universal Civilizations' fleets by quite a bit, and they were able to defeat the World Tree's assault troops at a lower cost.

The surveillance channels of Destiny's Child also discovered the signs of these two assaults in advance, which made the three Universal Civilizations wary, further reducing their losses.

With the special beyond vision detection devices provided by Han Xiao, the surveillance range and strength of the three Universal Civilizations had undergone a qualitative change. Even without Destiny's Child, they were able to discover most of the World Tree's actions near the intercepting circle. This important technology allowed the three Universal Civilizations to change parts of their strategy, and they no longer felt troubled because of their weakness in detection.

As such, the three Universal Civilizations also looked up at Han Xiao with more importance. They wanted Han Xiao to stay at the base and not participate in any battles, not allowing him to face any danger.

Black Star took out strategic technology one after another as if they were free, and almost every single one of them had the qualifications to be the trump card of an advanced civilization. This shocked the research departments of the three organizations, and they felt that Black Star's research ability alone was more amazing than their entire department.

While the three Universal Civilizations managed to defeat the two waves of attacks with brute force, their intercepting circle and the space anchor orbit were both destroyed during the advance of the World Tree fleet, and the expansion was indirectly stopped.

Ever since the war broke out more than half a year ago, the two sides had been facing each other in this meat grinder. The World Tree had always been blocked outside and could not break through the blockade. It was as if they had finally exhausted their patience after all this time, as Destiny's Child had captured important intelligence through the surveillance channels—showing that the World Tree Civilization was mobilizing troops in the territory and planning a new attack.

This was the World Tree's biggest wave of attacks so far. Its scale was even larger than the previous three combined. It had already exceeded 200 billion, and it was unknown how many more they planned to send!

With such a huge attack, even if the intercepting circle could repel the enemy like the previous three times, it would still be heavily damaged. The moment Han Xiao received the news, he informed the command center and called for an emergency meeting.

Chapter 1356: Fortitude Tree King

In the conference room of the command center, the commanders and Beyond Grade As gathered together.

The three-dimensional star map of the intercepting circle was suspended above the tactical simulation table. Simon stood at the side and kept fiddling with the star map, using his fingers to draw out tactical signs as he explained the current situation.

"… Based on Black Star's intelligence, the World Tree has gathered a 200 billion large army and is suspected to be launching an all-out attack. This is the distribution map of the various troops on our side, as well as the wormhole support base station. It can be seen that the fastest troops on our side are between sectors A-1075c and N-0744j. If the World Tree attacks this section of the defense line, all of our main defense troops can gather there at the fastest speed possible. However, the other defense lines are gathering at a slightly slower speed. This time difference might be the breakthrough point, causing the World Tree to break through the first and second layers of defense with its enormous strength. The strategic depth and wormhole support base will threaten the third and later layers of defense, creating a vicious cycle where we can only be passive…"

The expressions of the high-ranked commanders were grave. The pressure of a 200 billion large fleet was much higher than the previous three assaults. Any small factor could be the other party's breakthrough point.

"I think after the previous three failures, the other party won't repeat the same mistake this time. He will most likely change his attacking method and won't charge straight in."

"Our construction time is still too short. Not only does the World Tree want to break through the blockade, but it also wants to destroy our fortifications in one go. Only by removing the blockade—that we keep pushing forward—can they then stabilize the jump point and build the bridgehead to invade our territory."

"We need more reinforcements from the rear. It's best to increase the distance between the first two layers of defense and the strategic depth of the rear defense line to prevent the enemy from breaking through the blockade."

The commanders of the troops expressed their opinions one after another, and the group discussed them fervently.

As for the Beyond Grade As, they only listened and did not participate.

However, after the upper echelons argued for a while, Simon turned around to ask Han Xiao.

"Black Star, what do you think?"

"You guys can decide on this. I have no objections."

Han Xiao shook his head and expressed that he would let the professionals do the job.

However, he paused for a moment and added, "The World Tree is most likely aware of the source of the information leak. The authenticity of the information I obtained might also be the World Tree's deliberate plan. This risk has to be considered."

Simon took a deep breath and said, "I understand, but even if we can't confirm if the intelligence is real or fake, we have to be prepared to deal with the 200 billion large fleet. Even if there's only a one in a thousand chance that it's real, we have to be on guard, or the consequences will be dire."

"Indeed." Han Xiao nodded. If it was true and he did not take precautions beforehand, he would most likely be killed by the World Tree.

In the previous two attacks, Destiny's Child had also monitored it. Han Xiao had also kept his suspicions, but in the end, it proved that the intelligence was accurate. However, this did not make him feel at ease. Instead, he became more vigilant.

If the World Tree had deliberately leaked information about the previous two attacks in an attempt to reduce their wariness, then it must have been holding back a big move to send fake information at the critical moment. It was just that they had no idea what the World Tree was planning.

"Thankfully, I found a new type of observation device from the First Sanctum and equipped the three Universal Civilizations with it. The World Tree won't be able to act in secret like before. Any movements will be discovered."

Han Xiao thought to himself.

Ever since the three Universal Civilizations had applied the special beyond visible range detection technology that he had provided to the battlefield, their reliance on Destiny's Child's surveillance channels had decreased greatly. Even if the World Tree had some plan, it could not be carried out secretly, and the risk was greatly reduced.

After a long meeting, the commanders left with heavy hearts.

Han Xiao and the others also left the conference room and returned to their residences.

On the way, Kasuyi pushed through the crowd and came to Han Xiao's side.

"The World Tree did not send any high-level combatants in the previous two attacks, but this time, it suddenly launched an all-out attack. Do you think it might have found a way to restrict Aurora?"

Han Xiao glanced at him. Before he could say anything, Sun Hunter jumped from Han Xiao's shoulder to Kasuyi's head and muttered in a low voice,

"Heh, they might be planning to ignore the high-level combatants like us and just attack the defense line with their troops."

"Ignore us? That's possible. As long as they're willing to take the risk of a local battle, no matter how powerful we are, we won't be able to have a significant impact in a war of this scale. At most, we can open up a few opportunities." Kasuyi pondered.

Seeing that the two of them were chatting, Han Xiao also gave up on the idea of responding and turned to look at Ames.

"Hmm? Why are you looking at me?" Ames raised her brows.

"The enemy has brought out 200 billion fleets. Are you afraid?" Han Xiao asked casually.

"There's nothing to be afraid of." Ames shook her head. In the past few months, she had participated in the first two attacks of the World Tree, so she now had some war experience.

"This time is different. The World Tree might bring out a high-level combatant. You have not participated in the first large-scale battle and have not fought with the World Tree experts. They are very difficult to deal with."

"It's a good opportunity for me to experience it," Ames's expression remained calm.

"Don't look down on him. The intensity of the battle between Beyond Grade As cannot be compared to the previous two battles. I suggest you follow Milizaus." Han Xiao pointed at Old Dragon.

"Why do I need to follow him?" Ames was curious.

"He's so big. If you hide behind him, no one will be able to hit you. If necessary, you can even throw him out with force to help you block the attacks."

Han Xiao shrugged.

"…You know I can hear you, right?"

Milizaus' magic incarnation could not help but look over in resignation.

"I just want you to hear it. Her moniker is the Dragon Emperor. Isn't it reasonable for her to sit on you?" Han Xiao curled his lips.

"That sounds familiar. Did you tell me this before?"

Milizaus snorted, not taking it seriously.

Han Xiao shrugged. "Don't you think this strategy has some merit to it?"

"I don't think so at all. Plus, my body size has already shrunk a lot, so I won't be targeted by the enemy at all. This plan will surely be useless." Milizaus was very calm. People who had successfully lost some weight would always be this tough.

"Then recover your body. You have such a huge body, but you don't shield your teammates from the wind and rain. This is a waste of God's gift!"

What nonsense… Milizaus rolled his eyes and ignored Han Xiao.

The people were not scared by the large-scale battle that was about to break out. They returned to their residence chatting and laughing.

Han Xiao closed the door, and his smile disappeared.

He had a feeling that the World Tree was going to use its high-level combatants this time, and the Tree King should not have revived yet. This time, there might be a new Tree King coming.

Among the five Great Tree Kings, only the Subduing Tree King had the simplest and most violent ability. The other few were all full of tricks. No matter who came, they would only be harder to deal with than him.

At the same time, in the Flickering World, in the territory of the Black Star Army, on a desolate planet.

Boom!

The two blurry figures were like shooting stars as they flew across the barren land, colliding with each other continuously. Every time they collided, an intense shockwave exploded, leaving huge craters on the ground.

Suddenly, the two figures came to a halt and revealed their appearances. One was Lothaire, and the other was Karlot.

Lothaire spun the dagger with his finger and put it into the blade pouch on his waist. "Your strength has increased again. You can already withstand my current strength. I will release more combat strength in the next combat training and continue squeezing out your potential."

"Alright, I will train hard." Karlot's fists clashed together creating sparks. His face was filled with determination.

This was not the first time that he had requested to go to the frontlines to fight the enemies, but Black Star had rejected every time. He knew that this was a sign that Han Xiao valued his potential and was giving him time to grow.

Karlot understood that his main mission was to focus on training and grow to the point where he could rush to the frontlines to help Han Xiao. Therefore, after the war broke out, he took the initiative to train every day.

"Hmm, at this rate you will become a Beyond Grade A soon…"

Although Lothaire said this, he was secretly cursing.

After training Karlot for the past few days, he realized that Karlot's improvement was extraordinary. Furthermore, his growth did not slow down because of his increasing strength. Instead, it became faster and faster. It was as if there was no bottleneck. His daily improvement was visible to the naked eye.

Lothaire had originally been curious about why Han Xiao thought so highly of Karlot, but now, he no longer had any doubts.

There really was such a genius in the world? How did Black Star manage to dig him out?

World Tree Territory, Tree King Palace.

On the five thrones sat two figures. One was the Heart Tree King, and the other was the Fortitude Tree King covered in heavy armor. Below the two Tree Kings stood many Executive Officers. Some of those who had died in the battles before had been revived.

"Has the information been released?"

"It has been shown through the foreseers," Tedrian replied with his head lowered.

"Hmm, I hope they will place all their attention on this."

The Heart Tree King rubbed the armrest as he nodded slowly.

Tedrian continued, "In the previous attacks, we have already calculated the rough structure of the intercepting circle, as well as the number of troops the other party has stationed along with the follow-up reinforcement limit. This time, we will increase the strength of our troops, and we should be able to break through the intercepting circle in one go. At the very least, we will be able to clear their spatial anchor orbit…"

Hearing this, the Heart Tree King nodded and did not say anything else. He waved his hand and let the executives leave.

Very soon, only the two tree kings were left in the palace.

The Fortitude Tree King turned his head slightly. He seemed to be looking at the Heart Tree King from the corner of his eyes behind the mask.

"You've already decided to take action personally? Is this what you want me to do?"

"Hmm, I'm the only one who can deal with that recovery-type Esper, and that Universal Treasure can only be used to its fullest potential in my hands… If I die there, you'll be in charge of the matters here," the Heart Tree King said calmly.

"How long will it take for the Subduing Tree King to revive?" The Fortitude Tree King frowned.

"Although I'm supplying him with resources every day, it'll still take some time." The Heart Tree King waved his hand.

The Fortitude Tree King was silent for a bit, "In that case, bring my Lord's Avatar, Apostle Weapons, and mechanical army over."

"You plan to save my life?"

"If I let you stay alive, you can manage the affairs here, and I can continue to stay comfortably in the mother tree and absorb nutrients," the Fortitude Tree King said coldly.

The Heart Tree King shook his head. "The civilization this time is very strong. Sooner or later, you will have to participate in it yourself."

"We'll see."

After saying this, the Fortitude Tree King's body melted into the tree crown and disappeared.

Seeing this, the Heart Tree King felt a little resigned.

No matter how hardworking they were in the past, after being chosen as a Tree King, one would become lazier and lazier. This applied even to the Fortitude Tree King—a Mechanic.

He still remembered that this guy was a research maniac before he became the Tree King. Now, he could not even be bothered to build machinery, let alone research and develop. He had relied on the Mother Tree to transform everything for him…..

Comparatively, the Heart Tree King preferred the Subduing Tree King. He could make that guy work with just a few words. Compared to the others, he was indeed the best tool.

Chapter 1357: Battle of Attrition; Disadvantage

The three Universal Civilizations received news from Han Xiao that the World Tree was suspected to be planning for a new attack, and they began to prepare for war. The waiting troops stationed at the rear were mobilized, causing the intercepting force to rise steadily in numbers.

As Destiny's Child did not obtain any intelligence on the World Tree's subsequent actions, the three Universal Civilizations could only remain vigilant and maintain the highest level of detection throughout the day. The officers of the various levels were also tense and did not dare relax. It was as if they knew a knife would slash at them but did not know when.

Due to the expansion of the intercepting perimeter, the wormhole support network also had to be extended. The three Universal Civilizations could not be sure which area the World Tree would attack.

In the blink of an eye, almost a month had passed, but the World Tree still did not launch an attack. Just as the three Universal Civilizations were starting to suspect that this was a trap, a report finally sounded from the detection device. A large fleet of the World Tree had entered the observation area and was slowly advancing toward the intercepting circle. The number of battleships was more than 200 billion, which was clearly the new wave of invading troops that the intelligence had shown.

Due to the special observation device that Han Xiao had provided, the three Universal Civilizations' range of detection far exceeded their area of control. This meant that they could launch an attack at the World Tree fleet from a further distance, indirectly increasing the strategic distance between them and their enemies for interception.

After the three Universal Civilizations locked onto their target, they immediately activated their over-the-horizon firepower. At the same time, they used the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device to send out the Spacetime Splicing Self-Destructing Team in an attempt to exhaust more enemy forces.

The World Tree Army endured a period of indiscriminate bombardment before passing through a large portion of the strategic depth and arriving at the edge of the area controlled by the three Universal Civilizations. In front of them was the space anchor network that sealed the jump points.

However, the World Tree Army did not behave like the previous three times. To prevent too many troops from being consumed on the way, they stopped at the edge of the three Universal Civilizations' control area and expanded the Lerbo Space Protection Belt to block the long-range attacks of the fleet. At the same time, they split up and coordinated with each other while sweeping through the space anchoring tracks.

This time it seemed like the World Tree did not want to launch a sudden attack. Instead, it planned to use the large army as the base to launch a large-scale battle.

The fleet sweeping the orbit this time was not the small fleet from before. It was much larger, and the three Universal Civilizations were in a dilemma. They knew that the World Tree was forcing them to leave the interception fortifications and go out to fight in the wild, which would make it more efficient for them to be dealt with.

In the past few times, the interception circle had played a huge role in blocking the attacks of the World Tree. The most important thing was the wormhole network hidden in the middle of the layers of defense lines. This allowed them to be able to quickly gather their forces and arrive at the main area of the blockade.

If this was changed to a field battle, the Three Universal Civilizations' advantage in this aspect would be greatly reduced. Although the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device could also provide support, it was still a Universal Treasure that cost a lot to build. The restriction in its use caused the efficiency of sending troops in large quantities to be lower than the usual wormhole support channel.

However, if they did not do anything towards the World Tree fleet's actions, the space stabilization orbit that they had set up in the past few days would be destroyed. After weighing the pros and cons, the three Universal Civilizations sent out a portion of their forces to try and stop the World Tree fleet, and they continued to attack the large troops that the World Tree fleet had stationed at the edge of the control area. This led to many intense battles in the three Universal Civilizations area.

In order to reduce the casualties in the local battles, the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations took action one after another to help their troops fight against the enemy fleet. They were equipped with The King mechanical suits and could retreat to the intercepting base at any time. However, the experts from the World Tree did not appear, as though they did not intend to restrain the advanced combatants of the three Universal Civilizations.

Although the three Universal Civilizations had won most of the battles with relatively low casualties, they were unable to repair or maintain a stable space orbit under the pressure of the enemy's army, and they had to continuously suffer attacks. A short repulse of the sweeping troops was like drinking poison to quench their thirst.

After fighting like this for more than a month, both sides had lost tens of billions of troops. The three Universal Civilizations finally decided that they could not stop the enemy from destroying all the spatial stabilization orbits, so they had no choice but to throw away this burden and retract their forces to preserve their strength. They no longer invested their troops in a battle of attrition but exchanged for a different strategy to wipe out the World Tree Civilization's troops in the long-distance attack movements.

The two sides fought for another period of time. The World Tree Army finally wiped out all the space anchoring tracks set by the three Universal Civilizations after three months or so, freeing up the jump points of all the vanguard troops in the past half a year. They had paid almost a hundred billion troops for this.

On April 6, Year 784 in the Galaxy Calendar, the World Tree Army, which had been stationed at the edge of the control zone for months, finally started to attack the intercepting circle.

After a period of traversing, the World Tree Army, which only had about half of its troops left, finally crossed the strategic zones that the three Universal Civilizations set up, attempting to break through the blockade. They immediately engaged in an intense battle with the three Universal Civilizations.

The three Universal Civilizations were waiting for the enemy to be exhausted, and they also had the advantage in numbers. As soon as the battle started, they quickly gained the upper hand. According to this trend, it would not be difficult for them to withstand this wave of attacks and wipe out the World Tree fleet.

However, on the third day of the battle, three World Tree reinforcements arrived from the nearest jump point, and a total of 150 billion soldiers entered the battle. They attacked different areas, and the pressure on the three Universal Civilizations increased exponentially.

After fighting for five more days, two more batches of World Tree reinforcements arrived, totaling hundreds of billions.

On the ninth day, the eighty billion strong World Tree fleet arrived.

On the 14th day, 140 billion enemy reinforcements arrived.

On the twentieth day, 206 billion enemy reinforcements arrived.

The reinforcements from the World Tree were endless. The more people on the front line died, the more reinforcements would come from the rear. They wanted to fully utilize the advantage of a war of attrition, completely wearing down the entire intercepting circle!

...

"C-1008a battlefront is in an urgent situation … L-0213b battlefield front is in an urgent situation…"

The scene in the command room was very busy. The emotionless synthesized sound of the spaceship's artificial intelligence was constantly broadcasting the emergency alarms in the various war zones. Simon and the other upper echelons stared at the surveillance cameras of the battlefield with bloodshot eyes.

The intense battle had already lasted for almost a month, and it did not stop for even a second. All the surviving generals were exhausted, and the losses of both sides had already exceeded a hundred billion.

On their side, almost all the Beyond Grade As were injured. These injuries were all caused by the World Tree fleet and no fights between the experts on the two sides were included.

The World Tree's endless reinforcements put the battle at risk, and even the Beyond Grade As had no choice but to fight to resist the fleet. In this month, they seemed to have become firefighters—stabilizing the various battlefields that were in danger time and time again, without much time to rest and recover.

Even so, the contributions of many Beyond Grade As were only a drop in the bucket.

Many Beyond Grade As were worried. Although the high-level combatants of the World Tree did not take part in the battle, causing no new Beyond Grade As to appear on their side, seeing the three Universal Civilizations becoming more and more disadvantaged, everyone was worried.

Kasuyi looked at the battle monitors and came to Han Xiao's side. He said in a low voice, "The World Tree has launched an all-out attack, ignoring the casualties and fighting head-on. The first and second layers of defense have already been penetrated, and the enemy's reinforcements are still coming. From the looks of it, the intercepting circle would not be able to hold."

"I guess so."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh, having a solemn expression. He was equally fatigued as the rest.

The high-intensity war that lasted for a month had turned this place into a meat grinder. Most of the players had used up their daily revival quotas. In such a place, there was a limit to what he could do.

This time, the World Tree did not use any special plan. It simply relied on the advantage of numbers to fight head-on. If they did not break through the blockade, they would not stop sending reinforcements. If fighting for a month was not enough, then two months, three months… they could only be described with one word, reckless!

The intercepting circle could not stop the World Tree's advancement forever, and it would break sooner or later. However, this day seemed to have come earlier than expected. From the beginning of the formation, it only bought the three Universal Civilizations about a year more.

"Black Star, we have to consider retreating too," Kasuyi softly spoke.

Han Xiao ignored him, his gaze fixed at the battlefield outside.

Countless battleships were engaged in a fierce battle. The dazzling lights from their cannons were akin to the stars in the sky, silent and bright with a destructive aura. Every second, countless lives were being thrown into the embrace of death.

Even if the three Universal Civilizations' troops were routed, they would still have plenty of time to retreat.

Even if the World Tree had passed through the intercepting circle, it would still take a long time to reach the edge of the Flickering World. However, the three Universal Civilizations would most likely not be able to replicate a defensive line similar to the intercepting circle. This meant that the continuous charging of the World Tree Civilization could be seen as the countdown timer for the three Universal Civilizations' demise.

At this time, another World Tree fleet entered the battlefield. The familiar Tree King Halo followed and immediately increased the combat power of many World Tree members, attracting everyone's attention.

"This is the ability of the Tree King… They've finally sent out their high-level combatants. The three Universal Civilizations can hardly hold on any longer. If the Tree King uses his halo at this time, it will probably be the last straw that breaks the camel's back. I wonder which Tree King has come this time…"

Han Xiao's eyes flashed with unprecedented seriousness.

Not only him, but all the other Beyond Grade As also focused their attention on the source of the halo.

Chapter 1358: The Second Collision, The Unknown Tree King

In the real-time surveillance footage, the battle lines between the three Universal Civilizations' intercepting troops and the World Tree invasion fleet were extremely long. They were divided into many different war zones. The three most important war zones were the interception defense lines that the World Tree attacked heavily with troops numbering hundreds of billions.

Under everyone's gaze, a new fleet entered the main battlefield. There were not many of them, only a few hundred million, but they emitted extremely condensed energy fluctuations, displaying Beyond Grade A energy sources one after another on the radar.

As soon as this small fleet entered the battlefield, it brought a significant change to the main warzone. A green light spread out, and every World Tree battleship that was swept by it lit up with a faint green light, and with the enhancement of the Tree King's halo, the stalemate was immediately broken. The speed they were pushing forward with increased significantly.

"If this line of defense is breached, they will be able to reach the wormhole support network at the back of the war zone very soon. The situation will become even worse. This place will become a breakthrough point."

Simon looked at the situation. His deduction was the same as what the artificial intelligence had analyzed.

Secret Master crossed his arms and said with a deep voice, "You want us to kill this tree king? The difficulty is too high. Unless he leaves the protection of the fleet, we will only be throwing our lives away if we take the initiative to charge at him."

The other commander turned to look at Han Xiao. "Black Star, what do you say?"

"Let's wait and see. There's no opportunity right now."

It was rare for Han Xiao to have the same thought. Although he really wanted to get rid of this unknown tree king that had suddenly entered the battlefield, the other party was under the protection of hundreds of billions of fleets, so the possibility of killing him was too low.

Furthermore, the previous incident of the Tree King being killed had been sent back to the World Tree. This time, the Tree King would probably stay in the fleet obediently and not give him a chance.

He had already provided a lot of intelligence and technology, allowing the three Universal Civilizations to be in a much better situation than in his previous life. However, military strength had always been the World Tree's forte. Once they have launched a large-scale attack, the three Universal Civilizations would have to fight head-on if they wish to protect their territory. There were no shortcuts.

Although there were differences in technology between the two sides, they both had advanced civilizations that were equipped with lethal strategic technologies. For example, they knew how to defuse and counter the various spatial and dimension weapons. Most of the flashy technologies were useless against each other and could only be used to bully the weak. Only a small portion of their unique technologies was indecipherable.

The advantage of a Beyond Grade A was that their mobility and strength were concentrated in their individual body, and their strength was in guerrilla warfare. However, in such a large galactic battlefield, guerrilla warfare was unsuitable.

Generally speaking, the number of enemies did not mean much to Beyond Grade As. Whether it was tens or hundreds of billions of fleets, as long as they did not complete the encirclement, it would be very easy for Beyond Grade As to escape. However, due to strategic reasons, many Beyond Grade As had no choice but to hold the line here. This was not the forte of strong individuals. The time it took to destroy tens of thousands of battleships was more than enough for tens of billions of fleets to fire at the same time. Naturally, the efficiency of large scaling was incomparable.

However, only when dealing with foreign enemies would the Universal Civilizations bring out such a force. If they were to use it in a civil war, many new desolate universe belts would emerge.

"Send more reinforcements." Simon also knew that the risk was too high, so he did not request for a group of Beyond Grade As to carry out this mission. He only sent more troops to fill this war zone.

The World Tree Civilization kept sending reinforcements, and the three Universal Civilizations did the same. This was also the reason why the intercepting circle could last for a month. Otherwise, it would have been broken by the World Tree's second reinforcement.

As the spatial anchoring orbits had been cleared, the World Tree's jump point was directly outside the intercepting circle, and the reinforcement distance was shortened. Therefore, the reinforcements could quickly enter the battlefield.

However, just as Simon gave the order, something happened.

The reinforcements did not stay in the main formation but came to the crossfire area. One World Tree powerhouse after another flew out and surrounded a tall and skinny figure. The Tree King Halo on his body revealed his identity.

A group of Beyond Grade As patrolled back and forth on the battlefield, retreating every now and then. In terms of team battles, they were at the front.

"Hmm?"

Everyone's expression changed slightly.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "This guy wants to lure our high-level combatants out."

Everyone nodded. They naturally understood that the Tree King and a group of high-level combatants had not just appeared to take a stroll, but because they were unsatisfied with expending the three Universal Civilizations' forces.

If the three Universal Civilizations tried to surround them with troops, the Tree King and the others would surely retreat to the main formation. Only by sending out their high-level combatants would the Tree King and the others be willing to stay behind to fight and carry out the Exchange tactic that they had always thought was effective. Their goal was to exhaust the experts of the three Universal Civilizations.

If they did not do something about the Tree King, he would continue to provide halo buff, increasing the pressure on this war zone and opening up the battlefield. There was no loss for him.

It was as if he was exposing himself and providing an opportunity. If they did not go up and attack him, the opportunity would be wasted.

"Humph, looks like they are very confident," Reeve clenched his fists, eager to give it a try. She had never fought with a World Tree expert before.

Manison calmly said, "Be careful. They know that we have a recovery-type Esper and can greatly reduce our losses, but they still used the Tree King as bait to attempt the Exchange tactic. Maybe they have already found a way to deal with our recovery-type Esper."

"We can't rule out the possibility that they think that exchanging a hundred people for a few of us will be profitable," Sun Hunter said with a deep voice.

"So, are we going up?"

Kasuyi turned to look at Han Xiao, and everyone looked over.

Han Xiao did not reply immediately. Instead, he looked at the tree king who was being protected by many powerful experts.

After experiencing the war in his previous life, he naturally recognized the appearance of every tree king. Information about this person flashed through his mind.

'Heart Tree King Minacho, a Psychic among the five tree kings, has many methods. Although his strength is not much different from Subduing Tree King, he is probably twice as difficult to deal with. In my previous life, he heavily injured Kasuyi and Oathkeeper respectively and instigated more than four Beyond Grade As. Other than being killed in the last battle, he does not have any other records of death. The most common methods are Psychic Teleportation, Thoughts Tampering, Spirit Tide…'

The abilities of a Psychic were extremely strange and Han Xiao felt that it was extremely difficult to deal with them. The most threatening ability was the ability of instigation. It was extremely difficult to change the mind of a Beyond Grade A, and it was not something that could be done in a short time. The other party would most likely be unable to complete it during the battle, but even the slightest risk could not be ignored.

Han Xiao turned around and took in the expressions of the commanders. He took a deep breath and said:

"Since there's a chance, let's give it a try. If we can kill this tree king, the situation in this war zone will be much better. This is one of the few things we can do at the moment."

Han Xiao had another thought. Heart Tree King was a huge threat. If he could keep him here, the subsequent battles would be much easier.

Hearing this, the group nodded, and the Beyond Grade As who chose to join the battle walked out.

On the way to the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, Han Xiao was a few steps behind Aurora. He then opened his private communication device.

"Be careful later. I suspect that the Tree King will use his mental power to attack you from afar. Even if some of your life energy leaks, you'd better not go near the battlefield—even if you have to watch some of your comrades die. Remember to make Sorokin stay beside you and protect you. Although he's annoying, he can at least block a few mental attacks for you."

"Got it." Aurora nodded obediently.

On the other side, in the main war zone surrounded by the Tree King's halo.

Heart Tree King calmly led a group of resurrected World Tree experts around the battlefield. With so many Beyond Grade As gathered together, it was naturally very conspicuous. Wherever they passed, the fleets of the three Universal Civilizations focused their fire on them.

However, the nearby World Tree fleet kept using their shields to block the attacks for the Heart Tree King. Thus, Heart Tree King and the others seemed to be taking a stroll on the intense battlefield.

"Aren't the enemies sending their high-level combatants?"

Heart Tree King kept looking at the three Universal Civilizations' line of defense, but he was not anxious at all. After all, he had the initiative and was very patient.

As soon as he said that, Fortitude Tree King's voice sounded in his mind.

"Humph, I think you should come back. They probably won't dare to make a move. Don't waste my time. I want to return to the mother tree."

"Bear with it."

Heart Tree King was helpless.

For the Lord to descend, Fortitude Tree King had to be in the base. It had only been a short while, but he could not take it anymore and felt lazy to the bones.

At this moment, Fortitude Tree King was still on standby and had yet to activate his ability. They only had the powerless Lord's Avatar's body in their hands. This was Heart Tree King's request. This was a card he prepared to summon Fortitude Tree King when the time was right.

He still wanted to say something, but the next moment, Beyond Grade A energy suddenly appeared in his senses.

Heart Tree King and the many World Tree experts looked in the direction of the energy source and saw a group of Beyond Grade As flying out from the three Universal Civilizations' fleets and attacking them from across the battlefield. The leader was the outsider that left a deep impression on them.

"As expected, they still came… The number of people seems to have increased. It seems like they are using the same tactic, holding back their high-level combatants."

Heart Tree King's eyes flickered. Seeing the revivors participating in this battle, he immediately thought that they were the hidden experts of the three Universal Civilizations. As for Garoze and the others who had died in the previous battle, they did not join the battle because they were worried about their lives, so he naturally could not see them.

"Attack! Do your best to cause damage and force their recovery Esper out."

As this thought flashed through his mind, Heart Tree King did not show any signs of weakness. He took the lead and charged forward with the World Tree powerhouses following behind him.

The Beyond Grade As on both sides passed through the battlefield. There was no communication, they directly entered the enemy's formation and clashed.

The last time, the three Universal Civilizations had no choice but to surround and attack a portion of the peak Beyond Grade As. This time, the rest of the World Tree experts were stopped by the other peak Beyond Grade A Revivors. Reeve, Hilbert, and the others went to fight the Executive Officers, the high-level Holy Tree Emissaries, and the members of the 13 Ancestral Spirits.

The number of experts sent by the World Tree this time was almost the same as the last time, and they were at a disadvantage in terms of numbers. As soon as they fought, they were suppressed by the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations.

Han Xiao turned into the Mechanical Deity and went to find Heart Tree King. The energy shockwaves and psychic shockwaves exploded between the two of them, creating continually bursting blue and white bubbles.

Heart Tree King's combat style was completely different from that of Subduing Tree King. As a Psychic, he did not like to fight head-on and relied on his strange methods to move around nimbly. From time to time, he would release large AOE spells and convert his psychic energy into physical psychic energy, forming layers of shields to block the Mechanical Deity's torrential attacks.

Swoosh!

Psionic energy vibrated, and a huge mechanical blade slashed across. Heart Tree King seemed to have seen through it, and with a nimble dodge, he used psychic energy to pull his body away, avoiding the slash that contained Getta Hadoken.

The blade light was like a dark blue waterfall, sweeping across the battlefield. Hundreds of battleships exploded into smoke.

"Outsider, this is the first time we've met, right? I could not fight you the last time you came to our territory and caused a ruckus."

While dodging the close-range attacks of the Mechanical Deity and the mechanical army, Heart Tree King sent a mental message to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao did not reply. He raised his hand and shot out a few thin, dark red rays of light. Heart Tree King's body flashed, and he moved a distance away as though he had teleported. The rays of light only shattered the afterimages that he left behind.

This guy is so slippery…

Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

The psychic power of Heart Tree King was extremely sensitive. He used his psychic power to pull and control his body and was extremely agile. At the same time, he also constantly released mental interference to mislead the direction of his attacks and reduce his hit rate. Even when facing the bombardment from the mechanical army that had almost no blind spots, Heart Tree King was able to dodge them with ease, as though he had seen through all the attack trajectories in advance.

Heart Tree King's fighting style was the exact opposite of Kasuyi's wide-open combat style that ignored mana. It was exquisite and focused on harassing and exhausting the enemy. He flew around the enemy like a mosquito, stabbing the enemy from time to time before retreating immediately. It was very difficult for the enemy to hit him. His fighting style was very dirty and annoying.

'Pugilists are still the best. They like to fight head-on, how easy it is…'

Han Xiao could not help but miss Subduing Tree King.

However, although Heart Tree King was very agile, he had no choice but to focus on dealing with Han Xiao's attacks. Both of them restrained the other party.

While the two of them were fighting, in a certain battlefield not far away, a direct Beyond Grade A fought very fiercely. He exchanged blows with the Holy Tree Emissary and suffered heavy injuries. The next moment, a few dazzling beams of life energy shot out from the three Universal Civilizations' fleets.

The Holy Tree Emissary, who was long prepared, endured the pain and shot out a series of spells to intercept the life energy. Half of the life energy was scattered by his spells, but the remaining life energy suddenly changed its route, drawing a strange twisted path and hitting the target. This direct Beyond Grade A's life force quickly recovered.

"It hit!" Aurora, who was in the protective circle of the fleet, was overjoyed.

She had not spent the past half a year in vain. Every day, she trained her control over the life energy that left her body so that she could avoid being intercepted by the enemy and heal the target.

On the other side, Heart Tree King could not help but divert some of his attention to look in Aurora's direction.

"Found her…"

Before he could finish his thought, a few splitting rays arrived in front of him. He was slightly distracted, and he was a step too slow to dodge them, leaving several burning marks on his body.

Heart Tree King hurriedly retracted his attention and covered his wounds while avoiding the continuous pursuit from the mechanical army.

"I really can't afford to be distracted when dealing with this fellow. Fortunately, someone is able to stop him and give me the time to make a move…"

The next second, Heart Tree King suddenly retreated, and Han Xiao immediately chased after him.

One chased as the other fled, and their battlefield shifted by a large distance. A powerful Beyond Grade A energy suddenly rose from a World Tree battleship beside them.

The spaceship exploded, and a dark green Mechanical Deity appeared as though it had broken out of its shell. Its body expanded rapidly, and it held a double-edged mechanical war blade that was covered in energy circuits. The blade lashed down with astonishing psionic energy. At the same time, green armored mechanical soldiers swarmed out and bit Han Xiao's mechanical army.

"This energy… another Tree King!"

Han Xiao raised his brows and immediately raised his blade to meet the attack. Two gigantic Mechanical Deity weapons, one black, and one green clashed.

Clang!

The sound of heavy metals hitting each other reached everyone's mind, and a dazzling electric arc appeared in an instant. A huge energy shock wave swept away everything around it.

"Humph, outsider, I'll be your opponent." Fortitude Tree King's voice sounded in the public channel.

"Who are you?"

Han Xiao looked at the combat information and raised his brows in surprise.

This Tree King was not one of the five Great Tree Kings he knew in his previous life!

Wasn't Emperor Tree King the Mechanic class Tree King? Where did this Tree King pop out from ‽

While he was still in shock, Heart Tree King took advantage of the fact that Fortitude Tree King was blocking his opponent and left the battlefield. He locked onto Aurora's life force with his mind.

Then, he opened his arms, and a diamond-shaped purple leaf appeared on his chest, spinning and emitting strange fluctuations.

The next moment, Heart Tree King's mental strength burst forth.

"Illusion - Mind Lock!"

Chapter 1359: Thought Seal, Herberlon Moves

Surging psychic energy flowed into the floating purple crystal leaf, and a beam of purple light shot out toward Aurora, who was in the protective circle of the three Universal Civilizations.

Seeing this, a portion of the mechanical army closest to the beam shook off the entanglement of Fortitude Tree King and formed a psionic shield in front of the beam.

However, the moment they came into contact, the light purple beam did not show any signs of being obstructed. Its speed did not change at all, and it easily penetrated the psionic shield as though it did not exist. The mechanical soldiers that blocked it with their bodies were also penetrated, but their bodies were not damaged at all. It was as though this beam did not exist in the material world and could ignore all kinds of defenses.

"Hmm? Stop this attack." Han Xiao had been paying attention to Heart Tree King's actions. Although he did not know what method Heart Tree King had used, it would be best to stop it. He pushed Fortitude Tree King's mechanical body away and immediately called his teammates who were fighting all over the battlefield.

Hearing Han Xiao's command, a portion of the Beyond Grade As who were closer to Han Xiao barely managed to divert their attention. They used various methods, throwing out their magic, Esper Abilities, and Psychic powers in an attempt to disperse the light purple beam, but they were all penetrated.

Seeing this, everyone was shocked.

"What ability is this?"

"I can't block it. Why does it look like it has the characteristics of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter ‽"

Under everyone's gaze, the beam of light passed through the Beyond Grade As' battle zone and shot into the protective circle of the three Universal Civilizations. It passed through the battleships that came to stop it one after another. No matter how Aurora's battleship changed its position, the beam of light followed it and quickly entered Aurora's spaceship.

The light purple beam passed through the shield and the exterior armor and shot into the command room, heading straight for Aurora in the room. Sorokin, the double agent, appeared in an instant and sent condensed Psychic energy, but it did not cause any effect. Even his body was penetrated, but he was not injured at all.

Just as it was about to hit Aurora, when it was only a few meters away, the light purple beam suddenly slid away as if it had hit an invisible barrier. It flew out of the battleship in a flash.

Aurora, who was in a tense state, heaved a sigh of relief.

"Looks like the Spacetime Amber is still useful…"

In front of her was a Spacetime Amber Ball. Han Xiao had given her a batch of it to protect herself. Currently, there were still not any known items that could pass through the Spacetime Amber Ball.

However, the light purple beam did not dissipate. After flying out of the battleship, it circled and adjusted its position before shooting toward Aurora.

Seeing this scene from afar, Heart Tree King's expression changed slightly as though he was surprised.

"There's actually a way to block it? Could it be a special substance that isolates the mother tree from the individual?"

Heart Tree King did not hesitate. He immediately grabbed the purple crystal leaf and activated the green power of the World Tree, instantly activating a new power.

Crack!

Cracks appeared on the surface of the purple crystal leaf. While it was damaged, it released more energy and emitted a halo.

The light purple beam that was chasing Aurora suddenly exploded and disappeared.

At first glance, Sorokin thought that this guy had given up on attacking. However, he suddenly heard a 'plop' sound beside him. He turned around and saw Aurora falling to the ground.

"What's wrong?"

Sorokin was shocked as he quickly approached Aurora. He saw that Aurora's eyes were lifeless, and she was staring straight ahead. Her eyes did not move at all, as though she had lost her senses.

He quickly used his psychic energy to probe Aurora's mind, only to discover that Aurora's consciousness had already been sealed up and was wrapped within a thick purple crystal. Green energy flowed within the crystal and his psychic energy could not penetrate it.

"What's going on? Aurora and I have broken our soul link!" Hila's voice sounded in the channel. She was the first to notice the abnormality, and her tone was urgent.

"Aurora has lost consciousness. Some kind of energy has sealed her thoughts. I don't know what kind of psychic ability it is… Not good, I can't undo it in a short time."

Sorokin told the truth and used his psychic energy to attack the purple crystal. However, the purple crystal in Aurora's mind was extremely tough, and his psychic energy could only leave shallow marks on it. Very soon, the purple crystal repaired itself.

Swoosh!

Just as he said that Han Xiao used The King to leave the battlefield and instantly appeared beside Aurora. Without saying a word, he poked Aurora and forced out combat information to check on Aurora's condition.

All of Aurora's abilities turned into a frozen gray color, and a special status appeared in her stats window.

[Illusion - Mind Lock]: The sealed individual's thoughts and consciousness enter a vegetative state. The target will fall into infinite illusion composed of their desires, ambitions, visions, imagination, fear, dreams, goals, and other factors. If the target treats the illusion as the truth, they will continuously supply energy to the seal. The seal will not weaken with time and will instead grow stronger. Meanwhile, the target will continue to grow weaker and be unable to see through the illusion. Duration: Unknown.

"A thought seal that even Sorokin finds difficult to break… It must be a Universal Treasure's characteristic."

The purple crystal leaf that Heart Tree King had taken out flashed past Han Xiao's mind, and his face tightened. He did not have any information about this item in his previous life.

The eruption just now ignored the distance and attack path and turned into a direct attack within the range. It was like a spiritual explosion that directly affected an individual. As long as Aurora was not wrapped up tightly by the Spacetime Amber, there would always be a gap and she would suffer the attack.

If this move was used on others, it would also pose a great threat, but Heart Tree King only used it on one person. Furthermore, the purple crystal leaf was damaged after it was used, so there might be some restrictions.

This is not good. Aurora's energy level is still too low… Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

Aurora's Esper Ability was special, but her own level was limited. The effect of Heart Tree King's seal was very obvious, and the chances of her seeing through the illusion were too low. If her strength was at the peak Beyond Grade A level, the seal would definitely not be as strong as it was now.

"Anyone with psychic abilities, come and try to unseal it."

Han Xiao immediately gave the order. He did not have time to stay there any longer. He quickly activated the King's repeated warping ability and returned to his original position.

In just a short while, the Mechanical Deity, which had lost its core support, was cut into pieces by Fortitude Tree King. He had no choice but to use his Mechanical Force to connect the pieces of the Mechanical Deity back together and continue fighting with the Tree King.

Upon knowing that the healer had fallen, the Beyond Grade As were immediately anxious. They wanted to shake off their opponents and go back to check on Aurora, but the World Tree experts had also received the order from Heart Tree King. They were extremely spirited and charged forward with all their might, not letting the Beyond Grade As leave.

"Ha, your recovery-type Esper has been defeated by His Excellency the Tree King. Let's see how you can recover!"

"Aren't you unafraid of death? Come on, continue fighting!"

"Without confidence, do you still dare to exchange injuries?"

In the mental network, many World Tree experts were extremely excited.

The scene of the previous battle was still vivid in their minds. This group of enemies relied on the healer behind them to constantly exchange injuries with them. Even if they were heavily injured time and time again, as long as they were fed a mouthful of milk, they would instantly be full of energy and the battle would be very uncomfortable for World Tree experts. In the end, they had no choice but to use the self-detonation tactic, but they could only drag a few people down with them.

Thinking about the embarrassing battle last time, many of the World Tree Supers were furious. At this moment, Heart Tree King had used his methods to wipe out the confidence of these enemies, and the Beyond Grade As of the World Tree were all energized. They felt that they could finally show their strengths…

They had never been afraid of exchanging lives for lives!

Fortitude Tree King turned around and deflected Han Xiao's attack. Hearing the commotion in the mental network, he could not help but send a message to Heart Tree King.

"Are you sure this will seal the enemy's recovery Esper forever?"

"I didn't say forever. As long as there are enough people with psychic abilities who spend a lot of time wearing down the seal, it will be broken sooner or later… However, as long as the recovery-type Esper does not play a role in this battle, my goal will be achieved."

Heart Tree King kept the cracked purple crystal leaf into his body and heaved a sigh of relief.

"Without the recovery-type Esper, the battle losses will return to normal. As long as we destroy enough high-level combatants in this battle and cause substantial damage, it won't matter even if that Esper wakes up later."

In his opinion, even if he could only seal the Esper in one battle, the Exchange tactic would succeed. As long as they could get rid of enough high-level combatants this time, the World Tree's snowballing advantage could be put to full display.

Now that the plan was more than half complete, Heart Tree King was relieved and returned to the battlefield. Together with Fortitude Tree King, they surrounded and attacked Han Xiao. The three of them were locked in battle.

Not long after, some Beyond Grade As finally managed to shake off their opponents with the help of their teammates and returned to Aurora's side. However, after checking, their hearts sank.

"The situation is not good. This thought seal is too strong and is protected by a special force. Even if we attack together, it will not be broken in a short time." Kasuyi's voice sounded in the channel.

"Not even you?" Sun Hunter was shocked.

Kasuyi shook his head. "Although I have unlimited energy, there is a limit to the strength of my psychic energy. Just like how the water current keeps washing the reefs, it needs time."

Upon hearing Kasuyi's words, the hearts of many association members skipped a beat.

The next moment, a member of the association suggested in the channel.

"Black Star, why don't we retreat first and fight them after we break Aurora's seal?"

"Do you think the World Tree will blankly watch our retreat? Even if we retreat, the Tree King's Halo will continue to take effect. There's a high chance that the frontal defense line won't be able to hold on. When we unseal Aurora and want to fight them again, it's hard to say if they will give us the chance. By then, it will be too late."

Oulou spoke first before Han Xiao could.

A large number of direct Line members ignored life and death and continued to fight with their opponents. Seeing this, many association members who wanted to retreat could not desert and could only continue fighting.

However, without the protection of the milkmaid, a large number of association members considered their own safety and did not dare to risk their lives like last time. Their combat power was far inferior to the first time they had fought. Instead, they were faintly suppressed by the World Tree experts who were not afraid of death. Luckily, they had the advantage in numbers this time, and there was a group of revivors to hold the situation. Otherwise, their losses might have exceeded the other party.

The Beyond Grade As all had their thoughts and the battle this time was much bloodier. The Beyond Grade As on both sides were frequently sacrificed, and the damage was increasing.

"Hehe, without that recovery-type Esper, your true colors are revealed. The casualties will only increase. How long can you last?"

As Han Xiao dealt with the encirclement of Fortitude Tree King and Heart Tree King, the other party's mocking mental message appeared in his mind.

Boom!

Energy Explosion, a dark blue compressed energy cannon fired at Fortitude Tree King. Han Xiao took the opportunity to glance at the loss of the Beyond Grade As calmly and did not respond to the other's taunt.

Turning around, Han Xiao started to fight with Fortitude Tree King that was charging at him again. Suddenly, he felt a sharp pain in his brain as Heart Tree King sent several mental shockwaves.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao felt a little troubled.

"Just one Tree King alone is already difficult to deal with. With the two of them attacking together, it is much harder… Although I can withstand the attacks of these two, it will be difficult for me to deal much damage to them… I need someone to share the pressure and let me fight with one person…"

As this thought flashed through his mind, Han Xiao gritted his teeth and looked at Heart Tree King.

His goal was not to be in a stalemate with the two of them. If he could capture a tree king here, that would be for the best. At the very least, he would have to kill one of them and let the other party enter hibernation. If he allowed the other party to escape unscathed, that would be a huge loss.

He was being held back, and the two tree kings were looking after each other. If they wanted to leave, he would most likely not be able to stop them.

Han Xiao's target was Heart Tree King. After all, Fortitude Tree King was only a Lord's Avatar, so there was no need to deal with him. However, someone had to restrain him.

Although Fortitude Tree King was a stranger, his strength was worthy of his identity as a Tree King.

In his previous life, the World Tree War was a very late version. Now that the war had been brought forward by many years, Han Xiao could only think that Fortitude Tree King was the Mechanic-class Tree King of this time period. He would lose his position in the future and Emperor Tree King would replace him. As for the reason, Han Xiao had no idea.

Suppressing the distracting thoughts in his mind, Han Xiao looked at the battlefield. Seeing that most of his teammates were fighting a bloody battle, he could not help but switch to the communication channel and send an order to one of his external helpers.

At this time, Han Xiao felt a sense of danger. He hurriedly opened the Emperor's Cape and saw that Fortitude Tree King had used some kind of skill. The double-edged war blade swept up a whirlpool of green energy and smashed onto his body. Green flames exploded, and the gigantic body was sent flying for a distance.

"Humph, you still dare to be distracted in front of me. You are disregarding me." Fortitude Tree King brandished his blade and said coldly.

"What? Is this the best you can do?" Han Xiao clicked his tongue and casually replied with a joke that the other party did not understand.

"Humph, I don't know what you're talking about, but with me restraining you, you won't be able to help your other comrades." Fortitude Tree King pointed his blade at Han Xiao.

"Are you a pig? Snorting again and again!"

Han Xiao was not to be outdone. He realized that the World Tree experts liked to chat when they fought.

"Outsider, they think you have an almost indestructible body. I'll see if I can kill you today!"

Fortitude Tree King activated all his armor cannons and shot out countless beams of light. He then turned his blade and was about to charge forward.

However, right at this moment, the light from the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device suddenly flashed behind Han Xiao, and a gigantic Mechanical Deity appeared. It was none other than Herberlon!

The interception war had already been going on for a month, and Herberlon had been on standby since a long time ago. The moment he received Han Xiao's message, he immediately used the teleportation device and descended from the Flickering World. During the stalemate before this war broke out, he had already completed the loading of his weapons. He was now fully armed and in peak condition!

"World Tree! Our war is not over yet!"

Herberlon's furious roar could be heard in the public channel. Countless thrusters were activated at the same time, and a huge force pushed Herberlon to accelerate continuously. The giant blade in his hand swept up psionic energy and slashed toward Fortitude Tree King.

Clang!

Herberlon's attack landed on Fortitude Tree King's defense, and a shockwave swept out.

Another new force entered the venue, and many World Tree experts looked over, stunned.

"You… Herberlon? You're still alive ‽" Fortitude Tree King was shocked.

All the World Tree powerhouses present knew Herberlon. They had fought against him when they destroyed the Karma Republic, so they had a deep impression of this enemy.

Heart Tree King was stunned for a moment before he suddenly realized the truth.

"I see. This civilization's initial intelligence on our World Tree came from you!"

Chapter 1360: Heart Tree King's Bullsh*tting and Sealing Plan

The World Tree experts were suddenly enlightened.

No wonder this civilization had shown a certain level of understanding of the World Tree when they first came into contact with it. Herberlon, whose home was invaded, was the best source of information, which made sense.

The members of the World Tree remembered every battle clearly. Although the Karma Republic Alliance was not a strong opponent, Herberlon had left a deep impression on many World Tree experts. Some of them had even participated in the siege. This was a rare prey that had slipped away from their hands and disappeared into the vast universe after the fall of the Karma Republic.

Fortitude Tree King quickly recovered from the shock of seeing someone he knew. He activated the protective equipment on his body and blocked the furious attack from Herberlon.

"A loser from a destroyed civilization dares to continue opposing us instead of hiding. You managed to survive last time, but you won't be so lucky this time. The mother tree has always wanted to devour you, so why don't you merge with us and reunite with your compatriots!"

"As long as I'm alive, the glory of the Karma Republic will never disappear!"

Herberlon stabbed his blade into Fortitude Tree King's thick shield and embedded it inside. Two new mechanical arms suddenly grew out from his shoulders and firmly locked Fortitude Tree King's body in front of him. Following this, the flesh and machinery on his chest slid open, revealing a large energy outlet.

Boom!

An extremely thick dark red beam of light shot out, and in a flash, Fortitude Tree King's chest was penetrated, leaving a huge hole with a torn edge. Broken parts flew everywhere.

This time, the damage was not light. Fortitude Tree King hurriedly activated the flowing force field and the power structure of the mechanical suit. A huge force was generated, and he immediately cut off the mechanical arm that was holding him. He then kicked Herberlon away, leaving a deep footprint on the latter's abdomen armor.

A portion of the mechanical soldiers in the surroundings returned to Fortitude Tree King's body like tired birds returning to their nest. A large number of mechanical structures flowed in his body and quickly filled up the wound on his chest.

Herberlon's gigantic body stopped its retreat. He raised his hand and created an invisible force field that covered Fortitude Tree King. Fortitude Tree King's body froze as if he had been hit by a Body Immobilization spell.

Just as the decryption device on Fortitude Tree King's body was analyzing the operating principles of the force field at a high speed, Herberlon grabbed his blade with both hands. His muscles and machinery twisted, accumulating an endless amount of energy. Dark red streams of light appeared on his body, and his energy reaction soared!

The next moment, Herberlon's gigantic body suddenly turned into a red bolt of lightning and charged forward. He instantly passed by Fortitude Tree King as if he teleported and appeared behind him.

"Deity Maneuver!"

Swoosh!

In a flash, a huge hole was carved out on Fortitude Tree King's waist, and he was almost cut in half. Energy continued to destroy the insides of the body through the wound, and the wound was still expanding.

The space around Fortitude Tree King shook, and he suddenly broke the control of the force field and covered the wound on his waist. At the same time, he hurriedly turned around to block Herberlon's charge. The force traveled along the clashing weapons and into his arm, causing a violent tremor. A large portion of the parts in both of their bodies malfunctioned from the tremor.

"What a troublesome guy…"

Fortitude Tree King was in a stalemate with Herberlon. He glanced at Han Xiao and realized that he had already left to fight Heart Tree King.

He wanted to help but could not escape. Although he called Herberlon a loser, he had to admit that this guy had the might to restrain him.

On the other side, Han Xiao had finally gotten rid of the two-on-one situation. He chased after Heart Tree King with his mechanical army, and the psychic barrier clashed with the bombardment of fire.

Heart Tree King dodged Han Xiao's psionic slash and the World Tree Roots—that he got after transforming—moved like tentacles around him, blocking the attacks from all directions.

"I have to say, during our battle in the universe, you are the most troublesome Super Lifeform we have encountered. There are not many people who are qualified to stand shoulder to shoulder with you. Because of your existence, our large group of foreign experts is almost useless. Without you, your high-level combatants would not be able to fight us."

Han Xiao turned a deaf ear to him. He clapped his hands, and the anti-psychic energy device released waves of energy. The psychic barrier seemed to have received an attack at its weak points, and it exploded repeatedly, forcing Heart Tree King to have no choice but to invest more energy to stabilize his psychic strength.

Seeing that Han Xiao did not speak, Heart Tree King did not give up and continued.

"I can give you a promise. If you are willing to leave, the World Tree will not chase after you and your companions—not that we would be able to chase you anyway. You can stay far away from this battle that is bound to fail. The universe is so big, you can live anywhere. Living is more important than anything."

"You guys haven't won yet, don't be too confident."

Han Xiao replied calmly, ignoring the pain of his brain being tortured by the mental attacks. He swung his blade again and collided with the Psychic King.

Heart Tree King shook his head. "It's very difficult for high-level combatants to decide the direction of the universe-level war. Even if you can withstand the attacks of our high-level combatants time and time again, you won't be able to change the situation in the frontal war. You're destined to be defeated. Actually, you have another choice. You might as well join us and become a member of the World Tree. You can join us to fight in the universe. Your ability is more than enough to replace the position of Fortitude Tree King."

"Trying to instigate me?" Han Xiao sneered. "Putting aside whether I'm willing to become a puppet that has lost its free will, just my identity as an expert from another race will never allow me to become the Tree King. You'd better save this trick to fool others."

Heart Tree King did not mind. "Even if you kill me and cause our fleet in this war zone to lose the buff of the World Tree's power, we might still be able to break through your defense through normal battles. Is it worth it to sacrifice so many high-level combatants for such a small chance?"

Han Xiao was too lazy to respond. He activated another army combat skill and changed it to provide the bonus of agility and long-range attack speed, making the mechanical army more agile. The continuous energy weapons rained down on the roots of the World Tree, tearing them into pieces.

Seeing this, Heart Tree King did not give up and continued to use the chatting tactic. "You and I will not be able to determine the victor. I have witnessed the battle between you and Subduing Tree King. I will not fall into the same trap."

Wow, you can really bullsh*t, almost catching up to me!

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

However, on second thought, he felt that what Heart Tree King said was not without reason. If the other party was prepared, it would not be easy to replicate the strategy that dealt with Subduing Tree King.

If they fought normally, he would indeed have the upper hand, but at the crucial moment, Heart Tree King would still have the choice of self-destructing and retreating to receive the protection of the fleet. The chances of killing him were very low.

Han Xiao then opened the private chat and contacted Hila.

"Hila, leave the battlefield first and stay beside Aurora."

"Hmm?"

Hila's tone was filled with killing intent, but it was toward the enemy.

After Aurora lost consciousness, Hila immediately entered a berserk state, killing everyone on the battlefield. She did not even send the dead into the Underworld but turned them all into soul energy to strengthen herself. Her presence on the battlefield was extremely strong, and she had already killed two Holy Tree Emissaries.

The dead only had one soul. If they were sent to the Underworld to be heroic spirits, they would not be able to trigger the rapid growth of the Power Of The Dead. The galactic battlefield was like a meat grinder. Hila followed Han Xiao's philosophy most of the time and sent the soldiers sacrificed by the three Universal Civilizations into the Underworld. Only a few times did she use them to strengthen herself.

Even so, due to the huge number of people, Hila's combat strength was growing at an astonishing rate, and she was like a completely different person from before the war. Even without the ability to shorten the opponent's lifespan, there were not many people in the association who had the confidence to defeat her.

"I have a plan. Let's see if we can deal with this tree king who knocked Aurora unconscious. Follow my orders."

"…Alright!"

The one that Hila wanted to kill the most was Heart Tree King. Hearing that Han Xiao had a plan, she quickly regained some of her calmness. She glanced at the wounded ancestral spirit in front of her, suppressed the killing intent in her heart, and retreated toward the three Universal Civilizations' fleet.

After getting rid of the World Tree experts one after another, Hila returned to Aurora's spaceship with difficulty. To escape from the battle, she had gained many new wounds on her body. Although her healer had collapsed temporarily, her Power Of The Dead had extraordinary self-regeneration, and her wounds were gradually healing.

Suddenly, there was a flash of light in the cabin, and a mechanical soldier wearing the King armor teleported over, handing the item in his hand to Hila.

"Hmm? This is…"

Hila looked down at the item in the mechanical soldier's hands, and a hint of surprise appeared on her usually expressionless face. She coldly glanced at the surrounding crew members, and only when she saw that no one was moving did she take it.

This time, Han Xiao's voice sounded in the private channel.

"I'll give this to you for the time being. I've let you practice with it before. Do you know how to use it?"

"Hmm," Hila said with a deep voice. "What's your plan?"

"I'll try to create an opportunity later. If it succeeds, use the King on that mechanical soldier to teleport over, then connect to your Advancing in the Dead Sea and teleport to the target to use it…" Han Xiao quickly explained.

"I understand."

Hila nodded and looked at the item in her hand. It was a white crystal the size of a palm.

This item was the Spacetime Amber!

Usually, Han Xiao would not give this thing to others, but this time, he would probably need someone else to do it.

In the past few months, he had trained Hila on how to use this Universal Treasure to coordinate with [Azure Dragon Bind] and form a new strategy.

Through Phillip's battle simulation, he realized that in most situations, the die-together tactic could only kill the tree king or force it to self-destruct. From the looks of it, this new tactic was the method with the highest success rate to capture them.

Maintaining his private channel, Han Xiao looked at Heart Tree King, who was easily evading the attacks of the mechanical army.

"I hope this works…"

Chapter 1361: Facing Death and Gamble

The battle zone of the Beyond Grade As was scattered all over the battlefield, and it was a bloody battle. Individual strengths from both sides fell one after another, and the battles between the fleets of both sides were equally intense. The World Tree Army, which was enhanced by the Tree King's halo, continued to advance. Although the three Universal Civilizations continued to provide reinforcements, the defense line was still slowly but surely retreating.

Due to the constantly changing battlefield of the fleets, the battle areas of the Beyond Grade As were also shifting accordingly.

Ames moved around in space, controlling the force field to harass the enemies or help her comrades. Her dress was stained with blood.

There were more than ten Beyond Grade As participating in the team battle in the area she was in, and the association members and the direct descendants had the upper hand against the enemies.

Force Field Esper Abilities had an all-rounder characteristic and could be used for both attack and defense. Ames was mainly used as a control type on the battlefield. Occasionally, she would condense a force field or drag a battleship to attack, and the damage was not low.

She extended her palm and used Gaze of the Dragon on one of the Holy Tree Emissaries. Ames quickly scanned the battlefield and realized that the battlefield of Herberlon, Fortitude Tree King, Han Xiao, and Heart Tree King had already been shifted to a faraway place. The layers of battleships in the battlefield almost covered their figures, and she could only see the occasional flashes of energy that were far more intense than here.

"Looks like he won't be able to kill the Tree King so quickly…"

Ames frowned slightly and retracted her gaze. She dodged a compressed beam of light and countered with a pale green shock wave.

Looking at the battlefield, Ames saw a brief flaw in the enemy's side and was about to ask her teammates to work together to create time for her to gather her energy, but at this moment, the other party threw a wave of focused fire at her. The few association members who were supposed to be blocking in front immediately dodged, and she had no choice but to stop accumulating her energy and dodge.

"This won't do. There's no way to kill the enemy."

Ames glanced at the association members and shook her head.

Even after having the upper hand for so long, they had not been able to cause much damage to the enemy. Every time they wanted to advance, the World Tree experts would become more fearless. In contrast, the comrades of the association would cower in fear because of this, not wanting to be injured. This caused them to lose the opportunity to expand their advantage again and again.

The temporary loss of the milkmaid had a huge impact on the Beyond Grade As' battle. Most of the association members did not have the mentality to risk their lives like last time and did not want to get injured. Their combat style became more conservative while the World Tree experts became more ferocious.

Ames heard from the channel that many of the association members were dissatisfied with Han Xiao's plan. Initially, they planned to quickly get rid of the Tree King to reduce the disadvantage of the main battlefield. However, both sides were in a stalemate now. Black Star could not complete his goal, and Aurora was also beaten back temporarily, leading to the sacrifice of many Beyond Grade As. In their eyes, the plan had failed, and it was a sure loss.

Furthermore, after fighting for so long, the main battlefield was already in a bad situation. Even if they killed the Tree King now, they might not be able to reverse the situation. Therefore, in the eyes of many association members, the sacrifices from this attack plan were meaningless. Instead, many of them had lost the one-time Sanctum Revival opportunity, so they were filled with complaints.

The Beyond Grade A Association members had all prepared for the worst. They still believed that the Sanctum Revival could only happen once, so they did not take Han Xiao's words of 'convincing' the Revivors seriously.

Many of them were already thinking of retreating, but they could not leave the battle for the time being. They could only protect themselves and were not willing to pay the price for killing their opponent. This kind of conservative mindset affected their combat strength, and Ames could only cooperate with her teammates in retreating. She had no intention of charging into the enemies alone.

At this moment, one of the Holy Tree Emissaries suddenly paused, as if the damage had been accumulated to the limit. His body stiffened, revealing an obvious flaw.

"Chance!"

Ames and her teammates immediately changed targets and focused their attacks on this person. All kinds of abilities shattered the defensive shield that the other party had hastily constructed and landed on his body, causing blood to splatter everywhere.

Just as they were about to pursue and kill the enemy, the other World Tree experts suddenly unleashed their full strength and charged toward the front of this heavily injured teammate, trying to force them to retreat like the previous few times.

Facing such a powerful attack, the members of the association hesitated and retreated. They did not face it head-on. It was not that they could not endure the attack head-on, but they were unwilling to do so. They would rather give up this opportunity than getting injured.

Seeing this, Ames felt a little helpless. This situation had already happened a few times. Due to the members of the association retreating, they had missed many opportunities.

But at this moment, a firm voice sounded in the channel.

"Cover me!"

One of the direct descendants suddenly advanced instead of retreating and faced this wave of attacks. The scene was like a surfer charging toward a tsunami. The shield on his body was instantly torn apart by the combined attack of many Beyond Grade As, and wounds exploded on his body.

Everyone was shocked. They did not have time to think about anything else. They quickly stopped and used ranged attacks to cover this teammate.

Ignoring the damage to his body, he endured the huge impact of the attack and charged at the heavily injured World Tree expert resolutely and decisively. His Pugilist flames were all concentrated on him, completely ignoring the enemy teammates who were rushing over.

Bang!

The two figures collided, and the heavily injured World Tree Beyond Grade A activated self-destruction without hesitation.

Ames and the others could only see the figure of this direct Beyond Grade A who showed no intention of retreating. The next moment, their vision was covered in white.

Boom!

A powerful light burst forth, and a huge energy ball rose up. Before the light dissipated, the World Tree Race experts in the surroundings were still attacking the self-destruction area.

The group of people hurriedly retreated some distance. When the self-destruction energy was fully released, they focused their attention on the area. There were only fragmented corpses left.

"…He's gone."

Everyone had complicated expressions.

The direct Beyond Grade A who died in the battle was not a Revivor. He knew that there was only one chance for Sanctum Revival, but he still risked his life to seize the opportunity. This was something they would never be able to do. These direct descendants who worked for the civilization had a purer attitude toward this war than them and were unafraid of death.

Ames shook her head. She knew that she was not that great, nor was she willing to be.

...

Time quickly passed.

On the battlefield filled with countless mechanical fragments, Han Xiao and Heart Tree King had been fighting for a long time, and both sides were exhausted.

In comparison, Heart Tree King's energy consumption was much higher. This was not only due to suppression from Han Xiao's energy level but also because of his class.

After all, mental attacks were ineffective against mechanical soldiers, and Han Xiao's main body was not afraid of his mental attacks. Only his physical attacks and psychic attacks would be effective. This meant that Heart Tree King was at a disadvantage when facing Han Xiao.

The green light on Heart Tree King's body had become much dimmer, and more than half of the World Tree Roots that appeared with his transformation had been destroyed. He was not in the same state as when they had first started fighting, and his movements were also slightly slower.

Using psychic energy to block the firepower of another mechanical army, Heart Tree King sent another message to Han Xiao.

"Did you see that? You've already lost. Even if you kill me, you won't be able to turn the situation around."

Hearing this, Han Xiao looked at the battle situation and could not help but click his tongue.

The World Tree Army in this war zone continued to advance. They had already broken through the defense zone and penetrated a few battle lines, forming a situation that was difficult to reverse. They had at least an eighty to ninety percent chance of breaking through the interception circle and turning this place into a breakthrough point for the overall battle. In a war of a scale of hundreds of billions, the victory of high-level combatants could no longer turn the situation around.

"When we arrive at your territory, the mother tree will enjoy your world inch by inch. You won't have any chance. Do you want to reconsider my previous suggestion?" Heart Tree King continued.

Han Xiao did not say anything. He turned around and responded with a slash.

Heart Tree King hurriedly dodged but was still grazed by the psionic energy. The psychic barrier shattered, and another World Tree root broke.

"Hehe, looks like your stance is very firm…"

Heart Tree King smiled on the surface, but his heart was filled with fear. He already had the intention to retreat.

After this exchange, he realized that he was no match for this outsider. Just a bunch of powerful Apostle Weapons was enough to deal with him. His internal injuries were burning.

If this continues, I'm afraid I'll really die here. The other Beyond Grade As will probably have the time to make a move soon. It's time to retreat…

Heart Tree King thought to himself.

Many of the World Tree powerhouses had already been sacrificed because there were more Beyond Grade As present. Heart Tree King knew that the rate of casualties on his side would only snowball. Before long, there would be other Beyond Grade As coming to help this outsider deal with him, and it would be difficult for him to leave.

Although he was prepared to die here, the Exchange tactic had already taken effect. There was no need to continue fighting. It was best to preserve his life.

Having made up his mind, Heart Tree King no longer bombarded Han Xiao with chats. He immediately changed his strategy and attempted to break out of the encirclement of Han Xiao's mechanical army.

Sensing the change in Heart Tree King's actions, Han Xiao's eyes flickered.

"He finally wants to escape. It seems like he has used up most of his energy. We can execute the plan now!"

Han Xiao immediately gave a direct order to the combat artificial intelligence, and the mechanical army immediately surrounded and intercepted Heart Tree King, adjusting the weak points of the encirclement to guide Heart Tree King's movement.

At the same time, he sent a message to Heart Tree King.

"You will die here today!"

This time, it was Heart Tree King who turned a deaf ear. He focused on avoiding the focus fire of the mechanical army and quickly found the weakness to break through.

After Han Xiao shouted, he stared at the change in formation. Seeing that Heart Tree King was slowly being forced into a suitable position, his Mechanical Force flashed.

Buzz!

A Lord's Avatar wrapped in Mechanical Force suddenly shot out from the Mechanical Deity and flew toward Heart Tree King.

Sensing the impending danger, Heart Tree King suddenly turned his head and concentrated his psychic energy on this Lord's Avatar. If it was hit, it would surely be sent flying.

However, at this very second, a golden energy suddenly gushed out from the Lord's Avatar's body. Its entire body seemed to have turned into a golden chariot that pressed forward with indomitable will. It instantly shattered the psychic energy and was not affected at all. It locked onto Heart Tree King and charged forward with rapidly increasing speed.

"Hmm?"

Heart Tree King was a little surprised. He controlled the last World Tree Root to block it, but it was knocked away by the Lord's Avatar. It could not even slow it down.

Seeing this, Han Xiao, who was still inside the Mechanical Deity's body, could not help but clench his fists.

His main body was right in front of him, but he had used the Lord's Descent. Naturally, it was to capture Heart Tree King alive. For this, he did not hesitate to activate two Character Summon Cards—Silver Shadow's [Comet Rush], Oulou's [Golden Treasure Ship—Ram]!

The former was an endless acceleration, while the latter was a domineering state that was immune to any crowd control!

Success and failure depended on this. Han Xiao was betting that Heart Tree King would not self-destruct before he got close!

The warnings in Heart Tree King's mind became more and more obvious, and he hurriedly retreated. However, the speed of the Lord's Avatar's charge became faster and faster, and with the mechanical army around restraining him, the distance between the two sides rapidly shortened. In the blink of an eye, there was only a small portion left.

As the Lord's Avatar rapidly expanded in his vision, thoughts flashed through Heart Tree King's mind one after another, and the thought of self-destructing immediately surfaced in his mind.

However, he had many things to think about, and he tried to figure out Han Xiao's intentions. In moments of urgency, he could not be as resolute as the simple-minded Subduing Tree King.

In that moment of hesitation, the Lord's Avatar wrapped in golden energy crashed into him. Its biological muscles expanded instantly.

Heart Tree King only felt a strong force wrapping around his body. Not only was he unable to move, but even the cells in his body were being suppressed. He was shocked.

This is… a Pugilist's forced crowd control skill ‽

"It hit!"

Han Xiao clenched his fists in excitement.

To complement this move, he had specially tested a batch of lord bodies that were specialized in close combat. They were able to withstand his Strength and Endurance attributes to the maximum, allowing the [Azure Dragon Bind] to unleash even greater power!

However, Heart Tree King's strength and endurance were far inferior to that of a Pugilist. After the duration of the forced crowd control, he would not be able to escape so quickly.

At the same time that Heart Tree King was hit, the mechanical army around him was already prepared and released force fields to cover him, stacking many crowd control methods.

"Hila!"

Han Xiao shouted.

At this moment, a beam of light flashed past the mechanical army not far away from Heart Tree King. Hila suddenly appeared beside an Apostle Weapon that was carrying a throne. A bright red 'Dead Sea' instantly spread out.

The next moment, Hila's body sank into the 'Dead Sea' and appeared beside Heart Tree King in the blink of an eye. She held the Spacetime Amber and pressed it toward Heart Tree King.

The Spacetime Amber flashed, and the frozen spacetime quickly expanded, enveloping the immobile Heart Tree King and the Lord's Avatar.

Heart Tree King's eyes widened, but he could not even speak.

His encounter was transmitted through the mental network, and the fleets around him immediately turned their cannons around to fire at him. The World Tree experts scattered all over the place were shocked, and they retreated at the same time, charging madly in the direction of Heart Tree King.

"Crap!"

Fortitude Tree King's heart skipped a beat. He could not be bothered to deal with the enemy and turned around to reinforce Heart Tree King. However, a large part of the thrusters on his back was shattered by Herberlon's blade slash.

Han Xiao had already distanced himself from the battlefield, leaving Heart Tree King alone. There was no way the Beyond Grade As of the World Tree could arrive quickly.

Under the shocked, horrified, and disbelieving gazes, a new Spacetime Amber ball took shape, freezing Heart Tree King's shocked expression.

Hila stared at the shocked Heart Tree King in the amber.

"You hurt my sister, stay here forever!"

Chapter 1362: Fortitude Tree King: I'll Take Over Your Water Pot!

Heart Tree King was locked in a strange position by the Lord's Avatar, and they were trapped in the Spacetime Amber. Time seemed to have stopped, and this world-famous painting was seen by all the Beyond Grade As on both sides.

The Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations were overjoyed.

"Black Star has succeeded!"

"Beautiful! That Tree King did not have the time to self-destruct!"

"Support them with all your might! Don't let those enemies harass Black Star!"

The morale of the Beyond Grade As was greatly boosted, and they were no longer in low spirits for losing their healer. They launched ferocious attacks at the World Tree experts who were anxious to leave the battle.

The emotions of all the World Tree experts were the exact opposite. Their rapidly changing expressions were filled with shock and anger.

They could not be bothered to fight with the opponent and rushed toward Han Xiao like crazy, trying to snatch Heart Tree King back.

However, the moment Han Xiao succeeded, he controlled the Mechanical Deity to move again. He grabbed the Spacetime Amber ball and swallowed it into his body, taking back the Spacetime Amber in Hila's hands.

Without another word, he used his mechanical army as a shield to block the attacks of the World Tree fleet around him. He then flew in the opposite direction at full speed and stopped fighting. His goal was to retreat from the battlefield.

To lure the three Universal Civilizations into deploying their high-level combatants, Heart Tree King naturally would not stay too deep into the World Tree fleet. The battle zone was located at the periphery of the fleet and even if the World Tree fleet wanted to intercept Han Xiao, they would not be able to do so. Han Xiao paid the price of groups of mechanical soldiers and quickly entered the battle zone at the center of the battlefield.

The many World Tree Supers could not care less and surrounded Han Xiao in groups, trying to hinder his return. However, the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations that were chasing after them all acted as cover for Han Xiao, restraining one opponent after another. The energy waves that flashed when they fought lit up continuously around Han Xiao, creating a path.

Fortitude Tree King was entangled with Herberlon again, and violent vibrations were transmitting through his body. He also wanted to support Heart Tree King, but could not get rid of Herberlon and could not increase his speed at all. He could only watch Han Xiao's figure get further and further away. He was so angry that his energy core almost overloaded.

"D*mn idiot! Even Subduing Tree King is smarter than you!"

Fortitude Tree King was furious. They had clearly achieved a huge success in the Exchange tactic, so it would have been fine to retreat. At the very least, they could self-destruct and die. He did not expect them to be defeated at the last moment. It was supposed to be a great victory without much loss, but now, it had become a real 'Exchange'!

He had already cursed Heart Tree King's eighteen generations of ancestors in his heart. Just because he had thought for too long at that last moment, Heart Tree King did not self-destruct and was captured. This was a fatal mistake that even Subduing Tree King did not make. He was the shame of the Tree Kings!

What happened next could only be decided by Ancestral Tree King!

Seeing that Han Xiao was about to return to the fleet of the three Universal Civilizations, Fortitude Tree King knew that there was nothing he could do. His eyes flashed sharply as he sent a command in the mental network:

"Everyone, stop chasing. Retreat! Stop fighting!"

Now that Heart Tree King had been captured alive, Fortitude Tree King was the only one in charge. He took over the leadership without hesitation and ordered all the Beyond Grade As to retreat.

One Tree King was already gone, he was worried that Han Xiao would continue to seal more experts, so he decided to give up and ordered everyone to leave the battle.

Upon hearing the order, the World Tree experts who were chasing Han Xiao paused slightly. They looked at Han Xiao's back that was getting smaller and smaller, but they still chose to follow the orders of the Tree King and stopped their pursuit. While dealing with the Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations, they quickly retreated to the World Tree fleet.

The battleships in the distance also began to provide remote support to help them escape from their opponents.

The Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations did not chase after them too deeply. Instead, they chased for a while and killed a few World Tree experts who were exposed due to the sudden change of plan. Then, under the leadership of the association members, all the Beyond Grade As retreated and did not dare follow the remaining World Tree experts into the enemy fleet. If they did that, they would be the ones in danger instead.

Seeing this, Herberlon did not dare continue fighting alone. He fought fiercely with the Tree King a few times before gradually moving toward his teammates. After escaping from the battle, his eyes—flashing with Mechanical Force—locked onto the Tree King, filled with killing intent as though he was saying, "I'll teach you a lesson the next time we meet."

Fortitude Tree King took a deep look at this familiar face and did not say anything. He took the World Tree powerhouses and retreated deep into the World Tree fleet. Starships moved over and formed layers of barriers, blocking the sight of Herberlon and the others.

As the remaining Beyond Grade As of the World Tree retreated, the battle between the high-level combatants on both sides came to an end. The members of the association and the direct descendants did not stay on the battlefield. They went back to the three Universal Civilizations' fleet while bracing the merciless firing.

Everyone put away their weapons and returned to the temporary command ship at the back of the battlefield. As soon as they entered the command room, they noticed Han Xiao, Hila, and the others were already there. The remote projections of Simon and the many commanders were also gathered there, pointing at Heart Tree King's Spacetime Amber and talking.

"…Black Star, our front line of defense can't hold on any longer, and the other war zones are also showing signs of collapse. The World Tree breaking through the interception circle is already set in stone. We are currently mobilizing our troops to retreat, but this isn't your problem. You did very well by capturing a Tree King."

Simon's tone was low.

"I should have dealt with the Tree King Halo much earlier…" Han Xiao sighed.

"Although that would have been helpful, from the way the World Tree is attacking, it can only slightly delay them from breaking through the blockade. At most, the first to fall wouldn't be this war zone but the other defense lines."

Simon shook his head and said with a helpless tone. However, he was not angry. After a month of fighting, the entire command level had already mentally prepared themselves for the worst—for the interception circle to be broken.

"What do we do next?"

"There's no need for you to continue fighting. Return to the main base first. We will begin evacuating in batches. The World Tree's goal is not just to break through the intercepting perimeter but also to clean up our troops. Since the defense line has been broken, the trend will be difficult to reverse. There's no need to fight them head-on. We will use the various fortifications that we have built in the strategic depth of the rear for the past year to cover fire and harass them into slowing down. I…"

"You guys can decide the matters of the army." Han Xiao waved his hand.

Simon nodded and turned to look at the wounded Beyond Grade As. He changed the topic and said, "Everyone, please tabulate the damage. We need accurate data."

Hearing this, the Beyond Grade As sized each other up and began telling their names. The number of people had decreased by a lot compared to when they went to fight. Many of them had died in the intense battle, with the direct Beyond Grade As suffering the most casualties, as well as some Revivors. The number of casualties among the association members was relatively low.

Because the number of participants this time had increased quite a lot, the World Tree had lost even more people. The three Universal Civilizations, on the other hand, were in a far better state. However, the World Tree did not bring out all their high-level combatants. In terms of numbers, the number of participants was only a fifth or a quarter of the total.

However, although they had the upper hand in terms of battle losses, it was still much worse than the previous battle. Many familiar faces disappeared, and the Beyond Grade As present could not even muster any emotions. They were still immersed in the battle and could not extricate themselves from it. They still had lingering fears and felt like they had just survived a disaster. The atmosphere was like a dark cloud.

"The losses this time are not small," Sun Hunter muttered. "I think we should have retreated when Aurora was defeated…"

Hearing his soft voice, many Beyond Grade As nodded in agreement. They looked at Han Xiao with complicated emotions—helplessness, understanding, dissatisfaction, and resentment.

If they did not capture Heart Tree King this time, they would have suffered a huge loss. However, they had at least gained something and did not return empty-handed. Although many Beyond Grade As still felt that they had suffered a loss, they felt more or less comforted when they saw Heart Tree King in the amber.

Although they were unhappy, they could not say anything. After all, Han Xiao had captured a Tree King and made a huge contribution. At most, they felt that it was not worth it to exchange so many people for one opponent.

Han Xiao casually glanced at them. He knew what they were thinking, but he did not explain.

He had originally wanted to see if he could manipulate the scene and make some Revivors die in battle, but now that Aurora had fallen, although his losses had increased tremendously, it made it easier for him to act. He did not need to press Aurora to make a 'mistake' as he had planned.

These dead Revivors would be the best evidence to prove the truth of the Sanctum Revival. He was not sad at all; instead, he was relieved. It would have been troublesome if no Revivors died in this battle.

After listening to the war casualties of the Beyond Grade As, Simon sighed and shook his head.

"The direct descendants have suffered heavy casualties. No matter what, most of the victims still have a chance to revive in the Sanctum. Thank you for your hard work."

Everyone was in a bad mood and could not be bothered with him. They turned to look at Hila. They were most concerned about Aurora's situation.

"How's your sister?"

"The seal is a little thicker than before, and it will take some time to unseal it. Everyone, let's not delay any further. Let's rest for a while and start. We can be at ease if she wakes up as soon as possible," Hila said with a deep voice.

"That's right. Those with psychic abilities come out. While we're retreating, wake Aurora up."

Kasuyi stepped out from the crowd and released his psychic energy to enter Aurora's mind space. He then started to bombard the thought seal purple crystal in her mind.

Many Psychics, Mages, and Espers walked out one after another and worked together to speed up the process. With so many people working together, the thought seal was getting thinner at a visible rate. At this rate, it would be completely unsealed in a few hours.

Seeing this, Han Xiao turned to look at Heart Tree King in the amber. He remembered that Heart Tree King had used a leaf-shaped Universal Treasure to activate the Illusion - Mind Lock. That was probably one of the rare items that the World Tree grew, and it was hidden in Heart Tree King's body.

However, Han Xiao had no intention of unsealing the amber in the short term and temporarily suppressed his curiosity.

World Tree Territory, Tree King Palace.

The executives who did not participate in the battle found out about the situation from the mental network, and their faces were filled with shock and doubt. They were prepared for Heart Tree King to die in battle, but they did not expect him to be captured alive by the enemy with that strange sealing method, and they were all terrified.

Seated on the throne, Fortitude Tree King slowly opened his eyes and deactivated the Lord's Descent state. A rare look of anger appeared on his face, and he slapped the armrest of his chair heavily.

"Humph, Heart Tree King, so useless!"

As soon as he said that, the roots on the two thrones beside him suddenly rose, and two figures with different appearances appeared.

"Hehe, it seems like the enemy this time is indeed very difficult to deal with. Of the five Great Tree Kings, one is dead, and the other is captured. Now, only three can fight. You're right, Heart Tree King and Subduing Tree King are both useless." One of them turned his head and looked over with a sneer of disdain. "However, you're not much better. Your Lord's Avatar was clearly present, but you didn't save Heart Tree King."

Fortitude Tree King glanced at him coldly and snorted. "Secret Tree King, I can't be bothered to argue with you, but you better watch your words."

"Heh." Secret Tree King did not think much of it. He did not even care about Fortitude Tree King. Among the five tree kings, he did not like anyone other than Ancestral Tree King.

"Humph, I can't be bothered to argue with you." Fortitude Tree King turned to look at Ancestral Tree King in the middle seat and asked, "What do we do next? What do you think?"

The aura of Ancestral Tree King was the opposite of the other four tree kings. He was like an ordinary person, lacking any sense of presence. Be it his appearance or physique, there was nothing special. If one did not pay attention, they might subconsciously ignore him.

Hearing this, Ancestral Tree King said slowly without any expression.

"I've already tried. Heart Tree King is completely isolated from the outside world, and the mother tree can't take back his Tree King Crown. This means unless he's unsealed, I can't remove his position and replace him with a new tree king. Therefore, we must try to save him. At the very least, we have to take back his Tree King Crown. Otherwise, we won't be able to make the Tree God descend completely."

Hearing this, the faces of Fortitude Tree King and Secret Tree King turned solemn.

Initially, they had thought that Heart Tree King killed a lot of high-level enemy combatants by himself. Although it had become a real Exchange, it was worse for the enemy. However, if they could not retrieve the Tree King Crown, it would be troublesome.

The identities of the tree kings all came from the 'Tree King Crown'. This was a special ability given by the mother tree. Like the Apostle Weapons, there was a limited quota. The quota was only five, and it had to be five different Super systems. Other than Ancestral Tree King occupying one quota, the other four Tree King Crown positions had been changed over the years.

Only by gathering five crowns would they be able to make Tree God descend completely. This was their trump card.

"Then what should we do?" Fortitude Tree King asked.

"There's no need to worry for the time being," Ancestral Tree King said casually. "The civilization on the other side has yet to show the strength that would require us to use the Tree God's Descent. Heart Tree King is only sealed, so there's no danger. We have two paths now. One is to wait. The enemy might be interested in studying a Tree King. As long as we unlock that special seal, I can retrieve the Tree King crown.

The second is to send someone to rescue him. Although the mother tree's connection with him has been cut off, the broken connection can still point in his direction. We can organize high-level combatants to snatch him back."

"Then let's just wait and see when these enemies can't take it anymore." Fortitude Tree King snorted.

"Hmm, I think so too."

Ancestral Tree King nodded and continued.

"Although we have broken the enemy's interception circle, we still need to move forward to the enemy's territory. Just let the fleet carry out this task. There's no need for high-level combatants, so there won't be any opportunities to attack.

"Furthermore… Although we know the direction, the distance is unknown. We don't know how long it will take to reach the enemy's territory. It might take a few years or decades. However, according to the enemy's reaction, the distance shouldn't be too far."

The other two nodded silently.

"Also, Heart Tree King is gone. Someone needs to continue managing the daily affairs of this place." Ancestral Tree King turned to look at Fortitude Tree King and said slowly, "You shall do it."

Fortitude Tree King's face fell.

God knew how many years it would take for the fleet to arrive at the other party's territory. He did not want to keep showing himself. He wanted to slack off, but he did not dare go against Ancestral Tree King, so he could only agree in a muffled voice.

After casually instructing him on a few things to take note of, Ancestral Tree King's figure quickly faded and returned to the mother tree. Secret Tree King took a gloating glance at Fortitude Tree King and left, leaving only Fortitude Tree King on the throne.

"You want me to work? Fat chance."

Fortitude Tree King snorted, rolled his eyes, and came up with a plan.

By the way, the seed of Subduing Tree King should almost be ripe. When he revives, I can transfer this job to him. Anyway, that iron head is very hardworking and is willing to do this hard work. I can continue to slack!

As soon as he thought of this, Fortitude Tree King could not wait to see Subduing Tree King reincarnate in front of him.

He could not help but stand up and walk out of the palace. He inherited the glorious legacy of Heart Tree King and went out to water Subduing Tree King.

Chapter 1363: Spring Dream Vanishes Without a Trace and The Final Preparation

Han Xiao and the others retreated from the battlefield and returned to the main base at the rear. The World Tree Army had yet to break through to here, and it was not affected by the flames of war.

The troops of the three Universal Civilizations and the various large organizations had already formed a long line. They entered different Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices and returned to the explored universe.

The group boarded an evacuating main ship and watched the real-time surveillance of the battlefield while waiting for their turn.

The three Universal Civilizations had already begun to withdraw their forces and stop their losses. The battlefront formed by the starships retreated like a tide.

Kant looked at it for a while before shaking his head. "Looks like the three Universal Civilizations have completely decided to give up on the intercepting circle."

"Fighting to the death is useless. It will only increase our casualties, so we naturally have to retreat," Manison said calmly.

"However, once we retreat, we won't be able to stop the World Tree from approaching our territory. Sooner or later, we'll have to start a war on our own territory."

Clotti shook his head. Ever since Reeve and the others had revived, he had become more talkative and rarely acted as if he was unapproachable.

The group casually chatted about the battle to calm their emotions from the bloody battle earlier.

However, Han Xiao did not join their conversation. Instead, he stood aside and watched the unsealing of Aurora.

After watching for a while, he suddenly realized that many Beyond Grade As were sweating. He could not help but ask:

"How's the progress?"

"This is strange." Kasuyi pinched his forehead and said with a surprised tone, "We have already weakened the seal by more than 95%, leaving only the last thin layer. However, we encountered an unprecedented resistance, and the last bit of the seal crystal wall suddenly became indestructible, as if there is an infinite power supporting its existence."

"Really?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and immediately thought of the characteristics of the Illusion - Mind Lock.

It seemed like the target who was hit by this move would be trapped in a dream created by their desire. The more real they treated it as, the stronger the seal would be.

He took a closer look at Aurora. As the layers of the seal were broken, her expression was no longer blank. At this moment, she closed her eyes, frowned, and revealed a slight look of pain, as though she was saying, "Don't disturb my daydream."

Could it be that her subconscious had sensed that the dream was about to disappear, so she took the illusion more seriously and took the initiative to stabilize the seal and resist the unsealers?

What kind of dream did she have to make this woman wish she could sleep forever?

Han Xiao's mouth twitched, and he looked away helplessly. He patted Kasuyi and said, "Then can you unseal it or not?"

"Don't worry about that. Although the seal barrier is much stronger, with so many of us working together, we will be able to penetrate it sooner or later." Kasuyi did not even look back.

Han Xiao could only trust him and wait patiently.

After a while, Kasuyi and the others suddenly heaved a sigh of relief. They were just about to say that they had succeeded.

However, before they could say anything, Aurora suddenly opened her eyes and woke up from her coma.

"No—"

The sharp shout shocked everyone. Even the Beyond Grade As who were analyzing the situation not far away stopped chatting and looked over in surprise.

It was originally a happy matter for the milkmaid to wake up, but everyone was shocked by this shout and was confused.

Seeing pairs of shocked eyes staring at her, Aurora snapped out of her daze and quickly shut her mouth. However, her expression was still a little dazed, as though she had not gotten used to the feeling of leaving the dream. She was trying to determine if this was real or an illusion.

However, her senses and memories gradually adjusted, and Aurora slowly confirmed that she had really woken up this time.

This time, Han Xiao walked out from the crowd and stood in front of Aurora. He touched her head and said with concern, "Your mind seal has been removed. How do you feel?"

Aurora looked up at Han Xiao, and her delicate face suddenly turned red. She quickly turned her head to the side and looked away.

"I'm fine… How are you?"

"What problem can I have?" Han Xiao saw her strange expression and could not help but be curious. "What did you dream about in the seal?"

"I… I…"

Aurora stuttered as if she did not want to speak.

This time, Hila walked over and patted her head.

"What did you dream about? Why aren't your memories open to me?"

"D-don't ask! Anyway, it's nothing important…"

Aurora glanced at Hila before looking away in shock. She then recalled what she had experienced in the dream, and her face became even redder, as though she was about to bleed.

Seeing her strange behavior, Han Xiao and Hila exchanged surprised looks.

However, since Aurora did not want to say it, they could not be bothered to force her. Since she was already awake, there was no need to dig into the details. Perhaps it was because she had a secret in her heart, and it was not convenient for her to say it.

Han Xiao poked Aurora and checked her status. Seeing that Aurora's attributes had returned to normal, he did not bother about Aurora's dream.

Seeing this, everyone stepped forward to show their concern, pushing Han Xiao and Hila to the side.

Aurora's emotions gradually returned to normal, but she still did not dare look Han Xiao in the eye. Suddenly, she thought of something and asked with a serious expression, "You're all here. Has the battle ended? How are the casualties?"

As soon as she finished speaking, everyone's expression stiffened slightly, and they sighed. The atmosphere quickly became gloomy, and they started to talk about the battle situation after she fainted.

Hearing about the losses this time, Aurora was shocked. Then, she said with some guilt and disappointment:

"I—I'm sorry. I was careless and fell for the enemy's trick. I could not be of use, and more people died…"

"It's not your fault. It's all the enemy's doing. You're just a victim." Han Xiao rubbed her head, and her soft blonde hair slid across his palm.

"But if the enemy uses this move again, I will…"

Han Xiao waved his hand and interrupted her. He smiled and said, "Don't be afraid. The Tree King who attacked you has already been locked in Amber. He won't threaten you anymore."

"You're still so nice to me… cough cough."

Aurora subconsciously opened her mouth, but halfway through, she suddenly remembered that this was not a dream. She quickly shut her mouth, lowered her head, and coughed to hide the abnormal emotions in her eyes.

However, no one paid attention to her expression.

"It's all thanks to Black Star capturing that Tree King. If they sealed Aurora in the next battle, we would have suffered heavy casualties like today." Milizaus shook his head.

Guzar sighed softly. "From this point of view, it's already not bad that Black Star got rid of the future trouble. It's just a pity for those comrades who sacrificed themselves…"

"You can't say that. Since the enemy has this method, they will use it sooner or later, so our casualties are inevitable. When the enemy used this method for the first time, Black Star seized the opportunity to capture him. He has already done his best to minimize the cost to prevent losses in the future," Beiger immediately said.

Hearing this, everyone thought about it and felt that it made sense.

This was the enemy's trump card, and Black Star couldn't prevent them from using it in advance, so they could not blame Black Star. Getting rid of this hidden danger the first time was already the best outcome.

Ames walked forward and patted Aurora's head.

"It's good that you're fine. This is more important than anything else."

"Teacher, I'm… very sorry."

Aurora lowered her head timidly. Her face was red with guilt, and she did not dare to look up.

Ames, however, understood her and comforted her. "It's alright, don't blame yourself. Although you did not use your ability to protect me, it's not your fault. I'm fine."

"Hmm…"

Hearing this, Aurora felt even more embarrassed. She twisted her hands together and buried her head even deeper, almost like an ostrich.

It was finally their turn to leave, and everyone stopped chatting.

The spaceship followed the fleet into the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, and the two huge mechanical rings began to spin. The lights connected and flickered, sending everyone back to the Flickering World.

After Han Xiao and the others retreated from the battlefield, the situation developed just as Simon had said. The defensive lines of the various war zones were broken, and the World Tree Army marched in from various areas and spread out rapidly. A vicious snowball-like cycle occurred, and the intercepting circle gradually became riddled with holes.

As there was no way to reverse the situation, the three Universal Civilizations did not continue to recruit Beyond Grade As into the battle and did not force a direct confrontation. They continued to pull their troops and equipment to recoup their costs so that they would not be completely wiped out by the World Tree fleet.

This process lasted for about ten days before the World Tree Army completely broke through the intercepting circle. The three Universal Civilizations also withdrew all the fleets and equipment that should have been taken back, and those that could not be taken away were destroyed on the spot. The intercepting circle that had been built over a year was only left with countless metal trash floating in the universe like a man-made asteroid belt.

In the explored universe, the upper echelons of the three Universal Civilizations and the command center held a follow-up battle meeting after the interception circle disappeared.

Among all the Beyond Grade As, only Han Xiao was the representative.

In the large conference room, the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations listened to the military report with a straight face. As the commander-in-chief of the intercepting circle, Simon was reading out the strategic analysis.

"…The intercepting circle has been abolished. We have lost the biggest barrier stopping the World Tree from advancing. The war has entered a new phase.

In the past year, we have sent out teams of engineers to move toward the Flickering World from the interception circle, setting up traps and fortifications along the way for this day. When the World Tree moves toward our territory and enters the vast strategic zone, we can harass and obstruct them.

"Although we can't stop them from advancing, we can at least slow them down…"

At this moment, Marbruce interrupted him, tapped the table, and asked:

"This won't solve the root of the problem. Can you think of a way to build another blockade?"

Hearing this, Simon shook his head and sighed.

"Forgive me for being blunt, but before we find the World Tree's main body, all our strategies are just to treat the symptoms… We need to invest a lot of resources to build another intercepting circle. I believe that with this experience, the World Tree will use the same method to attack next time. Our troops will be heavily damaged once again, and we will fall right into their trap.

Furthermore, choosing a location is also a problem. Most of the areas in this strategic zone are also places that we have never set foot in, so we cannot go there casually. The earliest construction team to set out will only be able to build a new interception circle a year away from the World Tree. The time is too tight.

If we send a new batch of construction teams from the border of the Flickering World, there will be plenty of time to build an intercepting circle, but…"

"But what?"

Louis asked.

Simon frowned and told the truth, "The Military Strategy Department does not agree with this plan. Through the speed and drifting time of the Kunde Race survivors, we have already calculated the approximate distance between the World Tree and us. With their speed, it will take them about eleven years to reach our territory. With our obstruction and delay, this number will be extended, but not for long."

The Pope immediately questioned.

"Eleven years… This is enough to build a stronger interception circle. Why not?"

"It can be done, but the Military Strategy Department feels that it's a better choice to strengthen defenses in the border areas. Use destructive methods to develop the Flickering World border that has yet to be fully explored, squeeze out all the planet resources in these areas, and then turn at least five Star Clusters into desolate universe belts. We will not leave a single hair behind for the World Tree and build a defense line here.

After all, this is our home ground. This way, it would not only make it easier for mobile support troops but also greatly reduce the size of the defensive line, saving the expenditure of troops. Furthermore, the battlefield is close to our home, which can also stimulate the resistance of the entire universe.

Setting up a new blockade in the unexplored area countless miles away will consume too much of our forces. We will be dragged into a war of attrition that the World Tree is good at, which will be even more disadvantageous…"

Simon explained.

Hearing this, the upper echelons discussed the pros and cons of this plan.

The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations pondered for a while before turning to look at Han Xiao.

"Black Star, what do you think?"

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "I don't have too many opinions, but it's very necessary to strengthen our defenses. Instead of leaving those planets for the World Tree to devour, we might as well do our best and use the Planetary Shatterer to develop the planets at the border of the Flickering World so that the enemies can't replenish themselves. That way, even if they attack, we won't lose much."

He had already done what he could. Compared to the terrible start in his previous life, the situation of the three Universal Civilizations at present was many times better. He could not give any more suggestions regarding the war.

After all, the direction of the war between the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree was completely different from his previous life, and he could not be sure of the final direction of each plan. The best choice now was to trust the professional military personnel.

'In eleven years at the minimum, the World Tree will be able to invade the three Universal Civilizations… This is the final preparation period, I have to make good use of it.'

Han Xiao took a deep breath.

On the advancing route of the World Tree, the three Universal Civilizations most likely did not need high-level combatants to harass or stop them. This meant that they, as Beyond Grade As, did not have to be on standby all the time and could freely arrange the schedule.

He planned to spend some time nurturing those Beyond Grade A seeds, hoping to give birth to more Beyond Grade As and allow Karlot to grow as soon as possible.

On the other hand, he could also take the opportunity to settle down. The experience provided by the players would surely be enough for him to break through level 360 and complete his Promotion within a year.

The strongest period of a Mechanic was not when they had just advanced.

The peak of a Mechanic could only be achieved after his mechanical army and equipment are completely upgraded!

The last eleven years of preparation were a rare opportunity for him to digest his advanced strength!

After these two exchanges with the Tree King, Han Xiao had already noticed his current weakness. Although he could win against Heart Tree King or Subduing Tree King in a one-on-one battle, they were all experts of the same level. They had their own explosive trump cards, so it was almost impossible for him to defeat the other party quickly. Furthermore, the battlefield environment was complicated, and the mechanical army was the biggest target. There were too many factors that affected their combat strength.

Although his energy level was very high, he was still a peak Beyond Grade A in essence, and there was no qualitative change. Only with the power of sublimation could he solve this problem.

"I hope I can give the World Tree a 'surprise' the next time we fight!"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

However, these thoughts were suppressed in his heart.

He knew very well that the most important task at the moment was not these plans but to wait for Oathkeeper to gather the new Sanctum Key and enter the Sanctum again. He would use the truth of the revival to strengthen the belief of the entire Beyond Grade A group!

Chapter 1364: Determination and Shadow

The three Universal Civilizations would not deliberately publicize the failure of the intercepting circle, but the truth could not be hidden for long either. As the troops of the various large organizations retreated to the explored universe, this news quickly spread to the galactic society that was constantly paying attention to the battle situation, causing a large-scale panic.

For more than a year, the refugees who had migrated to the Central Galaxy from all over the world were used to the successive reports of the World Tree stopping them from entering the Central Galaxy. This was also the reason why many people felt that forcing them to take refuge was worth it. They had already treated the intercepting circle as a 'border' to block the enemies.

As long as they could intercept the World Tree, they would have a sense of security. They thought that this barrier would be able to stop the World Tree forever, preventing the flames of war from spreading to their area.

However, now that this barrier had been broken by the enemy, people's confidence had been taken away. The chain reaction was shocking. Not only did it cause fear and panic, but it also caused their trust in the three Universal Civilizations to plummet.

In the eyes of the galactic residents, the three Universal Civilizations were nigh-omnipotent 'kings'. However, even with such powerful rulers working together, they still failed to defeat the enemy. Although there were many factors involved, in the eyes of ordinary people, this was like a math equation of 3 < 1, which meant that the three Universal Civilizations were no match for the one enemy!

Many people were willing to accept the forced migration because they believed that the three Universal Civilizations would eventually be able to repel the invaders. However, if the three Universal Civilizations could not defeat the invaders, would it really be safe for them to stay in the Central Galaxy and seek refuge? Wouldn't they be waiting for death?

This thought spread like a virus in the hearts of the galactic residents, nourishing their unease, panic, and fear. Even if the public relations department of the three Universal Civilizations works themselves to the bone, the overflowing emotions were like a tsunami that could not be easily blocked.

Thus, chaos erupted.

There were many cases of people trying to escape from the Sanctuary planets. Some of them were no longer willing to believe the three Universal Civilizations and felt that staying behind was equivalent to waiting for death. They wanted to 'save' themselves before the enemy attacked, wanting to escape from the explored universe in spaceships.

In the face of life and death, the refugees, who were originally akin to docile sheep under the control of the three Universal Civilizations, suddenly displayed a sense of herd mentality resistance. The difficulty of managing them suddenly spiked, and the three Universal Civilizations had no choice but to divert more energy to comfort and suppress the refugees.

All of a sudden, chaos ensued.

In his previous life, the foreign enemies had charged in with a fierce momentum, and there was no way for the people to retreat. Now that the three Universal Civilizations had the time to prepare for war, citizens were given an option. There were pros and cons to this and they would not be able to achieve a state where everyone was a soldier like in Han Xiao's previous life.

At the Beyond Grade A Association headquarters…

Due to the large-scale deployment of the three Universal Civilizations' troops, many Beyond Grade A organizations decided to change the location of the association's headquarters. This planet located in the middle of the Flickering World had already been moved to Black Star's territory.

Ever since a large number of Beyond Grade As had rushed to the frontlines, the Beyond Grade A Association had entered a hiatus. Han Xiao and the other participants had returned to the association, and after a year or so, they once again convened a full meeting.

In the round table conference room, many association members were gathered. Compared to the seats that were full before the battle, there were many empty seats. Every empty seat represented a sacrifice.

"… to summarize, in at least 11 years, the World Tree will invade the mainland and reach the border of the Flickering World…"

Han Xiao's tone was low as he recounted the outcome of the battle conference he had with the three Universal Civilizations.

Hearing this information, all the Beyond Grade As present had solemn expressions.

"11 years is too soon…"

A Beyond Grade A could not help but speak with a worried tone.

In the eyes of a Beyond Grade A, this amount of time would pass in the blink of an eye.

The shocking attack of the World Tree breaking through the intercepting circle left a deep impression on the participants. When they thought about how the endless green tide would invade their territory soon, like a disaster that devoured everything, covering the entire explored universe bit by bit, everyone subconsciously tensed up and became extremely fearful.

Kasuyi knocked on the table and encouraged, "On the bright side, we still have at least eleven years to prepare. After fighting with the World Tree this year, we have also discovered many of our shortcomings. We can use this opportunity to improve ourselves."

Because he knew the truth about the Sanctums and the Iterations, he had always been a firm believer of the warring faction. He was another pillar of support other than Han Xiao.

However, after he finished speaking, the participants of the battles did not respond like before. They only remained silent, and the members of the Association in the avoidance faction had their differences, and naturally would not show any signs of approval.

Dillon placed his elbows on the table, took in everyone's expressions, and sneered.

"Tsk, I told you long ago that your attitude will change after you experience the war. Now you know that I made the correct choice, right? Look at all of you. You were so passionate when you set off, but now? You were all beaten back by the enemy! You sacrificed so many members of the association but still failed to stop the enemy. Tell me, what's the use of sacrificing these people? It was just a waste of our only chance to revive."

Hearing this, most of the participants clenched their fists and claws. They were clearly enraged, but no one spoke up.

What Dillon said had touched a raw nerve in their hearts. In the galactic battlefield of a hundred billion, many people felt how minuscule they were. Seeing those Beyond Grade As who usually called the shots in the galactic society die one after another, their belief in participating in the battle was shaken.

Seeing this, Han Xiao frowned and heavily spoke out.

"Alright, shut up. At least we managed to cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations and delay the World Tree's invasion for a year."

"Ha, a mere year…"

Dillon curled his lips in disapproval, but he did not dare say anything more under Han Xiao's glare.

Han Xiao did not look at him anymore. He looked at everyone and slowly said, "No matter what, these eleven years is the last preparation period. We can't waste it. I will use the Evolution Cube and a series of Universal Treasures to increase your strength unconditionally. The others who have similar Universal Treasures should do the same. You have all been in the position of 'galactic big shots' for too long. Some of you have not been able to improve for a long time and have already wasted your training. I suggest everyone undergo special training. Be as strong as you can."

"What special training? Who's doing the training?" Kohler was curious.

Han Xiao announced.

"The peak Beyond Grade As of the various systems will all be the mentors, imparting experience and guiding routes. As the Chief Instructor, I will be coordinating all the special training plans. On one hand, we will work towards increasing everyone's individual strengths, and on the other, your capabilities in working as a team.

In addition, this will be live combat training. There's no need to worry about getting injured, as Aurora will be in charge of healing. During times of peace, as the representatives of individual strength, we do not have the chance to fight frequently. Right now, this is no time to care about face or prestige. We have to increase our combat strength as much as possible, thus combat is the best way. Winning or losing is not important, the most crucial thing is to improve our abilities."

He did indeed want to increase the average combat power of the Beyond Grade As, but on the other hand, he also felt that this was a good excuse to find people to spar frequently. He might be able to obtain more abilities.

Hearing this, everyone hesitated but did not object.

At this moment, Secret Master solemnly spoke.

"What if the three Universal Civilizations lose in the end?"

Han Xiao looked downwards, before slowly speaking.

"…I promise all of you that if things don't work out, I won't ask for anything else. I will take all of you out of the explored universe and head to the endless galaxy. Therefore, these eleven years will also be the time for us to move the resources of our Beyond Grade A organizations and prepare for our future."

Han Xiao was uncertain that the three Universal Civilizations would be able to defeat the World Tree. Now that the timeline was different, whether or not they would be able to find the World Tree's main body was a complete mystery. This was still an unknown probability. If they could not find it, the three Universal Civilizations would have almost no chance of winning, thus he had also expected the worst and devised a backup plan for the association.

If the three Universal Civilizations were really done for, he would also abandon this place without mercy. The universe was huge, and there was nowhere he could not go.

The meeting lasted for a while more before everyone dispersed.

After everyone had left, Han Xiao took out his communicator, contacted Oathkeeper, and asked about the progress of the Sanctum Key collection. The priority was still the First Sanctum, and the time flow was the most consistent.

However, Oathkeeper replied that he had yet to gather the materials and would have to wait for some time.

"I hope we can start the second round of recovery as soon as possible. The fighting spirit of the association members has been shaken."

Han Xiao thought to himself.

Many of the revivors felt that they had used up their only chance to revive and would no longer need him in the future, so they did not listen to him. Now, they urgently needed to use the truth to correct these people's thoughts. Only by showing their indispensability would they be able to amplify their words and make the Beyond Grade As rely on him more.

At the same time, the two sisters walked out of the venue one after another.

Suddenly, Hila stopped in her tracks. Aurora, who had her head lowered, bumped into her back as if she did not notice anything. She then regained her senses and looked up in confusion.

"What's wrong with you recently? Ever since the seal on your mind was removed, you've been in a strange state. You've been spacing out all the time, and it was the same during the meeting just now."

Hila turned around and sized Aurora up with a frown.

"I…" Aurora clenched her fists and lowered her head. She hesitated and said," I was just thinking if I was much stronger than now, would these things still have happened?"

"Oh?" Hila raised her brows but did not reply.

Aurora pursed her lips and muttered to herself,

"Black Star once said that my current level is far from being able to unleash the true strength of this Esper Ability. If I become stronger, I can summon more Underworld Spirits at any time. If I become stronger, I will be able to resist the thought seal. If I become stronger, I won't have such comrades dying in battle…"

As she spoke, her voice grew increasingly disappointed and filled with reproach.

"This is all because I'm not strong enough!"

Hila looked at her quietly and waited for her to finish venting her emotions before speaking expressionlessly.

"That's right, it's because you're not strong enough! They're all comforting you, saying that it's not your fault, but in my eyes, it's your problem. If you were at the peak Beyond Grade A level, all the losses in this battle could have been prevented!"

Hearing this, Aurora twisted her fingers and felt even more ashamed.

After becoming a Beyond Grade A a few years ago, she no longer had to be controlled by Black Star and Hila. Her heart was wild, and she felt like she was finally free to do whatever she wanted.

Her Esper Ability could ensure her survival, and she had also inherited the powerful Underworld Spirit. She had also obtained a lot of support from the association members, and she even had the life-saving equipment that Black Star had given her. She had all kinds of trump cards since birth, so she relaxed and stopped training.

Only after this setback did Aurora regret not training hard for the past few years.

Aurora looked up into Hila's eyes, bit her lower lip, and made up her mind.

"Sis, can you give me special training?"

Hila's lips curled up into an almost undetectable smile. She then coldly spoke while holding a straight face,

"Then be prepared. I won't go easy on you."

Secondary dimension world.

This was a space filled with black liquid, like a pitch-black ocean in which one would not be able to see their fingers even if they were stretched out in front of them.

A fleet of spaceships was slowly advancing through it like submarines.

This was one of the earliest divisions that the three Universal Civilizations had sent out. After a year of travel, they had long entered the depths of the secondary dimension and left the shallow areas controlled by the three Universal Civilizations.

In one of the living cabins of the battleship, Harrison was pacing back and forth anxiously while chanting.

"In the main universe, the World Tree has already broken through the three Universal Civilizations' encirclement. If we don't speed up, the enemy will be able to invade our territory in no time… How do we find the thing His Excellency Black Star mentioned?"

Due to the lack of communication in the secondary dimensions, the expedition team could not maintain stable communication with their hometown and could only occasionally report the situation. The last time they exchanged intelligence, the expedition team that Harrison was in received news that the intercepting circle was broken, which made him anxious.

After more than a year of searching, the expedition team search could be called fruitless. They had not even seen a World Tree fleet.

The secondary dimensions were endless. New dimensions were born every second, and the old dimensions were destroyed. The relationship between the secondary dimensions was unpredictable and constantly changing. If there were no specific coordinates, it would be much more difficult to search for something.

"If I try my luck like this, the chances are too low. When will I be able to find clues…"

Harrison clenched his fists. The thought of his hometown being threatened by the invaders made him feel uneasy.

However, Harrison, who was immersed in his emotions, did not notice that there was a huge shadow swimming in the dark sea outside the porthole. It was almost impossible to tell its shape apart in the darkness. The strange thing was that even the radar of the fleet did not detect it.

Chapter 1365: Training and Abnormality

The destruction of the intercepting circle meant that the war had entered a new phase. The World Tree had the coordinates from the Kunde Race refugees. The army left behind temporary strongholds along the way and split into many routes as they headed toward the Flickering World. They were like green roots that grew endlessly in the universe, slowly extending toward the territories of the three Universal Civilizations.

The three Universal Civilizations used their super long-range weapons and harassment tactics to stall the enemy.

The players did not react much to the loss of the interception circle, and their morale was not affected. In their eyes, it was just a normal development of the main storyline. At most, some storyline-loving players would post on the forums to analyze the subsequent war trends, and most of it was just speculation.

The biggest impact was the main storyline mission of the players which was currently in progress. The requirements and the terms of guarding the intercepting circle had been changed to try to stop the World Tree's advance.

However, most of the players were quite happy. The Spacetime Splicing Technology had become useful again. They were able to work after being laid off, and they had many more opportunities to work.

In times of war, mercenaries like the players were the happiest. The reward level of the mission had increased by a few levels, and their wallets were filled up at a few times the speed.

During the harassment phase, the three Universal Civilizations had left a large number of suicide squad positions for the players, which made things easier for the Great Mechanic Han. He did not have to divert his attention to fertilize the players, instead, focusing his attention elsewhere.

Flickering World, Black Star territory.

A huge metal fortress was suspended in the space, it was triangular with a thin magnetic field binding track extending out from each corner. They looked like transparent pipes, but they were actually rapid shuttle corridors connected to crescent-shaped mechanical devices at the end. These three devices were like suction cups, sucking the three Fixed Stars from afar. They were all stars that had been migrated, and after special treatments such as gravitational restraints and energy restraints, they were very stable.

The three crescent-shaped mechanical devices were called Star Guiding devices, which were used to guide the energy of the stars. This was a model used for individual training. It could be used for body tempering, charging, and endurance enhancement by adjusting the output power of the star's energy.

This metal fortress was a specially built training ground. It was equipped with all kinds of top-notch training facilities such as Fixed Star cultivation room for star energy body tempering, environment simulation rooms for converting various cosmic radiation, ultra-high extreme density gravity rooms, and so on. There were also training-type Universal Treasures provided by the three Universal Civilizations and many Beyond Grade As that could stimulate the potential of different races and systems. It could be called the best training ground for Supers in the entire explored universe.

Those who could undergo training here were not ordinary people. More than 95% of the Beyond Grade A seeds in the entire explored universe had been sent here, regardless of whether they were regular people or civilizations' direct members. At the same time, there were also other Calamity Grades with potential that various organizations had selected.

In the open-air square of the training ground, a small crowd had already formed a formation. They looked at the row of figures in front of them with almost fanaticism, and most of their gazes were focused on Han Xiao who was in the center.

"All of you are Calamity Grades. I believe I do not need to explain why you are here. From today onwards, all the facilities here will be provided to you for free. We will set up a training schedule for you, and when we are free, we will discuss the problems you face during your training…"

As Han Xiao spoke, he scanned the crowd before him.

Establishing this training ground was also the intention of the three Universal Civilizations. Originally, the direct descendants had all received training in the various military bases, but now, they had all been sent over by the three Universal Civilizations. The people in front of them were all high-level Calamity Grades, including all the peak Supers in the explored universe below Beyond Grade As.

The purpose of providing the best facilities, the strongest teachers, and the best resources was to produce as many Beyond Grade As as possible in the next eleven years. Facing the suffocating power of the World Tree, the three Universal Civilizations could not care less about the imbalance of Supers.

"Understood!"

Hadavy shouted excitedly, and the hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds who had already joined the Black Star Army immediately echoed. Under their leadership, the people of other organizations also responded.

Han Xiao glanced at him. There were quite a few familiar faces among them, including the Beyond Grade A seeds of the Black Star Army. Lagi, Hadavy, Jotina, Nero, Mia, and the others were among them.

However, not all of the potential individuals participated in the training. Some of the golden leeks that they had high hopes for such as Karlot and Evans, were privately given special treatment.

"However, let's get this straight. All those who become Beyond Grade As in the training camp must participate in the war unconditionally and use it as your tuition fee. Otherwise, we will take back your strength. This is a deal, and it's not too late to back out now."

Hearing this, the excitement on everyone's faces did not change at all. They already knew the price.

However, the value of the training this time was extraordinary. Most of the Beyond Grade A seeds here grew on their own. In the past, there was no such thing as free use of such a treasure, and now they could even ask for help from different Beyond Grade As casually. Even if they joined a Beyond Grade A organization, they would not receive such treatment. Compared to this benefit, joining the battle was nothing.

Just as everyone was getting excited, an odd mutter sounded from the crowd.

"Sigh, I have to sacrifice myself in the war anyway. What's the point of training harder…"

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

The style was too obvious. He did not even have to look to know who was speaking. He immediately emphasized:

"Our training course is compulsory. We will not allow any form of laziness, and we will strictly control the rest time. Some people better pay attention."

"Sigh, totalitarianism…"

The same voice sighed.

Han Xiao ignored Lagi and continued.

"Alright, I won't say anything else. I've already made the corresponding timetable for each of you. These instructors will be in charge of training you. Training starts immediately. From now on, don't waste any second."

As he spoke, the Beyond Grade As beside him took away the Calamity Grades to train them separately.

Some ordinary Beyond Grade As who did not have much room to improve were more passionate about being instructors. As long as they could groom one more comrade, they would be able to share the pressure. Their experience was also precious to Calamity Grades.

"I hope that in eleven years, more than ten Beyond Grade As will be born…"

Han Xiao thought to himself.

Gathering all the potential stocks in the universe to help them grow, there was a chance to produce a double-digit number of Beyond Grade As in eleven years, which was equivalent to a batch of already grown leeks.

With his targeted training, the guidance of Beyond Grade As, and the support of a large number of resources, the probability of a high-level Calamity Grade completing the last step would increase many times.

Watching the group of potential stocks being taken away for training, Han Xiao turned to the other Beyond Grade As and nodded.

"The same goes for us. If you need anything, I can give you some training advice."

There were two groups of people training. One was Calamity Grades, and the other was Beyond Grade As. Of course, the two were different, and he was in charge of the latter.

The Beyond Grade As had been watching from the side the entire time. They looked at each other, feeling a little awkward.

Those who could advance to Beyond Grade A were all geniuses who had found their paths. They had always been exploring their own path of cultivation, and many of them were not used to suddenly receiving guidance from others.

However, Han Xiao's prestige was very high. Everyone present had agreed to the training plan that he had proposed during the regular meeting, so they could not go back on their words now. All of them came up one after another to be poked by Han Xiao.

Han Xiao used this opportunity to collect the information of most Beyond Grade As and analyzed their abilities.

Why do I feel like a Pokemon trainer…

After analyzing for a while, this thought suddenly appeared in Han Xiao's mind.

On the other side, when the Beyond Grade As saw Black Star accurately pointing out their weaknesses and even giving them effective training plans, they could not help but be stunned.

They knew that Black Star had great foresight, but it was all hearsay and not true. Now that they had personally witnessed this, they could not help but be interested.

"You didn't grow so quickly because of this ability, did you?" Oulou was surprised.

"To a certain extent, that's true." Han Xiao shrugged.

"I should give you the title of Super mentor. If you were in the Federation of Light, I might have lost my job," Verena had a helpless expression.

"Don't worry, it's not too late to lose your job."

Han Xiao could not be bothered to speak. After distributing the training plans, he urged everyone to hurry up and cultivate.

Although he really wanted to find someone to spar with and try to draw abilities, the training had just begun, so it was better to let others get used to it first.

The many Beyond Grade As dispersed. This was not their training ground. Han Xiao had modified some planets nearby to serve as a temporary training ground for the Beyond Grade As. In the next eleven years, most of them would move around this area. However, it was only limited to the ordinary Beyond Grade As and some high-level Beyond Grade As. Kasuyi, Manison, Hila, and the others all had their own special training route, so they did not need to come for training.

After doing all this, Han Xiao was about to return to the workshop to continue his research when his communicator suddenly rang. The caller was the department leader in charge of contacting the secondary dimension expedition team.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I have some bad news for you. In our last contact, we discovered that the fleet carrying the emissary you sent out has disappeared. We are currently unable to contact them."

"Missing?"

Han Xiao activated the Observer's Mark.

Before Harrison left, he had used his Void Talent to set up an Observer's Mark on Harrison. Because he had not obtained anything in a long time, he did not check on Harrison all the time. The last time he checked was a day and a half ago. Everything was normal.

He activated his ability, and his vision suddenly changed. All that was left was darkness, and he could not see Harrison at all.

Before he could observe carefully, his vision suddenly disappeared, proving that the Observer's Mark had been destroyed.

"What did they encounter in the secondary dimension world?"

Han Xiao frowned. Being able to remove his Observer's Mark meant that there was a high chance of the appearance of Beyond Grade A energy level.

Without hesitation, he changed into a specific King and teleported to the throne that Harrison had taken away.

With a flash of light, the surroundings spun. Han Xiao had already arrived in a black, deep sea-like space. There was nothing else around him.

The throne should have been stored in Harrison's room, but at this moment, the fleet was gone, Harrison and the other crew members were nowhere to be seen. Only the throne was left floating alone.

"What is this place?"

Han Xiao looked around and was surprised to find that his energy sense seemed to have disappeared. He could not even sense the situation in this deep sea-like area. The radar of his mechanical suit was also malfunctioning, and his vision was greatly suppressed.

He released a group of detectors and connected them with his Mechanical Force. However, the detectors only flew for a short distance before they suddenly disconnected, and he could no longer sense them. It was as if they were swallowed by this black sea.

Han Xiao tried to shoot a few energy beams in one direction, but there was no reaction.

"This is a strange secondary dimension. What did Harrison encounter?"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The secondary dimension world was filled with all kinds of possibilities, and anything could happen. It was very complicated, and this expedition team had been in there for more than a year, so he could not be sure what had happened.

Just as Han Xiao was about to start searching for this secondary dimension, a huge pressure suddenly came from all directions. A loud sound rang as if this black sea suddenly pressed toward Han Xiao.

At the same time, a cold mental wave suddenly invaded his mind, and a solemn voice sounded.

"Foreign high-level life form, leave immediately. Otherwise, you will become the Realmless King's enemy!"

Chapter 1366: Realmless King

Realmless King? What the hell was that? It sounded quite scary.

Han Xiao raised his brows with interest.

It would have been slightly troublesome if the problem here was just a secondary dimension with strange rules. However, this was an actual sentient being that could communicate.

He felt as though he was in the deep sea. The huge water pressure came from all angles, covering the sky and earth. However, this bit of pressure only made his body tighten slightly, causing almost no damage. Compared to the Dragon Emperor's force field, this bit of strength could not even be considered a massage. At most, it felt like he was wearing a tight suit.

The secondary dimension world was extremely dangerous, but once one reached the level of a peak Beyond Grade A, most dangers would no longer pose a threat, especially since he was one of the best among the peak Beyond Grade As. As long as this being was not an anomaly like the Celestial Star Alliance, it would not be a problem.

Han Xiao floated on the spot and ignored the pressure around him.

"What is Realmless King?"

As soon as he said that, another message came with an even more majestic aura.

"Realmless King was born in the Black Space Storm and rose from the void and unorthodoxy. He is the master of millions of dimensions, the hunter of millions of worlds. Any life form that enters his territory is a servant under the King's authority!"

Woah! The scene suddenly turned magical.

"Not bad. With such a long title, I feel like he's almost catching up to me."

Han Xiao grinned.

It sounded like a powerful dimension deity entrenched in a deep layer secondary dimension. If an ordinary Beyond Grade A were to encounter it, their lives might be in danger. Unfortunately for them, he was not an ordinary Beyond Grade A.

While he was deep in thought, this voice became more and more powerful, as if a huge bell was ringing in his mind, echoing with a powerful buzz.

"Foreign life form, leave this place immediately, or I will expel you!"

"Wanna try?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and activated the cells in his body. It was as though he had activated a mini reactor and pumped out energy.

Chi!

Golden electric arcs shot out of his body, leaving a burning trail of light as if splitting the surrounding black sea.

With a flip of his palm, a light blue psionic energy appeared in it, releasing spherical shock waves as if it was stirring up endless ripples on the surface of the sea.

Although he did not know what was going on in this secondary dimension, his previous probing was ineffective. It was most likely because he did use enough energy.

Because he was worried that he would hurt Harrison and the expedition fleet, Han Xiao did not explode the entire secondary dimension with too much energy. Instead, he controlled his energy output and increased it bit by bit.

At the start, there was no change. The explosive energy was like a rock sinking into the ocean, and it did not cause any reaction. However, after a while, the black liquid substance that filled the entire space started to vibrate. It seemed to have exceeded the limit of its endurance, causing huge waves.

Boom!

Amidst the tremors, Han Xiao could feel the strong undercurrents shooting toward him. At the same time, he felt a sharp pain in his brain as he got hit by the enemy's mental attacks.

However, to him, it was no different from scratching an itch. With just a blink, his HP was full.

There was something strange about this black liquid. It caused his energy perception to fail, and his radar to be ineffective. He could not find the other party, so he could only use violence to force the other party to appear. If this was a dimensional consciousness, then the dimension itself was the other party's body. If he released energy inside, it would be equivalent to giving the other party an enema. The other party would not be able to last long.

Not long after, the entire space was shaking violently, as though it was going to explode and disintegrate at any time. The mental attacks were getting weaker and weaker, and they were filled with pained emotions.

Han Xiao looked around and narrowed his eyes.

"Still not coming out? Do you really want me to inflate you?"

As soon as he said that, the pressure around him suddenly became lighter. The black liquid-like substance shrank and turned into a whirlpool. The black sea flowed into it like a bathtub filled with water had its plug pulled out.

As the black sea disappeared, Han Xiao's energy perception quickly recovered, and his vision returned to normal.

This secondary dimension was a white world without anything. It was like the prototype of a secondary dimension that had yet to be fully formed. It was also like all matter was swept away by the receding black sea.

In the distant horizon, there was a black vortex that was getting smaller and smaller, sucking away all the black matter. It was about to open a spatial rift and escape.

"Running? I will break your legs!"

Han Xiao opened his hands, and mechanical soldiers appeared one after another.

The mechanical army that appeared immediately released the binding force field and held onto this black mass, preventing it from moving. At the same time, they also used the secondary dimension spatial stabilization device to fix the spatial rift that the other party had torn out.

This black liquid was extremely strange and slippery. However, under the control of Han Xiao's mechanical army, it was still frozen in place and turned into a high-density liquid state. It kept changing its shape as though it was struggling.

At the same time, its mental energy fluctuations spread out in all directions with this liquid at the center. The solemn atmosphere from before was gone, and only shock and anger were left.

"Foreign life form! You will pay the price for your actions. Realmless King will take it from you!"

Han Xiao turned a deaf ear and told the mechanical army to increase the binding force field. He then took out a cylindrical container and stuffed the mass inside. The black mass was compressed into a fist-sized liquid that floated in the container. Tiny electric arcs were attached to it, causing the liquid to jolt nonstop. It was extremely painful.

This was a special equipment that he had used to capture Primal Esper Ability Entities. He did not expect it to be suitable for this strange substance.

After locking it in the container, the liquid finally stopped. Han Xiao knocked on the outside of the container and asked curiously:

"What are you? Also, did a fleet pass by here recently? Where did you take them?"

"So you're looking for those people. Looks like you're a high-level life form in the main material universe!" The mental fluctuation of this liquid was unstable, and it was already covered in a layer of fear. However, it soon turned into anger. "I'm just one of the guardians of the millions of dimensions. I've already offered them to the Realmless King. If you have the guts, go find him!"

"Offerings?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "Tell me everything you know… Forget it, since you're not cooperating, I'll just interrogate you."

Han Xiao injected his Mechanical Force into the container, and the container was instantly filled with lightning, forming a mini ion thunderstorm. This liquid was like a bug trapped in an electric mosquito swatter, crackling from the electricity.

After torturing it for a while, Han Xiao finally got the information he wanted.

This liquid life form was an energy field type life form, born in the secondary dimension of a nurturing type life form. This black liquid was the shell given to it by the so-called Realmless King. It called itself one of the guardians of the million dimensions, the confidant (doubtful) of the Realmless King. Its name was Bobanica, meaning 'Erosion' and 'Swallowing'.

Through this kind of black substance, the Realmless King devoured the matter and energy of the various dimensions and transformed them into his own 'territory'. He occupied this area with a large number of guardians guarding the dimensions that he occupied.

The fleet that Harrison was in had indeed been taken away by him. Through the special connection between the black liquid and the Realmless King, it had used dimensional teleportation and sent them to the 'King's Land' where the Realmless King was. This was the main job of a guardian like Bobanica. The life forms that had been intercepted and sent to the Realmless King were called 'offerings'.

"Tsk, looks like I'll have to find this Realmless King if I want to get them… I wonder if it's a good or bad thing for Harrison to encounter something like this with his luck."

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

He pondered for a few seconds, shook his head, changed into the Dimension Travel mechanical suit, set the coordinates given by Bobanica, and headed toward the Realmless King's location.

...

In the middle of a secondary dimension, on a huge platform that looked like a black crystal, Harrison was floating in midair. His eyes were closed, as though he had lost consciousness, but his face was filled with pain.

One end of the black fog-like energy stream was connected to his glabella while the other end was connected to a gigantic black finger. Light flowed on the finger.

The owner of the finger was a black entity the size of a mountain. It had a human form and had many heads and arms. It was sitting on a black throne—it was the Realmless King.

After a while, the Realmless King retracted its energy stream, and Harrison lost the ability to float. He fell onto the platform and was still unconscious.

"Interesting. With that tree finding a new prey, I can harvest delicious souls again…"

The Realmless King let out a deep laugh, but in the ears of others, it would only be a frenzied roar.

As a powerful entity in a secondary dimension, the soul of a life form was a rare delicacy. However, it could not completely descend into the main material universe and could only project a portion of its power. Furthermore, the main material universe was extremely vast. Without coordinates, one could only wander the endless universe, and it was very difficult to find life.

At this moment, he had absorbed the memories of these life forms from the main material universe, learned the coordinates of the three Universal Civilizations, and also knew that the famous World Tree Civilization was fighting with them. In his eyes, this was a feast to harvest souls.

Under normal circumstances, even a powerful dimensional entity like him was afraid of the power of a Universal Civilization and was unwilling to provoke them.

However, if a Universal Civilization were to fall into war, the situation would be different. He still had the guts to take advantage of the situation.

"After provoking that tree, your doomsday is almost here. Hehe, rather than becoming its servants, you might as well become my food… However, the World Tree actually has the weakness of a main body? This is the first time I've learned of it."

The Realmless King moved its body, producing a rustling sound like countless insects crawling.

Then, countless eyes on his body turned to look at the unconscious Harrison on the platform. Greed and desire appeared in the eyes, but they quickly suppressed them.

"It's rare to meet a life form with such strong luck. If I eat you, my causal force will increase by a level… It's a pity that the guy behind you isn't easy to deal with. It would be better to make a deal with him."

The Realmless King looked away.

From Harrison's memories, he saw Han Xiao and knew that they had a close relationship.

He was extremely wary of the top-notch experts of the main material universe. It was precisely because of Black Star that he did not dare eat Harrison immediately.

The Realmless King knew that this was one of the mediums of the causal force, but he did not intend to violate it. This was because there was a high chance that he would pay the price for violating the causal force. If he ate Harrison, the price would most likely be this Black Star coming to fight him to death.

Right at this moment, a black mass suddenly fell from the sky filled with black fog and floated in front of the Realmless King. It contained the emergency message from Bobanica before he was captured, showing the image of Han Xiao releasing energy to open up the black sea.

"Oh? He came so quickly. It seems like this useless thing, Bobanica, will not be able to escape his grasp. He will give me my coordinates. This is good too. Wait for him to come and find me."

Seeing this, the Realmless King changed his posture and waited for Han Xiao to come.

Black Star was very powerful and might be able to threaten his life, but the Realmless King did not panic at all.

In terms of secondary dimension exploration, the World Tree was far ahead of the three Universal Civilizations. Although the Realmless King had no dealings with the World Tree Civilization, he knew how to send a message to the World Tree Family.

The intelligence that he had obtained from the expedition team contained the coordinates of the secondary dimensions of the three Universal Civilizations as well as various other information. This was the best bargaining chip that he could use. He believed that the World Tree would be very willing to accept this gift.

However, the Realmless King did not intend to tell them. After all, he did not want to have too much contact with the World Tree. In comparison, he was more interested in Black Star, the guest of a new Universal Civilization.

Chapter 1367: Unexpected Deal

The flowing light particles formed an endless tunnel in front of him. There was only a single point of light at the end, and time and space were pulled into an infinite line in his senses. He did not know how much distance he had crossed or how much time he had spent, but it felt like only an instant.

Countless strange scenes flashed past outside the tunnel, and his body seemed to have turned into smoke. For a moment, he could not feel the existence of his body, and all his senses that were used to explore the world were mixed together. However, the next moment, all his senses returned to normal, and his vision suddenly changed. He had arrived in a new space.

Endless black fog pervaded the area and red lightning flashed from time to time. It was like dark clouds that were brewing lightning, or dark clouds from a volcanic eruption. It was like the end of the world.

A black mountain range flowing with lava-like scarlet light was floating in the black fog like an island. The mountain peak at the center was steep and tall, and a rusty dark gold chain was wrapped around it, forming spiral-like patterns. It was connected to a black crystal-like platform that was suspended in the air, and on it sat a gigantic black figure the size of a mountain. Countless red eyes turned in unison and looked over.

"Oh my, isn't this going to cost me my sanity?"

Han Xiao smacked his lips. He took a look at the scenery of this secondary dimension with interest and captured a photo as a memento. Otherwise, if they were to fight later, he might accidentally crush this place.

Looking up at the mountain-like figure, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"You're the Realmless King?"

It had to be said that this guy's appearance was quite scary. Ordinary people would probably be shocked to the point of losing their minds at first glance, triggering a deep-seated phobia of giant creatures. However, Han Xiao was used to seeing all kinds of things, so this scene did not have any impact on him at all. The shock was far less than a fleet salvo during the interception battle.

"Yes, I was waiting for you, Black Star," the Realmless King replied slowly.

"You know me?"

Han Xiao was a little surprised. He looked down at Bobanica in his hands and remembered that he did not mention his name. Could it be that his name had already spread from the main universe to the secondary dimensions?

"I know why you're here. You want to take this fleet and this intelligent creature called Harrison away, right? I learned about your civilization from their memories."

The Realmless King sat still, but the black fog in the sky suddenly moved away, revealing a fleet. It was the missing expedition team of the three Universal Civilizations. However, it was only shown for a moment before the black fog covered it again, making it impossible to sense.

The unconscious Harrison flew up from the platform and hovered in front of it.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, but he was not in a hurry to make a move. He asked curiously, "I see. Then why are you waiting for me here?"

The Realmless King did not reply immediately. He slowly said, "I usually digest the prey I capture immediately, but I learned your name from their memories. To be honest, I'm very afraid of you high-level life forms in the main material universe. Because of your existence, I did not eat them immediately."

"You're quite cool-headed."

Han Xiao sized up the Realmless King with surprise.

Your cowardice saved you, baby!

Just from the memories of Harrison and the others, he knew that I was their backer, so he did not dare to attack the expedition team… It seems that I am still very intimidating.

Seeing that the other party was giving him face, Han Xiao's expression softened a little. He stretched out his hand and said with a smile, "In that case, I don't mind being friends with you. Let them go first."

However, the Realmless King shook his head. "I didn't say I would return them to you."

Hearing this, Han Xiao paused.

"If you're not willing to provoke me, and you don't want to return the people, what are you going to do?"

"I want to make a deal with you."

"Deal? Although you didn't eat these people, you captured them and brought them here. I don't owe you any favors. You want to use these people as bargaining chips? It's difficult."

Han Xiao replied casually.

The Realmless King said slowly:

"No, my bargaining chip is the intelligence of the three Universal Civilizations in their memories. You guys are fighting a war with the World Tree, and I believe the World Tree will definitely like this intelligence. They will be able to find your secondary dimension territory, and I happen to have a way to contact the members of the World Tree."

This news was out of his expectations. Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and he immediately put down his hands.

"Threatening me? Are you tired of living?"

"It's not a threat, it's just self-preservation. Even if you agree to make a deal with me, I'm afraid that you'll take revenge on me after I return the person to you. I don't have the confidence to win against you… And with this trump card, I believe my safety will be guaranteed. This is the basis of the deal."

The Realmless King's tone was matter-of-fact.

"…How can I believe you when you say that you can contact the members of the World Tree? Do you think you can scare me with just a few words? It's not that I don't dare to bet that you know the term from their memories. Show me the evidence."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

The Realmless King did not mind and explained:

"I understand what you mean, but I'm not lying to you. Although you and the World Tree fought in the main material universe, the secondary dimension world is their base camp. They have devoured secondary dimensions one after another for countless years.

However, the secondary dimensions are endless, and the World Tree does not eat every single one of them. Its main method of expansion is to take root and imprint the secondary dimensions into their territory, turning them into territories that allow them to travel quickly. For some special secondary dimensions, they don't even interfere with them and instead focus on observation and research.

At the same time, they sent out countless members to explore the outside world, spreading the name of the World Tree and its connection channels. It's similar to what they did in the main material universe. One of their exploration teams passed by my outer territory, and one of my guardians received a lot of information and reported it to me…"

As he spoke, the Realmless King shared a small portion of his memories through mental communication.

Han Xiao did a check, but there were no signs of forgery. He did indeed have the contact information of the World Tree members, and he was a little annoyed.

'This is a little tricky… There's no 100% chance of stopping the information leak if I try to kill this guy. If the World Tree starts a secondary dimensional battlefront, our situation will become worse.'

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he quickly calculated.

The World Tree's main body was rooted in the secondary dimension, and this was its territory. Although its main body was found in his previous life, if not for the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device transporting to the central area and launching a sneak attack, it would have been almost impossible for frontal attacks to pass through the secondary dimension defense circle near the World Tree's main body.

Right now, the three Universal Civilizations were in a good situation. One of the reasons was that the World Tree did not have the time to figure out the secondary dimension territory of the three Universal Civilizations like in his previous life and did not activate this battlefront, which reduced the pressure on them.

Seeing the change in Han Xiao's expression, the Realmless King spoke again.

"You don't have to worry about me using this as leverage to threaten you. With the abilities of high-level life forms like you, even if your civilization is destroyed, there's a high chance that you can escape. At that time, this trump card won't be able to protect me anymore… So, you can rest assured. I just want to make a deal with you. I won't force you to do anything overboard. As long as you don't attack me, there's no need for me to tell on you. Trust me, no one is willing to take the initiative to have dealings with the World Tree."

The Realmless King's tone was sincere. Although he had a hold on him, he did not dare make any outrageous requests. He did not think that this trump card could support him in doing whatever he wanted in front of the other party. In his eyes, it was just a qualification to make a deal with the other party.

Han Xiao stroked his chin and looked at the Realmless King thoughtfully.

This Realmless King was a powerful dimensional deity, and his name was very intimidating. However, he remained humble in front of Han Xiao. Although he had a hold on him, he did not act tough. Instead, he was a little cowardly.

Han Xiao pondered for a few seconds and suppressed his hostility.

"…Tell me about your deal. What do you want me to do for you?"

"There are only two things. One is that after the battle breaks out, you will allow me to project my power and harvest the souls of those who died in battle, as well as some destroyed battleships. The materials of the main universe are quite valuable to us."

Are you trying to snatch business from the Underworld?

Furthermore, you're working part-time to retrieve the wreckage of the battleship. Are you a galactic scavenger ‽

Han Xiao's expression became strange. He looked around at the slowly flowing black fog and felt that the Realmless King suddenly looked like a trash station owner.

"…What about the second matter?"

"I once had a special secondary dimension, but it was snatched away by another group of dimensional entities. They are not easy to deal with, and I have never been able to deal with them. I hope you can help me snatch it back."

Han Xiao smacked his lips and said:

"I can help you with these two things, but since you said that the method of snitching is only to protect yourself and not threaten me, I won't take it as a bargaining chip. The price you offered isn't suitable, so I need more."

"What do you want?" The Realmless King did not reject the bargain.

"I need more information about the World Tree's force in the secondary dimension. Tell me everything you know. Also, I want some black matter for research. Finally… Maybe we can work together to deal with the World Tree. They have been expanding in the secondary dimension and will arrive at your territory sooner or later. It's best to strike first," Han Xiao said slowly.

"I can promise you the first two points. As for dealing with the World Tree, forget it. I can't afford to provoke them either. I'll just hide."

As expected, the Realmless King rejected.

Han Xiao smiled.

"Don't be too afraid. The World Tree has the weakness of the main body. As long as the main body is destroyed, your threat will be resolved once and for all. Isn't that good? Also, you might even be able to free a large number of souls to be your food."

Although Harrison and the others had been captured, causing the leak of information to appear, with Harrison's luck, he could turn bad luck into good luck. From a good perspective, this was also an opportunity for him to find out about the World Tree's force in the secondary dimension.

Therefore, he did not launch an attack. Instead, he was trying to see if he could pull in a new ally. After all, he was once the successor of socialism, and it had become a habit to unite all forces.

"It sounds very tempting, but I'm not sure if the main body really exists. Let's talk about it after you find it."

The Realmless King did not comment.

Seeing this, Han Xiao did not force him. He already knew that the other would not agree so easily, and only mentioned this topic.

At this moment, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the mission [Transaction with the Realmless King]!

Mission Introduction: For some reason, the Realmless King has something to ask of you. He has proposed a deal with you.

Mission Requirements: Retrieve the target's secondary dimension.

Reward: 250 Billion EXP,+25 Realmless King Favorability, x1 Character Summon Card.

Remarks: This mission may have unknown effects. Please accept carefully.

Han Xiao was curious.

What kind of secondary dimension was it that the Realmless King would risk offending him to snatch it back… Could this be his wife ‽

Chapter 1368: Strange Encounter and Lies

Seemingly noticing Han Xiao's confusion, the Realmless King explained with a deep voice.

"This secondary dimension is nurturing one of my children. It was a special case, as it was still an embryo, yet to take form when it was taken away. The dimension entities that took it planned to eat it after it matured, so I hope that you can snatch it back while protecting the secondary dimension from shattering."

"So, it's not your wif… cough, I'll try my best." Han Xiao hid his words with a cough, before asking, "By the way, what is the origin of that dimension?"

Realmless King shifted his sitting posture, before slowly speaking,

"They are external dimension entities. I was born in this area, and this area is my territory. Originally, I was the only overlord life form here, and there were no natural enemies or competitors. However, when those dimension entities arrived here from the spatial storm, my situation changed. They targeted me and settled down at the edge of my territory. I tried to expel them many times, but I failed. However, they could not do anything to me either…"

Following the Realmless King's explanation, Han Xiao quickly understood the situation.

The secondary dimension world had its own ecosystem. Due to the uncertainty of space, the division of regions was usually marked by some special secondary dimension or overlord-level life forms. For example, the territory controlled by the Realmless King was a representative stable region. The areas outside this region were akin to the desolate universe belt of the main universe, except they were not only desolate but filled with unknowns.

This was akin to being cut off from the rest of the world. It was just that the area was too vast, and they did not know the boundaries. Most of the stable regions did not know of each other's existence, and they did not want to be discovered by outsiders. After all, the environment here was more dangerous, and it was difficult to breed a civilization. The life forms born were more particular about the law of the jungle where the strong preyed on the weak.

However, order would also be found within the chaos. A small group of stable areas would usually maintain communications with each other, and for different reasons, their names would spread out and connect to other stable areas. Just like how the primitive tribes in the Wilderness discovered each other, they formed a new compound organization.

The Realmless King was a member of the composite ecosystem. He knew the coordinates of several stable areas and had always been without problems.

To put it simply, the situation that the Realmless King had encountered was that the local tyrant had met with a 'roaming dragon'. The secondary dimension was so big, but the other party refused to leave and even wanted to target him. Thus, it turned into a neighbor dispute.

Han Xiao had obtained information about these few dimensional entities from the mental messages that the other party had shared. They were the accumulated experiences of the Realmless King fighting them over the years, displaying their various abilities.

However, this information only had a little bit of reference value to him. As long as they fought, he would be able to obtain more detailed information through the combat information on the interface. Han Xiao did not take the Realmless King's exaggerated description of the enemy too seriously.

Although the secondary dimension world was strange and varied, as long as no one reached a higher level, the peak Beyond Grade As of the main universe would still be the predators at the top of the food chain. No matter how famous the dimension deities were, they would not appear impressive in front of him.

"I understand. Send a projection over with me."

Han Xiao's tone was casual. His body swayed, and a Lord's Avatar separated from his body. Mechanical Force electric arcs surged out from his body and entered the Lord's Avatar, activating the Lord's Descent state.

He did not plan to leave this place. His main body would stay behind to keep an eye on the Realmless King, in case he made any small moves. Sending the Lord's Avatar would be enough to resolve this mission.

"Alright, if you don't mind, I hope to let him temporarily inherit my power. It will only be beneficial to him and not detrimental. Consider it a small apology."

The Realmless King raised an arm and waved it. Harrison spun around and landed in front of Han Xiao. His eyelids trembled, and he slowly opened his eyes. He looked like he had just woken up from a coma.

As soon as he saw Han Xiao, Harrison's eyes immediately focused and he slowly recalled what had happened before he fainted. His face immediately twitched, and an expression of disbelief appeared on his face.

"Your Excellency Black Star?! I… I'm still alive?!"

Han Xiao pressed down on Harrison's shoulder and electric sparks appeared on his fingertips. He looked at the interface, nodded, and said, "Your vital signs are normal. It's good that you're okay."

"I still remember the fleet being attacked… Are you here to save me?"

Harrison was touched.

He still remembered his last memory before he fainted. The overwhelming black tide swallowed the entire fleet, and the fleet could not resist at all. He did not have time to do anything, and at that moment, he thought he was done for. Jenny's beautiful face and shiny forehead flashed in his mind, and his heart was filled with reluctance and despair.

Now that he had woken up and seen Han Xiao, Harrison's uneasy heart instantly calmed down. His fear, panic, and nervousness instantly disappeared. He knew that Black Star's arrival meant that he was fine.

Before he could ask why Harrison felt his body turn around and look behind him. At the same time, a message appeared in his mind.

"Kid, I'm the Realmless King. Relax your body and mind and accept my infusion."

As soon as Harrison turned around, he saw the strange sight of this dimension, as well as the terrifying body of the Lord of the Realmless. An instinctive fear rose from the depths of his soul, and it was like a chill that spread through his bones, freezing his body in an instant.

However, the feeling disappeared in the blink of an eye. If he was alone, Harrison might have felt that he had gone crazy from fear. However, the moment he thought about how Black Star, his "father-level" universe expert, was standing right behind him, an incomparable sense of security immediately dispelled all the fear in his heart.

Without fear, the explorer's soul was immediately ignited. Harrison looked at the Realmless King, and his tone was filled with curiosity.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what sort of thing is this?"

"He's not a thing. He's called the Realmless King. He's a life form from a secondary dimension. He's basically a trash collector," Han Xiao replied casually. He patted Harrison's shoulder and said, "Listen to him. Relax and let him enter your body. It won't hurt."

As soon as he said that, the Realmless King's eyes blinked. The black fog around him seemed to be drawn toward the confused Harrison and entered his body.

Very soon, thin black and red lines appeared on the surface of his body. They looked like bulging blood vessels, but they were messy and still twisting irregularly. However, Harrison did not feel any pain. He only felt his body burning.

In places that he could not see, every cell in his body got cleansed by the black fog-like energy and underwent a positive mutation in the direction of optimization. Although he was still a low-level Super, his basic physique was rapidly improving.

After a long while, the black and red lines on Harrison's body finally converged on his chest, forming a mark. This represented the contract formed by the Realmless King. With it, he would be able to borrow the power of the Realmless King from afar in most environments.

This kind of dimensional divine entity could project its power to life forms through contracts. This was also the main method for them to enter the main material universe. Some religious sects in the galaxy had connections with the dimensional divine spirits, and Han Xiao's Underworld Mark followed a similar process.

The amount of power that could be borrowed depended on the individual strength of the contractor and the level of the contract. For Han Xiao's sake, the Realmless King had made the highest level contract. In times of danger, the Realmless King could even temporarily take over and provide the 'strong family grandpa' service.

The treatment Harrison received was all thanks to Han Xiao.

"Damn, this Advanced Luck Glow is really…"

Han Xiao gritted his teeth in envy.

With his current level, he was already the source of luck for the owner of the Lucky Halo. Because of his existence, Harrison was able to turn this danger into a fortuitous encounter.

If I could have met someone like myself when I was weak, it would have been awesome!

It's a pity that I've already reached my current maximum. Not many people have the right to be relied on by me… Han Xiao sighed in his heart.

At this time, Harrison's pupils had already turned pure black. The Realmless King took over his body and nodded.

"I'm done. Shall we set off now?"

Han Xiao nodded and controlled the Lord's Avatar to take out the Dimensional Travel Device. Together with Harrison, they disappeared in a flash.

He suddenly thought of something. His main body took out the container that held Bobanica and spoke to the Realmless King, "By the way, I caught this guy and forgot to return him to you."

The Realmless King glanced at the container with a human-like look of disdain in his eyes. "Keep it. Let it out after we're done."

Han Xiao curled his lips and put away the container. It seemed like the liquid was bragging when it said that it was the Realmless King's confidant.

The Lord's Avatar needed to travel for a while. Han Xiao rose up and sat mid-air, hovering at the same height as the Realmless King's head. The two of them stared at each other.

...

The Lord's Avatar set the coordinates of the dimensions provided by the Realmless King, and it did not take long for them to reach their destination.

This was still a pitch-black secondary dimension, but it was different from the doomsday scene on the side of the Realmless King. The darkness here had a peaceful aura.

Han Xiao could sense that the energy of the entire secondary dimension was flowing toward the same location. In that direction, there was an incomplete life signal that showed something was being nurtured.

"This is it. Those dimensional entities have always been here. Be careful," the Realmless King spoke through Harrison.

Han Xiao nodded. He opened the dimensional army camp and from it appeared an endless stretch of his mechanical army. At the same time, he activated a portion of the mechanical soldiers to form a normal version of the Mechanical Deity and prepared for battle.

At this time, a few powerful energy sources approached from different directions. Three enormous figures covering the sky approached from afar and quickly occupied their sights. They had different appearances and were the external dimension gods that occupied this place. The moment they appeared, they gave off a strong sense of oppression.

"Who is it ‽ How dare you disturb our… F*ck, Black Star!"

"We can't win, run!"

As soon as the three dimensional entities saw the Mechanical Deity, they immediately turned around and ran.

Seeing this, both Han Xiao and the Realmless King were stunned.

He had thought that he would have to fight to solve the problem, but these dimension entities ran away like rabbits on seeing him as if they already knew him.

Has my name really spread in the secondary dimension world?

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, his mind working rapidly.

These three dimensional entities were outsiders, and they might have come from somewhere near the shallow layer. Could it be that he had accidentally beat up some dimensional deities—who did not realize they were third-wheeling—when he was traveling with Ames a few decades ago, inadvertently making a name for himself?

Han Xiao pondered over the reason, but his hands did not slow down. The mechanical army immediately chased after them.

These three dimensional entities could not even deal with the Realmless King, and in his hands, it would only be a one-sided abuse.

Han Xiao originally wanted to kill them, but since the other party knew him, he controlled his strength and left them alive.

After a round of beating, the three dimension entities with swollen faces sat down in front of him, leaving only obedience inside them.

"This…"

The Realmless King's face twitched. The situation was different from what he had imagined.

These people were powerful outsiders that he could not chase away no matter how hard he tried. But the moment they met Black Star, they were so terrified they had to run away but could not even escape being caught and beaten up. This made the Realmless King feel disillusioned.

Seeing Black Star take action with his own eyes, the Realmless King was afraid, but at the same time, he was also glad that he did not choose to be stubborn against Han Xiao. The top experts of the main material universe were indeed not to be messed with.

At the same time, Han Xiao was interrogating the three dimension entities with his arms crossed.

"Where have the three of you heard of me?"

"We… we've seen you kill dimension deities…"

The three dimensional deities who were strong enough to dominate an entire region in the secondary dimension had become extremely docile.

It was only after Han Xiao finished listening that he realized that there was indeed a reason for these three to come to the Realmless King's territory.

These three dimension deities originally resided near the 'secondary dimensional layer' controlled by the three Universal Civilizations. As the Universal Civilizations were planning to expand there, the three of them had planned to migrate.

A few decades ago, when he and Ames were traveling, they passed by the area and beat up another dimension deity. The three of them witnessed the tragic scene and were filled with fear. Thus, they decided to migrate and enter the depths of the secondary dimension. In the end, they came to the Realmless King's territory many years ago and finally met someone alone. They planned to devour the Realmless King before continuing their journey.

However, the three of them did not expect to be unable to defeat the other party. They originally wanted to leave, but they coincidentally discovered this secondary dimension with a special embryo. They instinctively felt that eating this life would be very beneficial to them, so they stayed on.

"What a coincidence."

Han Xiao did not know what to say.

If this mission was given to someone else, the difficulty would be enough to meet the highest reward offered. Ordinary Beyond Grade As would be served up on a silver platter in front of these three dimensional entities. But if it was him, he would not even need to move a finger. Having a high Reputation was just that convenient.

"Well, we've told you everything we know. Can you let us go…"

A dimensional entity carefully spoke out.

"Don't even think about it."

Han Xiao rejected without hesitation.

At this time, the Realmless King could not help but say, "Black Star, this secondary dimension has been taken back. I shall first occupy this place again."

As he spoke, black liquid appeared on his body, wanting to fill up this dimension and return it to being his territory.

Just as Han Xiao was about to agree, he suddenly paused and changed his words. "Don't be so anxious. Let me see what the embryo looks like first."

"My child hasn't even formed yet. Is this necessary?"

"This is the first time I've seen such a phenomenon. I'm just curious."

Han Xiao replied casually before flying toward the breeding ground. The Realmless King had no choice but to follow behind.

After advancing for some distance, Han Xiao saw a grayish-white sphere floating in the middle of the secondary dimension. It was like fog being condensed together before being wrapped up by a translucent membrane. Energy flowed in from all directions to nourish this embryo.

In his senses, this embryo had an extremely vigorous life force, as dazzling as dozens of stars put together.

Han Xiao looked inside and saw that within the gray fog flowing in the membrane, there seemed to be a long figure flashing around like a dragon.

The Realmless King came over and helplessly lamented, "It's not even born yet. What's there to see?"

Han Xiao ignored him and touched the embryo. Although the membrane was thin, it was very pliable and tough.

At this moment, the item introduction popped up on the interface.

Han Xiao cursory glanced at the interface before stopping short. He slowly turned to look at the Realmless King with a smile that was yet not a smile.

"You said… this is your child?"

"What's wrong?" The Realmless King met Han Xiao's gaze and suddenly felt a little guilty.

"Bullsh*t. No wonder you took the risk to order me to help you snatch it back. It turns out to be such a magical item… Are you betting that I won't be able to discover its wonders?"

Han Xiao flicked the embryo with his finger, and the sarcasm in his tone could not hide the joy within.

"Speaking half-truths? You almost fooled me."

Chapter 1369: Lucky Halo, Forever God!

"…You're mistaken. This is my child. It's just mutated slightly."

The Realmless King pretended to be calm.

Keep pretending!

Han Xiao snorted inwardly and ignored him. He turned to look at the item introduction on the interface.

[Pivotal Snake Egg]

[Pivotal Snake, also known as World Devouring Snake, is a rare species that lives in chaotic space stream. It is a creature that lives alone and feeds on secondary dimensions and special Information Form Phenomenons. Every World Devouring Snake will only lay seven eggs in its lifetime. After laying eggs, it will abandon them in the space storm, allowing the eggs to drift freely. When the egg encounters a secondary dimension, it will automatically parasitize and turn into an embryo state, absorbing multiple secondary dimensions until it completely matures. At the same time, Pivotal Snake eggs have an extremely strong attraction to some secondary dimension life forms. Eating them as infants is very beneficial. It has a certain chance of strengthening one's talent and raising one's life level.]

Remarks: The origin of this species is closely related to the World Tree. It can eat the body of the World Tree and has a certain level of restraint.

The item introduction was not long, but the information it revealed shocked Han Xiao.

The Pivotal Snake was like a space louse back then. It was not in the database of the three Universal Civilizations, and it had never been discovered in his previous life. Even to him, it was a foreign species.

What surprised Han Xiao the most was that this creature was actually related to the World Tree. The item introduction even stated that it was the World Tree's nemesis to a certain extent, which surprised him.

The World Tree was a unique Space Wonder, but there just happened to be a type of creature that could restrain it. Could it be that there was always a paper to every rock?

Perhaps the Pivotal Snake was, in a sense, a companion species of the World Tree, born to restrain it? If one thought deeper, what was the origin of the World Tree…

All kinds of guesses flashed through Han Xiao's mind, but he did not have a clue.

However, there was one thing he could confirm. If he did not have the item introduction on the interface, he would definitely not have been able to discover the uniqueness of this embryo. The Realmless King had claimed that this was his child, so it would be difficult for him to investigate further. It would be difficult for him to discover anything strange, and he would most likely be fooled by the Realmless King. This was probably what the Realmless King had planned.

All kinds of thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He raised his hand and pressed on the Realmless King's shoulder.

"Do you really think I don't know what's what? This can't be your child. Are you lying to me because you're worried that I'll be tempted by this thing? Our deal needs to be honest, and my impression of you is quite good at the moment, so I'll give you a chance to come clean. If you still lie to me, then don't blame me for holding a grudge. No matter how my civilization and the World Tree fight in the future, I'll guarantee that you'll definitely die."

The Realmless King's face twitched.

Although he had something on Han Xiao, it could not protect him forever. Facing Han Xiao's threat, he was still very weak.

His original intention of lying was to not let Black Star investigate further to avoid more problems. After all, as long as they came to this secondary dimension, they could feel the birth of a certain life-form, which would easily make people curious. Furthermore, the embryo had a special attraction to the dimension deities. If he did not claim to have a special relationship with it, he was worried that Black Star would be tempted.

He had originally thought that since Black Star was a guest of the main universe, he might not be able to feel the attraction of the embryo. As long as he did not study it, he would not be able to discover anything amiss, and he would be able to fool everyone. However, he did not expect Black Star to see through it so easily, causing his plan to fail. Of course, he could not rule out the possibility that Black Star was trying to trick him, but since he had made a threat, the Realmless King was not confident.

After hesitating for a while, the Realmless King said helplessly,

"If you know what this is, why ask me?"

"I just want to hear it from you."

Han Xiao crossed his arms. He was mainly curious about how much the Realmless King knew about the Pivotal Snake Egg.

If he was only tempted by the 'special attraction' shown by the item introduction, then the Realmless King's goal should also be to wait for the embryo to mature and eat it. However, if he knew the origins of the Pivotal Snake, then the Realmless King's actions would be a little subtle.

However, in his opinion, the Realmless King most likely did not know about the relationship between the Pivotal Snake and the World Tree, or even about the Pivotal Snake. If not for the item introduction, he would not have known about this secret. In the secondary dimension world where information was difficult to spread, the Realmless King would not have known about this secret.

As expected, the Realmless King's answer was roughly the same as what Han Xiao had guessed. He said that he had discovered this embryo when he was expanding his territory and felt the attraction, so he had brought it back to wait for it to mature, but it had been snatched away.

After explaining, the Realmless King asked Han Xiao if he knew the origin of the embryo.

"Of course I know, but the information isn't complete. I only saw it once when I was exploring the secondary dimensions, but it disappeared afterward."

Han Xiao waved his hands and found an excuse.

Of course, he would not reveal the information about the Pivotal Snake to the Realmless King. As for whether he was pretending not to know the Pivotal Snake, he could only observe.

"Alright… Then how do you plan to deal with this embryo? Our deal…" the Realmless King probed.

"Tsk, you're hiding something from me. Logically speaking, the deal should be canceled, but since your attitude is alright, the deal can continue. This embryo is still yours."

Before the Realmless King could heave a sigh of relief, Han Xiao paused and said:

"However, the deal is only to help you get the embryo back. Although the embryo is in your hands, you can't eat it. I'll have a mechanical army stationed here. I'm very interested in this embryo and want to see how it looks like when it matures."

Hearing this, the Realmless King had no choice but to agree. In terms of benefits, Black Star had at least gotten rid of his three neighbors, so it was not a loss.

After reaching a consensus, Han Xiao made the mechanical army build a temporary base around the embryo, and the Realmless King could only let him do as he wished.

At the same time, the mission completion notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface. He had obtained a large amount of EXP, but the favorability reward of the Realmless King had decreased, only increasing by five points. Clearly, it was affected by his actions. Only by completely returning the embryo would he obtain the most favorability, but this favorability was not important to him.

As for the Character Summon Card, it was the ability of the Realmless King. Its effect was to project the power of the Realmless King into the main universe and summon the black liquid that could block energy senses.

...

At the same time, the Realmless King Dimension.

Han Xiao's main body broke the silence and said:

"The matter is done. I will take these three dimensional entities with me. I will not disturb you anymore. It's time for you to fulfill your promise. I want all the information about the World Tree that you know."

"…Okay."

The Realmless King had no choice but to do as he was told, sharing this part of his memories through mental messages.

Han Xiao immediately turned these mental memories into virtual data and entered them into a device.

With this information, the expedition team of the three Universal Civilizations would no longer have to explore like a headless fly. They would be able to save a lot of energy and head directly toward the World Tree's territory in the secondary dimension. Although the closer they were to the World Tree's territory, the more dangerous it would be, there was a higher chance of finding the World Tree's main body.

The Realmless King also gave him the coordinates of a few stable areas and a portion of the map. The three Universal Civilizations were no longer completely clueless about this deep layer area, so the information was valuable.

Han Xiao browsed through the intelligence and suddenly said:

"I want to represent the three Universal Civilizations to reach an agreement with you. You control a large area of the secondary dimension, and I hope that you can lend a portion of your territory as a temporary outpost for the three Universal Civilizations to explore the secondary dimension world. Let our expedition team gather here and rest. This will provide us with a lot of help. What do you think?"

Hearing this, the Realmless King was immediately annoyed. He only felt that the other party was pushing his luck and could not help but warn him.

"I don't want to get involved in your war. Don't forget that I still have something on you."

"It's okay. We're temporarily stationed here, so we can give you more information. Plus, we're already here. Even if you don't welcome us, our large follow-up troops would still pass through here. You might as well cooperate with us and get some benefits."

Han Xiao did not mind it.

If he could obtain the Realmless King's support, he would be able to obtain the coordinates of the edge of the Realmless King's territory, which would save him the time needed to cross this area.

Setting up a transit station in this deep layer region was akin to obtaining a new entrance. Like a recording point, the expedition team would be able to set off from here as soon as they entered, saving them a lot of time. This would be very helpful for the expedition.

The Realmless King's heart was filled with uncertainty. After weighing the pros and cons for a long time, he finally nodded with resignation.

Even though he had something on Black Star, he did not dare use it because he was afraid of the consequences. Instead, Black Star had taken the initiative. Although Black Star had helped him chase away his evil neighbors, this was undoubtedly asking a tiger for its skin. The Realmless King was already regretting inviting a wolf into his house.

It's all Bobanica's fault for provoking such a troublesome guy. How dare he boast that he's my trusted aide? More like a big trouble!

Buzz!

Just as the Realmless King was getting frustrated, Harrison returned to his main body on the carrier. He had already exited the 'please possess me' state and regained control of his body.

Han Xiao released his magnetic force and drew Harrison in front of him. He then handed him the information recording device and said:

"The matter has been resolved. I have made a deal with the Realmless King. He is willing to lend out some secondary dimensions to act as our outpost. He will release the expedition team later. Go and report the situation to the commander and pass this information to him. Tell them to stop advancing and standby here. Wait for me to inform the three Universal Civilizations…"

"Understood. I promise to complete the mission."

Harrison nodded repeatedly.

Seeing how obedient he was, Han Xiao had mixed feelings.

Although Harrison and the others had been implicated this time, they had also benefited from the disaster, bringing substantial progress to their plan to search for the World Tree's main body. They found a 'temporary ally' deep in the secondary dimension.

What surprised Han Xiao the most was that Harrison had set off to search for the World Tree's main body. He had yet to find the location of the main body, but he had already found a strange object that could restrain the main body…

What else could he say?

Luck Glow, forever a god!

'Letting Harrison join the expedition team was indeed the right decision…'

Han Xiao was pleased.

If not for the Realmless King discovering him from Harrison's memories, this expedition team would have been a goner. In his previous life, perhaps due to the time difference, the Realmless King had already eaten the Pivotal Snake Embryo, or perhaps for some other reason, Han Xiao had never heard of the three Universal Civilizations obtaining the Pivotal Snake Egg.

If they had such a trump card in his previous life, the difficulty of attacking the main body would have been much lower.

However, although it was worth being happy about obtaining a trump card, he still had to find the World Tree's main body to put it to use. Furthermore, Han Xiao was still very curious about the connection between the Pivotal Snake and the World Tree.

In addition, he also wanted to know if the World Tree Civilization knew about the characteristics of the Pivotal Snake… He had a feeling that there was something fishy about this.

Chapter 1370: Current State of the Potential Individuals

"…You found us a temporary ally in a deep layer dimension and got information about the World Tree's territory?"

In the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations, Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope could not help but widen their eyes when they heard Han Xiao's notification.

"If it wasn't for Harrison, I definitely wouldn't have gone there. I wouldn't have met such a good thing."

Han Xiao spread out his hands. After leaving the throne in the Realmless King's dimension, he returned to the main material universe and informed the three Universal Civilizations about what had happened.

Considering the Realmless King's attitude, Han Xiao only hid the information about the Pivotal Snake Egg. Before this trump card matured, there was no need to tell the three Universal Civilizations about it for the time being.

After hearing the reason, the three of them looked at each other in shock and joy.

Marbruce cleared his throat and said in a deep voice, "It's been hard on you. This is an important discovery in the expedition plan. Our next search will be more targeted. We have agreed to this alliance. We will send some envoys to be in charge of negotiating with the Realmless King about the future cooperation."

Although Han Xiao did not report the matter beforehand and had made the decision on behalf of the three Universal Civilizations, this was a special time. As long as it was useful to the war, this problem was nothing.

Han Xiao nodded, took out a list of secondary dimension coordinates, and said, "These are the secondary dimension coordinates that the Realmless King lent us to act as the outpost. We can build a new gate entrance here and turn this area into a 'shallow layer'. You guys know what to do next. Just play your rogue side, but don't push the Realmless King too hard."

"What are you saying…"

Marbruce's face twitched. He helplessly took the list and showed it to the other two leaders.

"Alright, that's all I have to say. If there's no other problem, I'll head back to take care of the training." Han Xiao waved his hand.

"Wait a moment, we still have something to discuss with you…"

Louis called out to Han Xiao with a rare smile on his face.

"The Beyond Grade As have worked hard for the war. After a discussion, we have unanimously decided to set up a monument for all the Beyond Grade As sacrificed in the war. It has nothing to do with identity, only merits."

Han Xiao's eyes lit up, and he said with relief, "This was not easy. You guys finally said something sensible."

Louis' smile froze, and he laughed dryly as though he did not hear that. "Hehe, what do you think of this plan?"

"Very good, I have no objections."

Han Xiao shook his head.

When they were fighting in the interception circle, no one had the intention to do so. Now that they had eleven years of buffer time, it was suitable for them to do such things. Although the dark clouds of war still shrouded them, at least the Soul Comfort Monument would not let them die in obscurity. Compared to the battle damage report on the internet, the real thing was more meaningful and could slightly increase their cohesion.

However, under the premise of the Sanctum Revival, the effect of the Soul Comfort Monument would probably be different from what they had expected. The three Universal Civilizations still did not believe that the Sanctum Revival was limitless. In Han Xiao's opinion, the Soul Comfort Monument would probably become a 'battle record' that recorded the number of deaths of the various Beyond Grade As in the future. This would be different from what they had expected… but at least it was better than nothing.

"Since you have no objections, I'll have to trouble you to convey our intentions to all the members of the association and let them know that we're grateful for their help. No matter what grudges we had in the past, we were born from the same universe." The Pope nodded.

"…Did the three of you take the wrong medicine today? Why are you talking so much?"

Han Xiao looked at the three of them in surprise.

"Alright, that's all. You can go."

Han Xiao shrugged, deactivated the remote projection, and disappeared from their sights.

Seeing this, Louis relaxed, shook his head, and sighed.

"Sigh, Black Star always brings us surprises. If not for him saving Harrison, we would have missed this secondary dimension intelligence."

"Black Star's luck is unbelievable. Luckily, he's our teammate now." Marbruce exhaled.

The three of them sighed for a while before lowering their heads to study the information that Han Xiao had brought back.

...

The matter of Harrison did not take much time, and Han Xiao did not have to worry too much about the follow-up alliance affairs.

After returning to the training base, Han Xiao sent a message to inform them of the plan for the Soul Comfort Monument.

Although the original intention of both sides working together was to make a deal, the Beyond Grade As did not want their achievements to be neglected. It was naturally extremely good for the three Universal Civilizations to be willing to increase their reputation for them. However, this action seemed to be to sustain their sense of belonging to the galactic society, so it did not move the Beyond Grade As.

As usual, Han Xiao checked on the training of the Calamity Grade and Beyond Grade As. He then went to a mental strength training room and found Feidin, who was training his psychic energy.

A song that directly resonated in one's soul echoed in the room along with psychic energy. It was different from simple psychic needles or psychic blasts. This kind of psychic voice was not provocative at all. It was like the chirping of birds in spring, full of vitality and soothing to the soul.

However, the next moment, the calm sea suddenly became violent, and the slow psychic voice suddenly became high-pitched and sharp. It was as if the country music had suddenly turned into death metal, wanting to tear the soul into pieces and throw them into the furnace to be destroyed. The mannequins in the training room exploded at the same time and fell to the ground, twitching.

Han Xiao looked from outside for a while before walking into the room. The psychic singing immediately came like a tsunami, and the magical sound entered his brain, making his ears ring. However, they were all blocked by his tough mental barrier and did not cause any substantial damage.

Feidin only retracted his psychic energy when he sensed that an outsider had entered. He slowly opened his eyes and smiled.

"Your Excellency Black Star, why are you here? Are you out of luck again?"

"Let me give you some special treatment."

Han Xiao chuckled and looked at the interface.

"You're a qualified person. I can feel from your psychic energy that you've already touched the Beyond Grade A boundary."

"It's just that I don't know how long it will take to complete the final sublimation."

Feidin did not deny it and shook his head.

He had stayed in the Calamity Grade for a long time and accumulated a lot of experience. He had already touched the threshold of Beyond Grade A, but he had not taken the final step.

In the beginning, he had inherited Chen Xing's Psychic abilities, and he had already walked out of his own path. He had spent a lot of time summarizing his skills and trying to create a new path. He could feel that when his self-created path was completely formed, he would enter the final sublimation and join the Beyond Grade A realm.

In this aspect, the Soul Swapper had helped him quite a bit. This Universal Treasure also had the effect of assisting him in training. It was convenient for him to study the structure of different souls, and from there, he could develop various Psychic skills to perfect his path.

Among the five major systems, other than Esper class, the other four were interactive. Mage and Mechanic class mainly focused on knowledge, and they needed to learn all kinds of things. Pugilists and Psychics focused on pureness.

Pugilists created countless martial arts styles through the development of physical strength, while Psychics developed the soul and mind while also creating many skills systems. Like close-range skills, Psychic attacks had countless 'power exerting skills', mainly divided into Mental, Psychic, Sensory, and Potential branches. There were also various styles under each branch, just like Pugilists.

For example, Kasuyi was most proficient in the Psychic branch, while Feidin was proficient in the Mental branch. It was very rare to see Feidin use violent psychic energy, and most of his skills were of the Mental branch. The Psychic Song that Feidin used was from this branch.

"Don't worry, you will complete the Beyond Grade A transformation very soon."

Han Xiao patted Feidin's shoulder. He looked at the combat information and knew that Feidin was not far from the Beyond Grade A level.

"I hope I can help you when the time comes…" Feidin sighed." In just eleven years, even if I become a Beyond Grade A Super, I won't have enough time to accumulate. I'll probably be cannon fodder on the battlefield. "

"You have to be confident in your luck, and you have the Soul Swapper. No one will use your basic combat power to measure your usefulness."

Han Xiao encouraged.

Feidin did not have the same exaggerated talent as Karlot's [Everlasting Martial Path], but he was the only one who was perfectly compatible with the Soul Swapper. The power of this Universal Treasure depended on Feidin's own strength. Once he entered the Beyond Grade A realm, the Soul Swapper's effect would undergo a qualitative change. Although the soul of the World Tree expert was absorbed by the Mother Tree and could not be transferred completely, he had specially let Feidin test it in small-scale battles. The Soul Swapper could tear the soul of a World Tree member and cause heavy damage. If all the soul was pulled out, the enemy would die on the spot.

After a while, Han Xiao left the room and teleported to a secret location in the Black Star Palace.

...

With a turn of his gaze, he had already arrived outside a potential stimulation training room filled with all kinds of cosmic radiation and immense pressure. Evans stood in the middle of the room, and a gentle light flowed on his body, using the harsh environment to temper himself.

Han Xiao opened the door and walked in. The training room immediately stopped operating. Evans sensed something and turned around.

"Commander, what can I do for you?"

Evans greeted.

Han Xiao waved his hand. "There's no need to be so formal. I'm just here to check on your training."

As he spoke, he sized up Evans and nodded with satisfaction.

Han Xiao had always been planning Esper Ability Absorption for Evans. At this time, his genes were very stable, and all his Esper Abilities had been carefully selected. They were not many but were chosen meticulously, enough to deal with all kinds of complex situations. Not a single Esper Ability slot was wasted, and the combination of abilities was many times better than EsGod's.

At the same time, Evans also absorbed the gene-enhancing ability that increased Esper Ability Cultivation speed. Coupled with his [Highest Grade Esper Ability Affinity Physique], his growth speed was extremely delightful. After many years of bitter training, Evans had already reached the level of a high-level Calamity Grade and was not too far from becoming a Beyond Grade A.

Han Xiao poked Evans, looked at the interface, and said with a smile, "You're in the process of transforming, and it won't be long before you complete your sublimation. I'm afraid I have to congratulate you in advance for becoming a Beyond Grade A. What are your plans then?"

He did not doubt Evans' talent. With [Esper Ability Copy] and [Highest Grade Esper Ability Affinity Physique], it was only a matter of time before he became a Beyond Grade A.

Evans smiled and said steadily, "If not for you, I might still be an ordinary person. You've been helping me improve my strength for the past few decades, and I owe you too much. If you don't mind, I hope to stay in the army and repay this debt."

Han Xiao was quite satisfied with this answer. To be fair, he did not want to let this talent go either.

With his correct guidance and stabilizing himself for the first half of his life, Evans was not the type of Esper who took shortcuts. Instead, he became firm like a rock and made people free from worry.

Furthermore, Evans had always been grateful to him for stimulating his suppressed talent and giving him a new life. His loyalty was probably even higher than Lothaire.

Han Xiao pressed on Evans' shoulder with a smile and said, "Enter Beyond Grade A as soon as possible. I'll give you a gift then."

"What gift?" Evans was curious.

"It's a secret. You'll know when the time comes."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

When Evans enters the Beyond Grade A realm, he would be able to absorb Esper Abilities of the same level. Gaud, who had been locked up in the Spacetime Amber for many years, would be of use. After many years of observation, he was certain that Evans was qualified to accept this gift.

A Super High-Risk Esper Ability like Energy Control definitely could not be wasted. Letting Evans take this Esper Ability was the best way to make use of it, making EsGod's Esper Ability, which he had painstakingly synthesized, become someone else's wedding dress. He would also let this evil guy have a taste of being a victim.

By then, the reaction of the three Universal Civilizations would no longer be a problem. Han Xiao planned to tell them everything EsGod had done. Regardless of whether the three Universal Civilizations believed it or not, they would not turn hostile when there was an attack from the foreign enemy.

As for EsGod's main body, he believed that the Underworld would not mind having another strong man. Before EsGod was captured, he thought that the three Universal Civilizations would release him one day to ask about the World Tree. However, from the start to the end, Han Xiao did not plan to let this extremely dangerous and evil man regain his freedom.

...

The troops at the frontlines had been blocking the World Tree's advancement, and the three Universal Civilizations had also begun their forceful development of the Flickering World. The galactic society was in a state of panic; on the contrary, the training base was in rare peace.

The changes in the battle outside could not interfere with their training plan for the time being. Time passed quickly during the training.

Under Han Xiao's training plan, many of the trainees were overjoyed at their progress. Other than one person, the rest of the trainees were working harder.

After spending a few months in training, Oathkeeper finally sent a message saying that he had gathered another set of keys to the First Sanctum.

Han Xiao had been waiting for this moment. Without any delay, he informed everyone and entered the Sanctum again. Under the gaze of many Holy Accord members, he disappeared into the galaxy.

Chapter 1371: Suspicion and Reaction

A few hours after Han Xiao entered the Sanctum, a group of association members gathered in the secret conference room under the call of Dillon.

"Black Star has finally entered the Sanctum again… What do you guys think?"

While chewing on a fluorescent grass leaf, Dillon gently rubbed his finger and looked at the Beyond Grade As on the table with a scrutinizing gaze.

Everyone remained silent and looked at their companions. No one wanted to speak first.

Seeing this, Dillon removed the blade of grass from his mouth and knocked his fist on the table.

"Since no one is saying anything, let me explain. The last time Black Star went to the Sanctum, he spent about two months. This time should be about the same. I think this is a good opportunity to leave."

Everyone paused and turned to look at him, their gazes uncertain.

Dylan shrugged, waving his hands in response.

"Everyone understands me. I always say what I want to say. The last time Black Star entered the Sanctum, I wanted to make this suggestion. However, I did not know how long Black Star would disappear back then, and everyone was watching to see if the interception could really stop the enemies, so I did not make the suggestion. Now that the battle has changed, the enemies have broken through the interception and will arrive at the three Universal Civilizations sooner or later. At the same time, we also know how long it will take Black Star to enter the Sanctum, so this is a chance to leave the main universe and avoid the war."

Hearing this, everyone's expressions changed. Some were dissatisfied, some were tempted, and some had the intention to watch and see.

"Don't forget, Black Star revived us, and we all owe him a favor. It's not good to leave without saying goodbye."

Someone frowned and objected.

The members of the association were all revivors of the Holy Accord. They did not participate in the war only because they treasured the second life that they had obtained with great difficulty. Because Dillon was good at talking, they let him be the representative for the time being. However, he was not their leader, and they had their own thoughts and opinions as well.

Dillon played with the glowing grass as he calmly stated,

"I won't deny that Black Star has done us a favor, but he will never allow us to leave freely. The purpose of reviving us is just to make use of our strength.

"Right now, he's allowing us to avoid battle, but it's only temporary. As those participants become more and more dissatisfied with us, Black Star will pressure us sooner or later. Just like how he forced the third batch of Revivors to join the battle, he will do the same to us in the future. Therefore, we might as well leave the main universe before it happens or we will end up in a passive position.

While we might let Black Star down, we have to take responsibility for our own lives. Even if he revives us, it doesn't mean we have to accept their orders and sacrifice our lives for him."

Everyone frowned and pondered. These words had also hit the nail on the head. Many people did not dare disobey Black Star because of their feelings, but they were not willing to take the risk either.

"What about the Holy Accord?" someone asked.

Dillon snorted. "Oathkeeper and Black Star are on the same side. If we want to leave, we have to act in secret. We can't inform them."

"If we do this, we will probably be hunted down by Black Star. I don't think we should make such a rash decision," another person said.

Hearing this, Dillon retorted, "Black Star isn't in the main universe, which is why we have the chance to sneak away. Every minute and second we waste now is the time for us to escape. If we wait for him to return, will we be able to leave? Anyway, no matter what you say, I will definitely leave!"

Many of them had conflicted expressions.

The pressure that Black Star put on them was too heavy. Only when he was not around would these people dare to plot and think that this period of time was a rare opportunity to escape.

If Black Star had not entered the Sanctum, they would not have dared act rashly, afraid they would be taught a lesson by Han Xiao.

After discussing for a while, the avoidance faction could only barely reach a consensus. Those who were willing to leave would make their own plans, and those who were unwilling to leave were not allowed to leak the secret, creating another layer of assurance.

As he gazed at everyone debating, Dillon was a little distracted. He played with the grass in his hands as memories of the past flashed through his mind.

He then thought of the Elven Holy Land that he had once created, and he could not help but reminisce about the times when he played with the many consorts in the pure white imperial court. Those beautiful, cold and pure faces flashed past his eyes.

It was a pity that after his death, the Elven Holy Land lost its protection, and these concubines could not control their fate. The identity of a Beyond Grade A widow was like the emperor's harem, enough to attract the interest of many people in the gray area with power and influence.

At this point, although he had come back to life, his old confidants had also long disappeared with time. He had power, but there was nothing he could do.

Dillon's face tightened, and he subconsciously crushed the grass into powder.

"The three Universal Civilizations… not kicking you while you're down is already the last line. How can I help you!"

On the other side, somewhere in the training base.

A group of Beyond Grade As gathered in the room and looked at each other.

The group consisted of the members of the third Revival. Other than the majority of the direct descendants of the civilizations, the remaining neutral Beyond Grade As were all present.

Because they had the same interests, the Beyond Grade As in the third batch of revivals all gathered together privately. The revivals formed a faction, and the free Beyond Grade As formed a faction. Although the three Universal Civilizations had placed everyone under house arrest, they could still communicate privately. After all, they were a group of important combatants, and they could not restrict all their freedom as though they were in prison.

After a while, one of them broke the silence.

"Black Star has gone to the Sanctum. Why did he summon us at this time?"

Everyone immediately turned to look at the initiator of this gathering, a high-level Beyond Grade A named Stein.

Stein was a male Demon with transparent wings, and his outer appearance looked like a moth. Other than his wings and antennae, his other body was shaped like a human. At this moment, his two antennae trembled, making him look nervous.

"I heard some news. The infinite number of times the Sanctum has been revived that Black Star mentioned might be a lie meant to deceive us…"

"What?!"

Hearing this, everyone's expression changed.

The three Universal Civilizations had always controlled the channels and did not allow the third batch of revivors to come into contact with the relevant information. Therefore, they never knew that Han Xiao had once said that the Sanctum Revival could only be done once.

"What exactly is going on?" everyone asked.

Stein quickly explained, "Black Star's explanation to us was different from what he told the other Beyond Grade As when it came to the Sanctum Revival. In the past, he claimed that the Sanctum Revival was only limited to one time, but to us, he said it was unlimited… I only came into contact with this information by chance. There must be a problem!"

"Is the news reliable?!"

"I can't guarantee it, but it's most likely true," Stein said hastily.

Everyone's face turned gloomy as they sunk into their own thoughts.

If Black Star had two theories, the other Beyond Grade As would definitely know about it. However, no one had exposed it yet.

Perhaps, Black Star's words to them were a lie on purpose to trick them into contributing. The other Beyond Grade As were all beneficiaries, so they tacitly agreed to this. Not only did they not expose them, they even cooperated to deceive the third batch of Revivors… This was everyone trying to use them as cannon fodder!

This speculation was probably correct. Based on their perspective, this possibility was completely reasonable and extremely convincing… However, because they misunderstood the key information, their conclusion was completely different from the truth.

The more they thought about it, the more shocked they became.

"Then what should we do now?" someone asked with a deep voice as he took a deep breath to calm his anger.

"If we can only revive once, then this will be our last life, and we have no choice but to consider our path of retreat," Stein mused.

"Are we going to take the opportunity to escape? Although Black Star isn't here, we're being confined in this area, and those Beyond Grade As aren't easy to deal with."

After a heated debate, someone suddenly made a suggestion.

"The situation is still unclear. We will wait for Black Star to come back and revive the Sanctum. We will most likely be invited to watch it together. At that time, we will see if he revives a second death.

"If not, then no matter what reason Black Star gives, we will question him face to face and make sense of it. This way, we will be able to shake the new revivors and the direct descendants of the same batch as us. Together, we will break the restrictions of the three Universal Civilizations and resist the fate of being cannon fodder!"

Hearing this, many people's eyes lit up.

It would be difficult for them to fight back on their own, and the next revival might be an opportunity to seek a temporary alliance.

"Then it's settled. We'll attack together!"

Stein agreed.

Primeval Star River, Mechanical Race territory.

In the mechanical palace, Manison's Lord's Avatar and Kasuyi's remote projection sat opposite each other, casually playing cards.

"I really envy you. You don't have to manage the affairs of the association and can spend all your time digesting the war insights. I want to do the same…"

Kasuyi grumbled as he watched the layout of the cards.

Manison did not mind and casually said, "Since Black Star isn't around, we will need someone to supervise the association. I have long been stripped of my position as president, and I'm not even the vice president. This job is yours."

"Sigh, there's nothing I can do. Before Black Star left, he told me that some of the association members and revivors might not know their place during this period. He told me to be careful of any variables, so I can only do as he says."

Kasuyi shook his head helplessly.

Just like the exploration era in the past, the war had always been the catalyst for the strong. Many Beyond Grade As had been stationed in the interception circle for the past year, and after experiencing all kinds of battles, they more or less had new insights. Manison and Kasuyi had both discovered a wider room for improvement. As long as they were in seclusion for some time, their strength could still improve.

It was a pity that Black Star had gone to the Sanctum and even told him to be careful. Kasuyi could only suppress his desire to digest the war experience in the wormhole and manage the association instead. Thus, he was very envious of Manison being able to focus on training behind closed doors.

"You're thinking too much. I've also encountered some miscellaneous matters," Manison said with a calm tone. "Nilfgadi has been restless recently. He was unwilling to let the Machinery Faith and the Mechanical Race be controlled by Black Star and me. He felt that these benefits were originally his, so he tried to regain his former leader position."

"Oh? What did he do?" Kasuyi was curious.

"Humph, just as Black Star left, he sent people to promote his return to the Machinery Faith. He wants to use his identity as the founder to harvest the believers' main faith. He wants to take advantage of the situation."

"What's the result?" Kasuyi was interested.

"What else can he do? He's the founder who was eliminated by history and only revived because of Black Star. He wants to shake Black Star's position? Dream on." Manison snorted.

"That's true. The prestige of Nilfgadi has long been worn down by time. He still doesn't have the qualifications to compete with Black Star."

Kasuyi nodded, paused, before jokingly saying,

"Furthermore, even you can't beat Black Star, let alone him."

"…Humph, ridiculous."

Manison glanced at him and snorted.

This person really doesn't know where to stop. If we hadn't known each other for so many years, I would have ignored you!

Kasuyi shrugged and asked, "How about the Mechanical Race? It should be quite troublesome for him to return as an ancestor, right?"

"Who do you think I am? I've managed the Mechanical Race for many years, and he wants me to give up my base just because he's an ancestor? Is that possible?" Manison's tone was calm.

"So what did you do to him?"

"If it was in the past, I would have made him into a criminal a long time ago. However, I haven't done such a thing for a long time. After all, Nilfgadi is the ancestor of the Mechanical Race, and I can't do anything to him even if I want to. Therefore, I gave him a batch of Mechanical Race members and told him to set up a new Mechanical Race."

"So, the Mechanical Race has already split up?" Kasuyi raised his brows.

Manison did not take it to heart and said calmly, "It's not that serious. I can hand over some clansmen since they can be replenished. However, he won't get even a single strand of my accumulated wealth."

"Hehe, you're still the same. Other than Black Star, no one can gain anything from you."

Kasuyi shook his head and laughed.

"Humph, even Black Star can't take much advantage of me."

Manison was simply being hard-mouthed.

Kasuyi only smiled and did not expose Manison's stubbornness. He changed the topic and said curiously, "By the way, before Black Star left, he left me a stranger's contact number. Tell me, if those revivors have any abnormal movements, I can find this person to settle it."

"Black Star will not speak without thinking. What's that stranger's name?"

"I don't know his name. Black Star only told me to call him Oathkeeper. I haven't contacted him yet. I wonder what his background is. Even Black Star thinks so highly of him."

Kasuyi seemed quite interested.

"Looks like Black Star still has many secrets." Manison snorted.

World Tree Territory, Tree King Palace.

Dark green lights full of vitality flowed along with the roots and veins into a huge cocoon made of leaves. It looked like the heart of a cabbage, and below it was an opulent base that looked like an altar.

After a long while, the leaves that formed the cocoon suddenly opened layer by layer, and a figure covered in a dazzling green light walked out. He walked down the steps step by step, and the green light slowly faded, revealing the appearance of Subduing Tree King.

"You've finally revived!"

Below the altar, joy flashed in the eyes of Fortitude Tree King who had been waiting for a long time. He took two steps forward to welcome him.

After watering it for so long, Subduing Tree King has finally matured. Now I can finally laze off!

"Phew, I'm still not used to it."

Subduing Tree King let out a breath and moved his body stiffly to rouse his senses.

Although the World Tree could allow him to return to his seed form and be reborn, the process of the seed germinating and maturing was very uncomfortable. The thought of Black Star, who had caused him so much pain, made Subduing Tree King furious.

"I died once. Next time, I'll make that foreigner pay!"

"You will have a chance."

Fortitude Tree King immediately tried to interject.

Subduing Tree King turned to look at him in surprise.

"Why are you here? Where's Heart Tree King?"

"He's dead, sealed by that foreigner," Fortitude Tree King's tone was filled with disdain.

Subduing Tree King frowned, before asking in a solemn tone,

"What happened after I died?"

Fortitude Tree King did not beat around the bush, directly telling him the whole story through the mind network.

After finding out the whole story, the former's expression softened, and he slowly nodded.

"So that's what happened. Heart Tree King restrained the Esper of the Recovery class, which resulted in the successful exchange of attacks. Many high-level combatants of the enemy civilization were killed. Although Heart Tree King was defeated later, the strategic results he created have already laid a good foundation for us. The advantage in numbers is gradually slipping toward us. The high-level combatants of the enemy civilization will only become fewer and fewer in the future. Good job."

"But Ancestral Tree King is not satisfied. Heart Tree King has been captured, and we cannot recover the Tree King Crown," Fortitude Tree King stated.

"It doesn't matter. It's just a crown. We'll find a chance to save Heart Tree King in the future. Using temporary losses in exchange for permanent damage to the enemy is undoubtedly a win for us."

Subduing Tree King waved his hand, not taking it to heart.

"Alright, since you've revived, I'll leave the matters here to you. I'll return to the mother tree first."

Before Subduing Tree King could react, he immediately dispelled his physical body and returned to the World Tree.

"Humph, you still have to rely on me."

Subduing Tree King snorted and had no intention of rejecting. As a Pugilist, he was already used to doing such tiring work.

Chapter 1372: Persuasion and Return

In the blink of an eye, several days passed.

Everything in the training base was the same as before. However, Black Star's temporary departure caused the emotions of many to fluctuate.

After experiencing so many storms, In the eyes of the Beyond Grade As, Black Star was like a stabilizing needle. Under his control, the common interests of the Beyond Grade As continued to extend. To a certain extent, they were gathered under the banner of the Beyond Grade A Association because of Black Star.

Therefore, although Han Xiao said he was going for business and would not be gone for long, everyone still felt as though something was amiss.

Kasuyi was in charge of the overall situation during this period, following Han Xiao's instructions and paying attention to the movements of the many revivors. He originally thought this was just a routine matter, but he did not expect there to be real changes.

A few days after Han Xiao left, Dylan and some of the revivors disappeared. Kasuyi had been paying attention to the movements of the association members, and it did not take long for him to notice this anomaly.

As comrades who stood firmly on the side of the Association against the three Universal Civilizations, the treatment of the first two batches of revivors was naturally different from the third batch. The Association had to consider the feelings of all the members. They would not take away the freedom of this group just because some of the members were unwilling to participate in the battle. Therefore, Dylan and the others were not placed under house arrest like the third batch of revivors.

In shock, Kasuyi immediately investigated and asked those who had yet to leave. Only then did he finally understand that Dylan and the others wanted to take the opportunity to leave. However, no one revealed their route, only saying that Dylan had cast a spell and brought some of his companions into the secondary dimension to leave using this method.

Kasuyi tried to contact Dylan and the others, but they seemed to be determined to leave and could not be contacted at all. Helpless, he thought of the Oathkeeper method that Han Xiao had left for him and turned to this stranger for help.

In the office of the training base, Kasuyi was leaning on a chair. The communicator on the table shot out a cone-shaped light, sweeping out a virtual screen in front of him, showing the image of a dialing phone.

The ringtone rang for a few seconds before the call was picked up. The black communication interface immediately changed, revealing a mysterious figure in a hooded black robe.

Kasuyi looked at this person curiously and said, "I'm Kasuyi. Are you the Oathkeeper that Black Star mentioned?"

"It is I."

Oathkeeper replied calmly and looked at Kasuyi.

The two of them sized each other up, and the atmosphere turned a little strange.

After a few seconds, Kasuyi asked curiously,

"Before Black Star left, he gave me your contact number. He said that if the revivors make any movements, I could ask you for help?"

"He informed me too." Oathkeeper nodded.

"…So, what's your relationship with Black Star? I've never heard of someone like you."

"It's normal that you don't know me. I have a closer relationship with Black Star," Oathkeeper said calmly.

Upon hearing this, Kasuyi's eyes narrowed as all kinds of guesses flashed through his mind.

The existence of the Holy Accord had always been a secret, and he naturally would not know about it.

On the spur of the moment, Kasuyi probed further.

"Are you… Black Star's secret subordinate?"

Oathkeeper's eyes immediately turned sharp. His tone grew solemn,

"You're thinking too much. I'm just an important partner, never his subordinate."

'Really? I don't believe it…'

Kasuyi cursed in his heart. Many members of the association were always putting themselves on a pedestal. They all said that they were not Black Star's subordinates, but they still followed his orders. He was already used to such situations.

After cursing to himself, Kasuyi calmed himself down and curiously asked, "I don't quite understand. What's your relationship with those revivors? Why did Black Star ask me to ask you for help?"

"This is a secret. Black Star didn't tell you, and I can't tell you. You just need to know that I can help. Don't ask too much."

Oathkeeper's tone was calm. He did not know that Kasuyi was also an insider of the truth behind the Sanctum Revival, so he naturally hid it.

Among all the partners of Han Xiao, the Holy Accord was an extremely important existence, and an 'outsider' like Kasuyi definitely could not touch the core secrets. Therefore, when Oathkeeper expressed his stance, it was easy for others to misunderstand that he held a superior position.

Seeing this, Kasuyi secretly curled his lips.

Tsk, you still say that you're not Black Star's secret subordinate. If not, why would you have such a sense of superiority when keeping Black Star a secret?

Seeing that Oathkeeper did not intend to talk much, Kasuyi temporarily gave up the idea of gathering intelligence and told him about Dylan and the others.

After hearing that, Oathkeeper's eyes flickered, and he slowly said, "Dylan? As expected, I'll talk to him."

"He has already blocked all communication from the outside world. You can contact him?" Kasuyi was surprised.

"I have my ways. You don't have to know, Just leave it to me."

Oathkeeper waved and hung up.

Kasuyi mumbled with a strange expression as the communication screen turned black.

"He's so mysterious, I've never even heard of his name before… When did Black Star meet such a guy?"

...

Somewhere in the secondary dimension world, Dylan and the others were riding on the golem vehicles of the elves.

The room was silent. No one spoke. From time to time, they looked at the magic compass which served as a radar, afraid someone would chase after them.

"Everything is going smoothly so far. We have already entered the secondary dimension world. As long as we avoid the three Universal Civilizations' territory, we won't have to worry about being discovered."

The carrier had magical awareness and was reporting the situation. So far, the operation had been going smoothly and did not meet much resistance.

"It will take at least a month for Black Star to return. That much time is enough for us to completely hide. We have no chance of winning the war," one of his comrades said with a chuckle.

Hearing this, all the revivors who had left with Dylan could not help but smile in relief. Only Dylan was the exception, sitting in his seat expressionlessly.

Whoosh—

At this moment, a cluster of black flames suddenly appeared out of nowhere and formed Oathkeeper's mind projection. It appeared in front of Dylan, and the laughter in the room immediately stopped.

"You really came."

Dylan was not surprised at all.

Oathkeeper stared at him and said calmly, "Leaving without saying goodbye isn't appropriate, right?"

"No one knows if the world will explode tomorrow. It can be the last time, so there's nothing to be particular about." Dylan crossed his arms and coldly replied.

"Black Star will be very unhappy if you do this." Oathkeeper's expression was calm.

"I don't care if he's happy or not." Dylan snorted. "If you're just here to chat with me, I welcome it. If you want to persuade me, then forget it. You know that I will never help the three Universal Civilizations."

Oathkeeper shook his head. "I understand the hatred between you and the three Universal Civilizations, and I won't persuade you to let it go. However, leaving the main universe is just an act of escapism."

"Since I owe you guys a favor, I won't take revenge on the three Universal Civilizations. What else can I do if I don't leave? Or do you want to persuade me not to run away and stay behind to make the three Universal Civilizations pay the price in blood?"

Dylan's tone was sarcastic.

Oathkeeper did not mind and instead replied in a calm tone.

"It's normal for you to have complaints, but you have to be forward-thinking in everything you do. Now that we're fighting for the three Universal Civilizations, it's only to protect our hometown, the galactic society. Working together now is just a temporary measure. Even if we win in the end, the three Universal Civilizations still have many irreconcilable conflicts with us… Black Star is tolerant of you. Other than sympathizing with your situation, he also foresaw many conflicts with the three Universal Civilizations in the future. He never asked you to let go of your hatred, so why not wait a while?"

"Humph, I don't doubt Black Star's foresight, but I'm not someone who will easily change my mind. No matter what, I'm not willing to work for the three Universal Civilizations. If you want me to go back, wait until the day you become enemies with the three Universal Civilizations again."

Dylan straightened his back and curled his lips.

Oathkeeper said calmly, "If you run away now and don't join the battle with the association, we won't welcome you even if you return in the future."

"Then I won't be coming back." Dylan pointed at Oathkeeper and said coldly, "Also, pay attention to your words. I'm not your soldier, and neither is the association an army. Don't use the term 'escape'."

Oathkeeper nodded and said calmly, "You've made up your mind to leave. Since that's the case, I won't persuade you. The association doesn't lack you. Just don't regret it."

Then, Oathkeeper turned to look at the other revivors and casually spoke out,

"As for you guys, when Black Star returns from the Sanctum, I will tell you a valuable piece of information. Whether you want to leave with Dylan completely or come back to fight with us, you guys can decide for yourselves."

As soon as he said that, Oathkeeper's mental projection cracked and turned into black sparks before disappearing.

With his identity, he could actually stand out and emphasize the truth behind the Sanctum Revival, proving Han Xiao's words. However, Oathkeeper did not plan to do so now. Firstly, it was his personal wish, and secondly, it was because of Han Xiao's reminder before he entered the Sanctum.

If some of the revivors wanted to take the opportunity to leave, they could do as they wished. There was no need for them to urge others to seek the benefits of eternal life.

Oathkeeper knew that what he needed to do was to use the communication function of the Soul Flame to show these people that Black Star had revived in the Sanctum. At that time, people would return to the Sanctum if they wanted to, and those who still did not care would leave. It would be hard to say who would beg who then. They have to put down the mentality that Black Star and himself would keep asking them to stay.

Seeing Oathkeeper's figure disappear, everyone heaved a sigh of relief. Their eyes flickered as they pondered his words.

Dylan sneered.

"Regret? The word never existed in my dictionary!"

...

Under Kasuyi's control, the departure of Dylan and the others did not cause much of a commotion, but it was inevitable that the other association members would feel a difference.

Most of the people participated in the war and fought on the frontlines, while some of their comrades stayed away from the war and went to the secondary dimensions to enjoy themselves. This made some of the association members feel dissatisfied.

However, as Beyond Grade As, they would not change their decision easily. Although they were a little shaken and dissatisfied, no one followed the actions of Dylan. They only hid their emotions in their hearts and trained silently.

Soon, a month passed.

In a certain space of the Ancient Star Desert, a Holy Sanctum passageway appeared, and a figure was spat out.

"Phew, I'm back…"

Han Xiao shook his head and felt that the symptoms this time were lighter than the last time. He quickly regained his senses, and the many technologies that he had obtained from the First Sanctum were quickly stabilized in his memory palace.

After adjusting his state for a while, he took out his communicator and looked at the time. His lips curled up.

"This time, I only used forty days. My authority has increased by one level, and the time flow has decreased. If this continues, I might be able to come out in a few days."

Han Xiao was in a good mood as he scrolled through the information bar.

He had only left for such a short period of time, and there was nothing else important. Only Kasuyi and Oathkeeper reported to him about the situation of Dylan leaving.

"He slipped away while I was not around… Tsk, I'll deal with him in the future."

Han Xiao curled his lips. Thinking about what kind of person Dylan was, he did not find it surprising.

However, for now, this problem was unimportant. The most important thing was to digest the gains from this trip.

Han Xiao looked down at the back of his hand. The brand of the new Sanctum Revival was glowing, and he could not help but smile.

"This time, I can finally make the Beyond Grade As decide to participate in the battle… I hope the three hooligans can stay calm when they hear this."

Chapter 1373: So, We Were the Ones Lied To!

Black Star Territory, Training Base, Artificial Planet.

On a metal wasteland, many Beyond Grade As were gathered. They stood in groups of two or three, whispering to each other as they waited for Han Xiao to arrive.

The situation had not changed much in the past month. Han Xiao had notified Kasuyi the moment he returned from the Sanctum and told Kasuyi to gather everyone, but he had not arrived yet.

Many of the Beyond Grade As present had already heard from Kasuyi that this gathering was to carry out a new Sanctum Revival. Many of them were filled with curiosity, especially the third batch of Revivors who had yet to witness the process of their revival.

Stein and the others were scattered in the crowd and deliberately did not stand together. Their eyes met occasionally when they turned their heads and communicated with each other with their eyes. They had a tacit understanding of today's plan.

A month ago, when they found out that Han Xiao might have lied about the Sanctum Revival, they did not publicize it openly. Instead, they secretly prepared to question Han Xiao publicly on this special occasion and expose his lie, causing the third group of revivors to be united against a common enemy. Therefore, they were the only ones who knew about it.

On the other side, the association members and the first two groups of revivors were scattered at the edge of the crowd, forming a semi-circle, sandwiching most of the third group of revivors in the middle. On the surface, they were chatting with their companions, but in reality, they were secretly nervous.

They did not have any private plans, and they did not know what Stein and the others were planning. However, everyone knew that Black Star had lied to the third batch of revivors, and it was very likely that he would be exposed today. If the third batch of revivors saw that the people who died twice did not revive, who knew how intense the backlash would be.

Therefore, although many Beyond Grade As did not plan in secret, they stood on their own and formed an obscure encirclement. Although they did not know what excuse Black Star would use to trick the third batch of Revivors, they were all prepared to prevent any unforeseen events from happening today.

"It's a pity that Aurora was defeated in the last battle of the intercepting circle. If she had played her usual role, there might not have been people who died a second time. This way, Black Star's lies could've continued to stabilize these people…"

Everyone secretly glanced at the third batch of revivors. Most of them felt that it was a pity that they could not fool these people for long.

All the Beyond Grade As waited patiently. After a while, a stream of light suddenly broke through the atmosphere and fell from the sky, landing in front of everyone. It then turned around and the sparks disappeared, revealing Han Xiao.

"I haven't seen you guys for more than a month. Are you all thinking about me day and night?"

Han Xiao looked at everyone with a smile, seemingly in a good mood.

"Who is this? How shameless," Milizaus had a look of disdain.

"Want my fart?" Sun Hunter curled his lips.

"Tsk tsk, it's a pity that I already have a crush. Or else, I wouldn't mind welcoming you with my body," Reeve licked his lips shamelessly.

As soon as he returned, it was as if they were injected with vitality. The crowd immediately became lively and started to joke around.

After teasing the others for a while, Han Xiao stopped smiling and showed the Sanctum revival mark.

"Alright, let's get down to business. The sacrificed comrades are still waiting for us to wake them up."

After saying that, he turned around and activated the brand, releasing rays of light.

Everyone quietened down and watched him operate.

The historical Beyond Grade As in the explored universe were limited. The last revival had already used all the mediums that had been gathered, and the mediums of the remaining historical Beyond Grade As had yet to be found. Thus, there were no newcomers this time, all of them were those who had died in the intercepting circle battle.

One after another, the figures of those who died in battle began to materialize.

Stein and the others immediately perked up and stared at the reviving light cluster. Their bodies tensed up, and they all prepared to take action. As long as they did not see the people who died twice in this batch of revivors, they would act according to the plan.

At the same time, the association members also quietly changed their positions. The intention of surrounding them became more obvious. They were tense and prepared to deal with the possible backlash from the third batch of revivors.

Right at this moment, under the watchful eyes of everyone, the light slowly faded. This batch of revivors finally took shape, revealing their faces. They were all familiar.

Stein's eyes quickly swept across and suddenly focused on a few figures. Surprise flashed in his eyes, and he turned to look at his companions.

These figures were among the third batch of Revivors who had died in the interception battle, the Beyond Grade As who had died twice.

"The people who have died twice really revived? Black Star did not lie to us!"

Stein was rather surprised, and his tense body relaxed. He secretly wondered if he had gotten the wrong information.

"Regardless, it's good news that Black Star isn't lying. According to the plan, there's no need to take the risk today."

Stein breathed a sigh of relief.

Since they were not exposed, they had already agreed to keep it to themselves and pretend nothing had happened.

However, at this moment, Stein suddenly thought of something and his mood became strange.

Wait, Black Star did not lie to us. Doesn't that mean…

Stein subconsciously turned to look at the association members beside him and was shocked to find that their expressions were all frozen on their faces. They were staring at the people who had died twice in disbelief.

The other third batch of revivors who did not know the truth looked as usual. They had always thought that Han Xiao was not lying to them, so they had no reaction.

However, the association members who believed that the Sanctum Revival was a one-time thing were completely dumbfounded.

They had originally wanted to help Black Star prevent the backlash after his lie was exposed, but they did not expect to be the ones who were shocked.

Didn't he say that the Sanctum Revival could only be used once? What was going on ‽

The association members could not suppress their emotions and surrounded Han Xiao, squeezing him in the middle.

"Black Star! What's going on?"

Sun Hunter's tiny head was filled with question marks, and he urgently asked what everyone was thinking. Although he did not point it out clearly because he was wary of the reaction of the third batch of Revivors, everyone understood what he meant and stared at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao raised his brows and said, "Didn't I say that there's no limit to the Sanctum Revival? Why are you making a fuss?"

"You, you…"

Everyone stared at Han Xiao, speechless. Only then did they understand.

It turned out that Black Star was not lying to the third batch of Revivors and was telling the truth!

So the one you lied to was us ‽

You made us think that the Sanctum Revival would only revive once, and we had to fight in fear… You really fooled us hard!

Many association members looked at Han Xiao with resentment. If looks could turn into blades, they would have given Han Xiao a beating.

Kant pressed on Han Xiao's shoulder, clenched his teeth, and said in a low voice, "You actually kept it from us…"

Facing the indignant looks of the others, Han Xiao remained calm. He shook Kant's hand and smiled.

"So what? Don't tell me you guys don't feel surprised now."

Without waiting for a response, he tilted his head and continued.

"Don't forget the situation we were in back then. If this matter was exposed at that time, would the three Universal Civilizations still choose to wait and see, giving us some time to accumulate? There could have been internal conflicts long ago, and the current situation would only be worse.

"However, our situation is different now. With the pressure from the enemies, the three Universal Civilizations can't do anything to us. Now that we've revealed the truth, it's good for morale.

Just think about it and you will understand. You won't revive only once, you will find out sooner or later about this matter that is beneficial to the whole of Beyond Grade As. What I hid in the past was just a deceptive tactic from a strategic point of view… Furthermore, I am not the only one who knows. I have long told this secret to a Beyond Grade A who is worth trusting."

As he spoke, Han Xiao looked at Kasuyi and nodded.

Seeing this, Kasuyi stood out and said,

"That's right. Black Star told me about this a long time ago, and I agree with the reason for hiding it. I didn't tell you guys in the past because I wanted to deal with the three Universal Civilizations, but now is the time to make it public…"

Kasuyi supported Han Xiao's words while cursing in his heart. His understanding of the Sanctum came from the Celestial Star Alliance, but when he received Han Xiao's signal, he could only say that it was Han Xiao who told him and played along.

After listening to the explanation, the association members blinked their eyes and calmed down. They pondered over this explanation and had to admit that there was indeed a reason to hide it.

If they took too big a step, they would most likely be in trouble. If Black Star had made this matter public back then, it would have been too much of a threat to the three Universal Civilizations. They would not have let the matter rest and would have probably started an even more intense civil war. Things like the Mechanical Race battle would definitely have happened earlier.

Furthermore, although they had been tricked, this was not a loss to them but a pleasant surprise.

They originally thought that they could only revive once, but it turned out to be an infinite number of times. As long as Black Star could continuously provide the Sanctum Revival, wouldn't that mean they had achieved another form of immortality ‽

Thinking of this, a strong sense of excitement replaced shock!

The eyes of the association members lit up, and their confidence skyrocketed. They felt that Han Xiao was emitting an extremely alluring aura, and they just wanted to hug this golden thigh tightly.

Beiger, who was standing at the side, was shocked. Oathkeeper's instructions flashed through his mind, and he immediately understood that Oathkeeper was also someone who knew about it. He and Han Xiao were colluding together… cough, working together to hide it.

"No wonder he suggested that I join the battle and continue to help Black Star. Those guys who thought that they had used up all their revivals and disregarded Black Star will regret it…"

The thought flashed across Beiger's mind, and he secretly rejoiced.

On the other side, the third batch of revivors who did not know the details looked at the excited group of association members around Han Xiao and were secretly surprised. They did not know why these people were so excited.

While everyone was excited, Manison's Lord's Avatar asked with a confused expression,

"Black Star, you knew that the World Tree would attack, so you hid the truth of the Sanctum Revival to protect the Beyond Grade As and the three Universal Civilizations?"

Han Xiao smiled and did not retort.

Seeing this, the expressions of the Beyond Grade As changed.

Although they were already very impressed by Han Xiao, they could not help but respect him even more.

It turned out that Black Star had long been planning for the safety of the galactic society. For the sake of today's war, he had done so many things in secret to obtain temporary peace… To the entire galactic society, only the phrase 'a great man' could be worthy of such a contribution!

Such a foresight, just thinking about it made everyone gasp in admiration.

Only such a person had the qualifications to be the leader of their entire Beyond Grade A group. His ability was always trustworthy!

Secret Master shook his head and sighed. "Black Star, someone like you probably doesn't need the help of luck."

Don't talk nonsense, I need it very much!

Han Xiao curled his lips.

Then, he turned around and patted Kasuyi.

"There's no need to hide this matter. In a while, tell all the Beyond Grade As, including those who are avoiding the battle, as well as all the Calamity Grades who are training, and tell them the truth about the Sanctum Revival. Tell them that no matter the outcome of the war, only by fighting alongside us now will I let them enjoy this benefit in the future. Otherwise, don't even think about getting a chance to revive in the future."

"Understood."

Kasuyi nodded.

Upon hearing that, the association members felt much better.

Only participants like them would receive special treatment. This was the right way. Otherwise, it would be unfair.

All of a sudden, everyone's determination to join the battle was unprecedented. The confusion and hesitation that they had initially felt instantly disappeared.

Black Star had said that if the three Universal Civilizations lost this war, he would take them away. This meant that the Sanctum Revival would still be a guarantee for their future!

In the hearts of the association members, the importance of Black Star's safety was immediately raised to the highest level. Even if they had to die in battle, they could not let Black Star be in danger. The association's cohesiveness instantly exploded!

Seeing how motivated everyone was, Han Xiao smiled. He knew that the most basic goal had been achieved.

Then, he stopped smiling and turned to look at the direct Beyond Grade As who were equally shocked.

It's time to have a chat with the three Universal Civilizations…

In the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations.

Today was the day Han Xiao was going to perform Sanctum Revival. However, because they had seen it the last time, and since the people who were going to revive this time were the ones who died in the war, Marbruce and the others did not pay much attention to it. Instead, they discussed the situation of the harassment battle at the frontline with the Military Strategy Department.

As for the situation of the Sanctum Revival this time, some supervisors paid attention to it. The three of them did not watch it with their own eyes and waited for the report.

A meeting was being held in the room, and the remote projections of Simon and the other military officials were reporting.

"…This is the current situation. The harassment troops at the frontline have already done their best, but the World Tree Army is steadily advancing and cannot be stopped…"

Marbruce, Louis, and the Pope were listening attentively to the battle report.

Beep beep beep—

Suddenly, the sound of emergency communication rang out, interrupting the report from the military personnel.

Louis frowned and opened the emergency communication channel. "What's going on?"

"Your Excellencies, the Sanctum Revival is complete!" The supervisor's anxious voice sounded in the channel.

"Okay, got it. Write a report for us later. I have an important battle conference to attend."

Louis did not think much of it and was about to hang up.

However, right at this moment, the supervisor suddenly yelled out. His tone was filled with anxiety and panic.

"This time, Black Star revived the direct Beyond Grade As who died in battle twice. Your Excellencies… the Sanctum Revival is not limited to once. What he said about it being limitless might be true!"

[EMPTY]

Just as the words landed, the three of them were stunned for a moment before standing up with a shocked expression!

Chapter 1374: The Game With Confirmed Victory

After stabilizing the Beyond Grade As, Han Xiao submitted a meeting request to the three Universal Civilizations which was quickly passed through.

As soon as he arrived at the conference room, he saw the solemn expressions on the faces of Marbruce and the other two. The atmosphere in the room was heavy, and for some reason, it felt as though there were three trials.

Han Xiao was not bothered by this. He ignored their sharp gazes and said with a smile, "You guys don't look too good. Have you been too tired recently?"

Marbruce did not respond. "Black Star, you tricked us."

Louis and the Pope also tensed their faces and looked serious.

Ten minutes ago, when they received the report of this revival, they were shocked and immediately stopped the battle conference regarding the frontline situation to discuss this matter.

A few years ago, when the Revivors were born, Black Star had claimed that the Sanctum Revival was a one-time thing, and the three Universal Civilizations had also suspected it. However, only Black Star could enter the Sanctum and they had no way of verifying the truth. They could only obtain the relevant information from Black Star and they had always been on the passive side.

Even now, although the three Universal Civilizations were still skeptical, they had accepted the fact that the Sanctum Revival was a one-time thing and had made the main plan based on this. However, the sudden change at this moment had disrupted many of their plans.

Although the Military Strategy Department had made contingency plans for this kind of situation, in the current situation, no plan could deal with this situation perfectly.

In their shock, the three of them were just about to come up with a new strategy when Han Xiao requested to meet them. The three of them stopped their discussion and suppressed their chaotic thoughts, planning to hear Han Xiao first.

"Is that so? Then I'm honored." Han Xiao spread out his hands and smiled. "Don't forget how the three Universal Civilizations planned to deal with us back then. We were on opposite sides, and I used a tactic to trick you guys. I don't think there's anything wrong with that. It only proves that I did a good job."

"You must be very proud now." The Pope snorted.

"No, I don't feel anything." Han Xiao shook his head and said with a playful tone, "Besides, why do you guys look like you're at a disadvantage? A group of high-level combatants who can revive multiple times just happens to be at odds with the World Tree. Isn't this good news for the battle, or do you guys still have some bad intentions?"

Hearing the mockery in Han Xiao's tone, the Pope's face was expressionless, but he was furious.

During the negotiations back then, they had played a hidden risk game with Black Star, using the Beyond Grade A Association's independent political position as a bargaining chip in exchange for the association joining the battle.

One of the reasons the three Universal Civilizations agreed to it was because they hoped the war would reduce the Beyond Grade As of the Association, using external forces to clean up the high-level combatants and reduce the hidden dangers of Beyond Grade As. This way, they would not have to fight internally and waste strength.

The starting point of this plan was the one-time use of the Sanctum Revival. However, this was a trap that Han Xiao had dug long ago. When the three Universal Civilizations agreed to the deal, they had already lost this game. It was equivalent to the association getting a free political position without suffering any losses as the three Universal Civilizations wished.

The three of them had also realized that Black Star was trying to gain something without risking anything of his own. He had benefited greatly from them and now that he had revealed his trump card, they were filled with hatred. They knew that they had fallen into his trap.

The pressure from the foreign enemies was huge, and the three Universal Civilizations could not focus on this game for the time being. Instead, they did not mind expanding the size of the high-level combatants. However, this was still a potential strategic direction. From the looks of it, this plan to ease the imbalance of the Supers had failed.

If they had known that there was no limit to the Sanctum Revival back then, they would not have chosen this game path. Unfortunately, the boat had already sailed and they could only swallow their losses, temporarily not having the energy to fight among themselves.

Marbruce took a deep breath and slowly said, "It is indeed as you said. This is good news for the battle. Black Star, we hope you can give us a definite answer. What is the situation with the Sanctum Revival? Is it really not limited to one time?"

The other two stared at Han Xiao without blinking.

Han Xiao did not give a definite answer. "Theoretically, there's no limit."

"Theoretically?"

The three of their hearts skipped a beat, and they looked at each other with an expression that said, "What are you playing at this time?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin and raised his brows. "Every Beyond Grade A individual can revive an unlimited number of times, but there is a limit to the number of people who can revive in the Sanctum."

"What do you mean?" Marbruce frowned.

"Activating the Sanctum Revival requires authority. Every time the Sanctum is opened, the activator's authority will increase by one level, and the number of times an individual can revive will be recorded. Every additional revival requires a corresponding level of authority… Let me explain it to you this way. If you die twice, then the third revival requires a level three authority, which means that only the person who opens the Sanctum for the third time can do it. If a new person opens the Sanctum halfway, the authority will not be enough," Han Xiao said with a wave of his hand.

Hearing this, the three of them exchanged looks.

"What you mean is, it's best to make the emissary who opens the Sanctum remain the same person till the end?" Louis looked at Han Xiao up and down and said with a deep voice, "Why do I feel like you're lying to us again?"

Black Star had already entered the Sanctum many times. If there was really such a thing as the authority, it would definitely be beneficial to him. If the war became critical, even if they could unravel the secret of the Sanctum in the future, the best candidate would still be Black Star. A new member would not be able to make the most of it.

"When you guys enter the Sanctum one day, won't you know if the authority is real or fake?"

Han Xiao did not think much of it. He did not care if the three of them suspected him.

The Sanctum mission from the past had yet to be completed. He used this excuse to build a foundation for it. It might be useful in the future.

Seeing this, the three of them felt a headache coming on.

Black Star was certain that they would not be able to prove the Sanctum's mechanism. He was not afraid of being exposed no matter what!

There was no way he could get an answer if he kept asking. Marbruce had no choice but to change the topic.

"No matter what, this is good news to boost morale. Are you planning to announce it to the entire galactic society?"

"There's no need. The World Tree has yet to reach the mainland. There's no need to let the people know so early. It's enough for the upper echelons and some of the chosen ones to know."

Han Xiao waved his hands casually.

Marbruce nodded. Suddenly, he paused and changed the topic.

"Black Star, we know each other very well, so let's not make empty talks… Thinking about it carefully, it's understandable that you hid it from us back then. If we knew about the truth of the Sanctum Revival long ago, we would not have been able to sit still as we did back then, and a large-scale clean-up would have started. You knew about the intelligence of the World Tree long ago, and to maintain the internal balance, you had put in a lot of effort. But what I'm curious about is… if a large-scale civil war had broken out, what would you have done?"

"Hmm, I wanted to delay as much as possible and give us more time to prepare, but if you had insisted on acting willfully, I was also prepared to reveal the existence of the World Tree to you in advance and divert the conflict."

Han Xiao did not hide his original thoughts. He smiled and continued.

"However, you found the World Tree on your own, which is a good thing for me."

He only said half of what he wanted to say. Back then, he had not managed to gather the second set of keys and was worried that the three Universal Civilizations would get serious. This lie was also part of the empty fort strategy, but he naturally did not have to reveal it to the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations. There was no need to let them know that they had missed the real opportunity to 'clean up'.

The three of them shook their heads with complicated emotions.

Indeed, if not for the Research Department discovering the World Tree and Black Star taking the initiative to inform them, they would most likely have treated it as Black Star's stalling tactic and would not have stopped. They might have continued to push for internal cleansing, and that would have been bad.

At least from the current situation, the three of them had to admit that Black Star's actions had brought them a good result. There was no large-scale internal conflict that consumed their strength, just like how Black Star had hidden the World Tree's existence for many years. However, the three of them did not like this kind of passive position. Even though they knew that it was beneficial, they could not be happy.

"As expected of the receiver of the Stuarts Peace Prize, you're really great," Louis snorted. Three parts were sarcasm, and three parts sincere. The remaining four parts were gloom.

"You're too kind. I'll take it as a compliment." Han Xiao chuckled. "Since you guys already know what to do, I won't disturb you anymore."

The purpose of this meeting had already been achieved. Han Xiao did not continue to chat with the three of them. He deactivated the remote projection and thoughtfully left them alone. He knew that the three of them still needed some time to accept the truth.

Seeing Han Xiao's figure disappear, the three of their faces immediately fell.

"Originally, I wanted to use the foreign war to weaken the combat power of the association, but it seems like there's no chance," Marbruce sighed helplessly.

"If that's the case, it will be very difficult for us to clean up individual strength. The total number of Beyond Grade As will continue to increase, and it will not decrease anymore." There was a hint of fear in the Pope's tone.

The three of them looked at each other and could not help but sigh. Their hearts were filled with seriousness and helplessness.

The threat of the World Tree was too great, and they did not dare drag their feet in the war. Even though they knew that it would create a huge problem of imbalance in the Supers in the future, they did not have the extra energy to deal with it.

Furthermore, they still had to rely on the Beyond Grade As to deal with the high-level combatants of the World Tree. What could they do? They could only watch and not dare do anything. If they forced Black Star away, the consequences would be unimaginable!

"As expected of the leader of a Beyond Grade A group. He chose good timing!" Louis emphasized heavily, his face ashen.

Not to mention the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade As who witnessed it with their own eyes were still extremely excited as they accepted this reality. With Kasuyi and the others spreading it, the news of the Sanctum Revival reached the entire training base.

All the Calamity Grade Supers who were undergoing training felt their emotions boiling!

They had thought that stepping into the Beyond Grade A realm would only grant them a second life, but who would have thought that this was the ticket to eternal life ‽

The attraction between the two was completely different!

The Calamity Grade Supers were extremely excited. The temptation of eternal life became the source of motivation, and almost everyone turned into a cultivation maniac in an instant. Even Lagi, who was extremely disheartened, secretly increased his training volume.

On the other side, Beiger received Han Xiao's approval and secretly sent the news back to the Holy Accord Organization.

Ancient Star Desert, Holy Accord Organization base.

Many Holy Accord Revivors forced Oathkeeper to a corner with their strong bodies. Their faces were filled with disbelief and shock.

"Did you already know the truth and had been working with Black Star to deceive us ‽"

"Damn it! You kept us in the dark!"

"Say something!"

The group of revivors started talking at the same time.

Oathkeeper pushed through the crowd with a calm expression.

"That's right. Black Star had already analyzed the pros and cons. I also agreed with his plan back then. If you guys have any objections, go find him. After all, without his support, I won't be able to open the Sanctum. He has the main responsibility."

Hearing this, everyone was stunned.

Even though they were talking in private, they did not dare look for Black Star to express their dissatisfaction.

Furthermore, they had thought that they would only be able to revive once in the past and had already used it up, so their attitude toward Black Star was more or less a little casual. At this moment, everyone present immediately felt guilty and quickly recalled if they had respected Black Star before.

After a while, one of the Primordial Ones asked,

"Since there's no limit to the number of revivals, can we enjoy this treatment forever?"

Oathkeeper looked at him and slowly said, "Didn't you hear what Black Star said? Only by fighting alongside them can we obtain unlimited revivals in the future."

Hearing this, the Holy Accord Revivors present were shocked.

"We're doing the same ‽"

"What else?" Oathkeeper was expressionless. "The first revival is free. We can't expect it to be free forever, right? Everyone is treated equally. There's no reason for you guys to enjoy such benefits while living in seclusion. If you want this kind of treatment, you have to contribute. Black Star's intentions are my intentions as well."

The faces of many Holy Accord Revivors twitched.

They were all people who lived in seclusion and had rejected the invitation to leave. Initially, when they saw the association fighting to the death on the frontlines, they felt that they were not involved at all and were overjoyed. But now, it seemed like Black Star was using the benefits that they could not reject to force them to leave their seclusion!

Live in seclusion? Did they think that he was starting a charity? Don't even think about it!

Many of the Holy Accord Revivors understood this point, and their expressions immediately changed. Some of their eyes flashed with ominous intent.

If they worked together to snatch away the Sanctum information stored in the Holy Accord, they might not have to care about Black Star's coercion…

However, before they could finish their thoughts, Oathkeeper spoke with a calm tone.

"I suggest that you guys don't take the risk. That would be a waste of energy. The Sanctum Revival requires authority. Currently, only Black Star has opened the Sanctum multiple times and has sufficient authority. Furthermore, Black Star isn't as gentle as me. It's best not to make a huge mistake, or the Underworld can grant you eternal life as well."

The crowd fell silent.

After more than ten seconds, a Revivor suddenly walked out from the crowd with a righteous expression.

"My hometown is in danger, and everyone should contribute their strength. I'm ashamed to stay here and watch the show. It doesn't matter if I revive or not. I just want to join the battle!"

Everyone was surprised. They did not expect this person to be so thick-skinned.

However, the next moment, everyone followed suit. Their faces were filled with righteousness, and their facial lines became extremely firm. Even their style changed.

"That's right. How can we allow the enemy to trample on our territory? I will offer my heart to the world I love!"

"My home has been invaded. My heart hurts too much. My sword is Black Star's sword. I'm willing to die for my home!"

"Justice will never be absent!"

Everyone shouted and expressed their stance. It was as if they had all become warriors willing to protect their homeland. Their bodies were shining with righteous light, and they could not wait to rush to the battlefield.

There was no lack of people who had grudges with the three Universal Civilizations, but they knew what was more important. In the face of the temptation of eternal life, the grudges of the past could be held back for the time being, because the future was limitless.

Most Beyond Grade As had pride, but they also knew how to be flexible. In the face of almost eternal benefits, they could put aside all minor conflicts. Not many Beyond Grade As would be trapped by the past.

Oathkeeper was not surprised by the Holy Accord Revivors' choice. No one knew the allure of the Sanctum Revival better than him, and he had already expected this scene.

As long as they could grasp the path of the Sanctum Revival, there was no need to care about what the Beyond Grade As were thinking. This was the lifeline of countless Beyond Grade As. If they were given a hundred chances to choose, the result would be the same.

Oathkeeper raised his hand and summoned a cluster of Soul Flames, which reflected Dylan's figure.

"I wonder if you can make me see you differently…"

Chapter 1375: Your Feud Has Nothing to Do with Me.

This was a secondary dimension. The sky was filled with a fluttering ribbon-like aurora. A high-speed stream of light passed through it. It was the magic vehicle of Dylan and the others.

After sailing for more than a month, they had already left the area controlled by the three Universal Civilizations. The initial vigilance of Dylan and the others gradually became relaxed.

A month ago, Oathkeeper had used mental projection to meet them and then disappeared. They were all Revivors of the Holy Accord and knew the effects of Soul Flame very well. They knew that Oathkeeper could only talk to them and could not lock onto their location, so they were not worried about exposing their coordinates.

"It's been so long. It's about time for Black Star to return from the Sanctum. Oathkeeper said he would tell us something valuable, so he should be here soon."

A Beyond Grade A teased the furry pet on the table and casually mentioned this.

The other person was in a small ecological area in the cabin, watering and nourishing the decorative plants. Hearing this, he turned around and smiled. "Oathkeeper seems to want to use this news to change our minds. I want to know what he will say."

The revivors in the cabin were all doing their own things, but everyone was present. All of the Beyond Grade As who left the main universe with Dylan a month ago were there.

Other than their special relationship, the Beyond Grade As were not willing to submit to others, and they did not treat Dylan as their leader. The reason they had yet to part ways was mainly because of the risks of dealing with the secondary dimensions. After all, this place was still a threat to normal Beyond Grade As.

Someone turned to look at Dylan. "I'm quite curious. What about you?"

"I'm not curious at all." Dylan closed his eyes to rest, not even bothering to open them. "Since you've chosen to leave, be firm. You're all Beyond Grade As, don't you have any backbone? Anyway, no matter what he says, I won't go back."

Everyone laughed and was about to say something when black sparks suddenly appeared in the cabin and quickly formed Oathkeeper's mental projection.

Seeing this, Dylan's brows twitched, and he slowly opened his eyes. The other Revivors' expressions also changed slightly, and they stopped smiling. They stopped what they were doing and stared at Oathkeeper.

"You're here again." Dylan narrowed his eyes. "What, you still want to persuade me to go back?"

"It's up to you to return. I'm just here to deliver the information."

Oathkeeper did not want to bother with him and turned to look at the other curious Revivors. A black flame ignited on his palm, and blurry images flashed in it, containing the information of the Sanctum Revival.

With a light flick of his finger, sparks shot out and fused into everyone's foreheads, transmitting the information directly into their mind. The sequence of events was clear at a glance, and the relevant memories were released, allowing them to check.

The next moment, everyone received this information and was instantly dumbfounded.

"So the Sanctum Revival isn't a one-time thing ‽ You and Black Star have been hiding it from us!"

Many people's expressions changed drastically as they glared at Oathkeeper. Their expressions were indescribably ugly, as though they had fallen into a pile of feces.

"The choice is yours."

Oathkeeper was too lazy to say anything else. He left a sentence, deactivated his mental projection, and disappeared in front of everyone.

Seeing him leave, everyone's expressions changed.

One of the revivors looked around before looking at the shocked Dylan. "Everyone, I'll go back and take a look. We'll meet again if fate allows it."

After saying that, he ignored everyone's reaction and directly flashed out of the carrier. He raised his hand to cast a spell, summoned a fixed teleportation gate, and directly stepped in, disappearing along with the door.

This became a signal. The revivors took their leave one after another, using various methods to leave. Those who were patient would say their goodbyes and those who were not would leave without saying a word. There was no need to explain anything to these temporary companions.

They were all people who had been revived. They left the main universe because they thought that the one-time Sanctum Revival was useless to them, this was their last life. However, only now did they realize that this was just a scam created by the Holy Accord and Black Star. However, the reason was no longer important to them. The Sanctum Revival was almost eternal. There was nothing to hesitate about in front of this benefit.

The group of friends left one after another. Very soon, the cabin that had been quite lively a while ago became empty, leaving only Dylan alone.

He did not care about the others leaving at all. He was still immersed in shock and muttered to himself,

"No wonder, no wonder. Black Star has never cared about us, the avoidance faction. So, he had this trump card…"

The opportunity of eternal life was right in front of him, but…

Dylan's expression changed, and he was extremely conflicted.

...

A few days later, in the conference room on the top floor of the training base.

Han Xiao sat at the head of the table and looked around at the Beyond Grade As present. Seeing that everyone was staring at him, he casually said:

"Everyone already knows about the true situation of the Sanctum Revival. I believe there's no need for me to repeat the unnecessary explanation. Everyone should have digested this information over the past few days. Today, I gathered everyone to discuss the follow-up issue of the Sanctum Revival. This will be an important trump card for us to fight the World Tree. The three Universal Civilizations are very surprised by this and have decided to continue to support us and keep it a secret for the time being…"

The people present nodded silently with subtle expressions.

They believed that there was indeed a surprise, but it was more of a shock. Even if they used their butts to think, they could imagine how the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations felt when they found out about this 'surprise'.

They had been looking for Han Xiao for the past few days, but after Han Xiao used the Sanctum Revival, he had left temporarily and could not be contacted at all. He had only just returned and gathered all the Beyond Grade As in the training base.

All the participating Beyond Grade As had been waiting for the meeting and immediately rushed over.

Han Xiao took in everyone's expressions, tapped the table, and chuckled.

"By the way, let's count your opinions today and see if you're willing to continue participating in the battle. After all, from now on, participating in the battle will be linked to the revival treatment of the Sanctum. I need to record it in the register. Who knows, some people might not like this treatment, but I can't force them. After all, I'm a very democratic person."

Democracy? Bah, shameless!

Everyone cursed silently.

Black Star had grasped this lifeline, and his authority had already risen to a whole new level to the point that whatever he said went. No one would be willing to give up this opportunity.

Although they were complaining in their hearts, the Beyond Grade As present were still very honest and could not wait to speak.

"Count me in!"

"There's no reason to give up halfway. Of course, we should continue fighting."

Everyone expressed their stance enthusiastically.

Initially, some from the third batch of revivors did not fight and did not participate in the interception battle. However, after seeing the substantial evidence of the Sanctum revival, they changed their minds.

Han Xiao smiled as he watched this scene. He opened a virtual screen, pulled out a memo, and recorded the names of the people who expressed their stand in front of everyone.

'The temptation of the limitless Sanctum Revival is indeed something that not many people can resist. The effect is similar to what I expected…'

A few days ago, Han Xiao had received Oathkeeper's report. Upon learning that the Revivors of the Holy Accord had also requested to come out and join the battle, he had gone to deal with the matter in the past few days. He had appeased the group of Holy Accord Revivors and said that they would only need to take action when the World Tree invaded the mainland. There was no need for them to come out now, and they could continue to hide in the dark as long as they accepted his targeted training plan.

The reason those Holy Accord Revivors had stayed in seclusion was partly that they were unwilling to continue being involved in the conflict between organizations, and partly because they had a grudge against the three Universal Civilizations. However, they had all abandoned their original intentions and changed their minds. Although they spoke nicely, their actions were still realistic. Beyond Grade As who knew their own needs would make rational choices.

Of course, Han Xiao would not scoff at them. It was only human nature. Not many people could watch others enjoy such benefits without getting a share.

Just as everyone was expressing their stance, the conference room door was suddenly pulled open, interrupting the meeting.

Everyone turned to look and could not help but have a playful look on their faces. They saw that the revivors of the avoidance faction who had stayed on Planet Finn had all arrived.

The room immediately fell silent. This group of people who had stayed behind to avoid the battle stood by the table.

Han Xiao glanced around, put on a calm expression, and casually said, "Why are you guys here? What's the matter?"

Hearing this, one member of the avoidance faction stepped out from the crowd and spoke loudly like the representative of everyone.

"Your Excellency Black Star, after careful consideration, we have made a unanimous decision. Please allow us to join the training. We request to join the battle!"

The Beyond Grade As present exchanged looks, shook their heads, and laughed, not surprised at all.

Han Xiao smiled, nodded, and said, "As I said before, if you change your mind one day, we welcome you to fight alongside us."

With that, he snapped his fingers, and with a flash of Mechanical Force, the conference table suddenly moved. Mechanical particles extended, and the table slowly expanded. The seats slid sideways leaving more gaps and new seats rose from the ground.

After doing this, Han Xiao pointed at the empty seats and chuckled.

"Everyone, please take a seat."

Seeing this, the revivors of the avoidance faction heaved a sigh of relief. They nodded and thanked him one after another before finding empty seats to sit down.

Initially, they had wanted to watch from the sidelines as the group of association members attacked the enemy at the frontline. However, after learning the truth about the Sanctum Revival from Beiger, everyone changed their minds overnight and decided to join the battle.

Initially, they were worried that Black Star would make things difficult for them, or at the very least, some people would make sarcastic remarks. However, they realized that this group of participants looked at them like it was a matter of course and no one teased them about their choice. This made their nerves relax. However, thinking about it, since they were all alike, no one would laugh at the other.

Sun Hunter glanced at them and said, "Why are there so few of you? There are still some people, right? Where's that foul-mouthed Elf King?"

"They…" A former member of the avoidance faction paused for a moment before smiling helplessly." They are not willing to get involved in the war and have already left the main universe. No one can contact them. "

Everyone was surprised. Not everyone knew about this. Kasuyi had hidden the news.

"Then they really made a huge loss, missing out on such a good thing." Sun Hunter clicked his tongue in wonder.

The corners of many people's mouths curled up, secretly mocking them. Since they had chosen this path, they would have to walk it even if they had to kneel. They would not feel pity for these guys who had a severe lack of judgment and ran away.

"They still don't know the truth about the Sanctum Revival, right? Should we try to get them back?" Milizaus turned around and asked.

Han Xiao did not mind and said calmly,

"Our association is not an organization that cannot be left once entered. They have the freedom to leave. Don't bother about them…"

Halfway through, he suddenly paused, chuckled, and continued.

"Besides, didn't they come back on their own?"

After saying that, everyone noticed it too. They turned to look at the bright starry sky outside the window and saw a teleportation gate spinning open. Streams of light landed on the training base.

Very soon, the sound of footsteps could be heard from afar. They were getting closer and closer. Everyone turned to look at the opened door. Under everyone's gaze, all the revivors of the avoidance faction appeared at the entrance and walked in one after another. Dylan was the last.

Kasuyi calmly took a sip of the Spirit Concentration Tea. The group of people that had just returned contacted him one after another since they could not find Black Star. He arranged for them to appear together today, separately from the other group that stayed behind to avoid battle. However, only he and Han Xiao knew about this.

"Yo, we were just talking about you guys. Didn't you say you were going to stay away from the war? Why are you back?"

Sun Hunter winked and teased.

The others also had a mocking expression on their faces. Their eyes kept sweeping past Dylan, who was at the end of the line. They still remembered that Dylan was the most determined member of the avoidance faction. They could still remember how he had slammed the table and objected to the battle in the past, but now, he was silent, expressionless, and looking straight ahead. It was as if he saw everyone else as air and did not even look at them after entering the room.

Dylan ignored Sun Hunter and looked at Han Xiao. "Black Star, we wish to participate in the war. Do you agree?"

The others stopped talking and turned to look at Han Xiao, waiting for his decision.

Han Xiao looked at this group of people and knocked on the table. Another batch of empty seats appeared on the ground.

"Have a seat."

Seeing this, the group of people finally relaxed, not daring to look into Han Xiao's eyes. They quickly sat down after bowing.

Seeing that Han Xiao had no intention of talking to him, the anxiety in Dylan's heart dissipated a little. He found a seat and sat down obediently.

Before he came back, he had been worried about being punished. After all, he had always been against the war, so it was very likely that Black Star was not willing to accept him. He did not have much confidence and felt that he would be mocked no matter what. He did not expect Black Star to treat him the same way, as though he did not care about him at all.

This time, Sun Hunter curled his lips and looked at Dylan with disdain.

"Tsk tsk, didn't you say that you would never regret it? Didn't you say that you have a deep grudge? Weren't you quite stubborn? I am disappointed in you."

Dylan did not mind. He could not help but retort, "Do I need you to think highly of me? Whatever I do is my freedom. Can't I change my mind? To make you think highly of me, I have to give up the chance to live forever? Who do you think you are?"

He had always done what he wanted. If he cared about what others thought, he would not have died so miserably in the past.

After a series of internal conflicts, he finally chose the opportunity to live forever. Although the hatred in the past was unforgettable, it did not blind his rationality. He was not willing to fight for the three Universal Civilizations. Hatred was one factor, and another was the lack of benefits. Now that the truth of the Sanctum revival was right in front of him, he naturally knew which was more important. There were endless possibilities as long as he was alive. The disdain of others did not hinder him from making the right decision.

"Humph, I'll kill you one day." Sun Hunter snorted coldly and turned around, too lazy to argue with this guy.

The others also looked away. For the sake of important benefits, not many Beyond Grade As would be affected by the opinions of others. It was fine to tease them in their hearts, but there was nothing to look down on since they could understand their choice.

Han Xiao ignored them and waited for everyone to quiet down before continuing with the main topic.

Not long after, the simple meeting ended, and everyone dispersed.

Just as Dylan was about to leave, Han Xiao's voice sounded from behind him.

"Stay for a while."

Everyone paused and looked back at the calm Han Xiao with a contemplative look. They then sped up and left the room, leaving only the two of them.

Dylan's expression froze, and he turned around to look at Han Xiao. He did not dare meet Han Xiao's indifferent gaze, so he forced himself to ask,

"What's the matter?"

Han Xiao tilted his head and pretended to be confused. "You incited the members to leave the association. Don't tell me you think this matter is over just like that?"

"…What do you want to do?"

Dylan's heart skipped a beat. Although he had a foul mouth, that was because of his personality. He was not really afraid of anything.

Han Xiao did not reply immediately.

"Your past was indeed tragic. However, this isn't an excuse for your repeated incitement. Are you the only one here who has a grudge against the three Universal Civilizations? But you are the only one who jumped the gun like this.

I don't care about your hatred. That's your private matter. How you deal with it has nothing to do with me. I don't pity you either. You deserve to be beaten to death. I only care about whether my plan can be carried out as usual, whether the battle can progress smoothly. You've obstructed me many times, you should pay a price…"

"I've already let go of my hatred and am willing to come back and work for the three Universal Civilizations. What else do you want ‽"

Dylan said with a deep voice.

"What does it have to do with me whether you let go of your hatred or not? Do you think that just because you've overcome your own difficulties, I'll let you have your way? If there's no chance of eternal life, will you come back? I'm only concerned about whether you can be of use!"

Han Xiao did not buy it.

"But you came back of your own accord, and you did make the right choice. No path leads to darkness, so I'm giving you a chance."

"What are you going to do?"

Dylan clenched his fists and backed away carefully.

"If you hadn't taken the initiative to return today, I would have hunted you down and not let you have the chance to encounter the World Tree and leak intelligence. I believe your companions would have been very happy to expose your route. After you had died, I would have sent you to the Underworld to serve the war forever.

"However, I'm very satisfied with your return, so I won't kill you. But I still need to send an unstable factor like you to the Underworld, but I promise that after the war ends, I will remove your heroic spirit status and use the Sanctum Revival to return you to normal. You will also obtain eternal life in the future…"

As he spoke, Han Xiao slowly stood up, rubbed his fists, and narrowed his eyes.

"I hope you can fight back. You talk senselessly all the time. I've always wanted to beat you up and cure your mouth!"

Chapter 1376: Violent Beating and Establishing Power

"What do you think Black Star intends to do, making that annoying bastard stay behind?"

The Beyond Grade As walked out of the conference room and left along the corridor. Sun Hunter's tiny body floated midair as he followed the crowd.

Kant shrugged and fiddled with the thrusters on the back of Manison's Lord's Avatar. "It's definitely not anything good."

Secret Master looked down at the light of the enchantment tattoo and said calmly,

"I did divination just now. Dylan's luck is dark, and there seems to be a bloody disaster."

"Hmm, looks like Black Star is planning to teach him a lesson. He deserves to be beaten up."

Sun Hunter smacked his lips and chuckled.

Just as they were guessing, there was a loud explosion behind them!

Bang!

A powerful shockwave suddenly came from behind, causing everyone to stagger.

The Beyond Grade As turned around in surprise, only to see that the corridor they had come from had exploded into pieces. The conference room was at the center of the explosion, and it had already turned into a huge hole. The changes in the internal and external pressure exerted a shocking suction force, sucking away a large pile of junk. Two streams of light intertwined and soared into the sky, instantly entering the universe.

The group of people looked up in surprise and realized that the psionic energy in the sky was exploding, and magic power was surging. Han Xiao was fighting with Dylan. His black robe danced, and dark blue psionic energy shot out, colliding with the spells that Dylan was continuously releasing.

"Whoa, they're fighting!"

"Hit him hard, Black Star. I support you mentally!"

"Count me in. Punch him a few times on my behalf."

Be it the association members or the direct members of the civilization, all of them had gathered. They looked up at the two people fighting in the sky through the open hole.

With Dylan's lacking social relations, no one went up to help him. Everyone was watching the show with gloating expressions.

In outer space, Dylan kept trying to pull away from Han Xiao, but he was stuck to him. Because it was a close-range attack, Dylan could not react in time and was flustered. His fair face was punched a few times and was slightly swollen.

Dylan hurriedly took out a magic tool, and his magic power circulated along the complicated circuits. The elven secret skill was released, and thin blue and green light ribbons quickly extended out. They were densely packed, and the light rays almost solidified, wrapping around Han Xiao's hands and feet, flashing countless elven inscriptions.

Taking advantage of the short duration of control, Dylan quickly activated the short-range teleportation enchantment. With a flash of light, a large distance was opened up, and he hurriedly raised his hand to cast a spell to construct a long-distance transportation door.

He was not willing to sit back and do nothing, nor did he want to fight it out with Han Xiao, so he only wanted to escape as soon as possible.

However, the door had just emitted a spark when Han Xiao tore apart his control spell and shattered his weapon. He then used Void Hyperdrive to appear beside Dylan.

The next moment, an elbow condensed with psionic energy slammed into Dylan's magic shield. The powerful force instantly shattered the shield into pieces of light, and the unhindered iron elbow slammed into Dylan's chest.

Dong!

A dull vibration spread from the point of impact. Dylan's eyes bulged out, and he felt as if a huge force was crushing his internal organs. Many of his bones broke, his chest caved in, and his back suddenly swelled up.

"Cough—"

A gush of blood rushed up to his throat, and Dylan could not help but cough out a mouthful of blood. Enduring the pain, he quickly activated Phase Void Transformation, instantly avoiding Han Xiao's headbutt.

However, before he could use this opportunity to cast a spell, a mechanical palm wrapped in a pale white light quickly attacked him. The force field emitted by the Phase Stabilization device instantly neutralized his spell. The large hand immediately grabbed onto the physical body and held onto his throat. Immediately after, a storm of fists quickly enlarged in Dylan's vision.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

In just a blink of an eye, Dylan had lost count of the number of punches he had received on his face. He felt as if his head had become a sandbag that someone had hit crazily. Parts of his head caved in, and his entire body deflated. Waves of shock penetrated through his skin, muscles, and bones, penetrating deep into his brain. His brain was almost shaken into foam-like matter.

"Get lost!"

Dylan gritted his teeth, and his magic power flowed into his mind through a specific circuit, stimulating his mind. The dizzy negative status was cleared, and he regained his focused state. Without a word, he raised his hand and cast five instant-cast spells.

Amidst the flow of magic, the five spells instantly formed a combo. A shield that specialized in defending against melee attacks was formed again, barely blocking a few chain attacks. Following this, an escape spell broke free from the control, followed by a high-level Body Immobilization spell, which blocked Han Xiao for an instant. Then, the shockwave from the explosion of magic power pushed him away, and he used a Starlight Evasion skill to slide out, pulling away from Han Xiao again.

After finally getting a chance to catch his breath, Dylan quickly activated the healing magic that the elves were good at and healed his body. However, after receiving a series of heavy blows, his originally handsome face was now swollen like a pig's head.

"Although this guy, Dylan, is annoying, he still has some ability. It's a pity that the opponent this time is someone outside the norm. He's definitely unlucky."

The Beyond Grade As below watched the show while whispering.

Pinnacle Beyond Grade A Mages were known for their rich means. As an arcane master who had left his name in history, Dylan naturally knew countless spells. Unfortunately, these spells could only allow him to struggle for more time and had no other use. As a peak Beyond Grade A, Han Xiao's energy level far exceeded his.

Seeing that Dylan was being beaten up, everyone's enthusiasm soared. If not for their status, they might have cheered loudly. If not for knowing about Han Xiao's abilities, they would have thought that Dylan was being beaten up by a Pugilist when they saw the close combat suppression earlier.

This time, Han Xiao's energy surged and shattered the runes of the high-level Body Immobilization spell. He summoned the dimensional army box. A black army surged out, finally showing the style of a Mechanic.

Dylan's heart skipped a beat, and he did not dare to be distracted anymore. He quickly chanted incantations, and powerful forbidden spells flew out one after another, turning into magic artillery that bombarded the endless mechanical army. The colorful but fatal explosions burst out in the sea of machinery.

However, the performance of Han Xiao's mechanical soldiers was already extremely shocking, and with the support of his extremely high Machinery Affinity, there was no way that Dylan could cut through them. The toughness of the soldiers was like a nightmare, and most of his attacks were blocked by the mechanical army's shields and armor.

Switching to the Mechanic's group fight mode, the battle entered a rhythm that Han Xiao was familiar with. Dylan was surrounded, and he could not escape no matter how hard he tried. The mechanical army, on the other hand, moved back and forth like a rag wiping a stubborn stain.

After enduring the attacks time and time again, Dylan's aura slowly slid down from its peak and gradually weakened. He tried to open a stable transportation door again and again, but all the spatial fluctuations dissipated.

He was already an arrow at the end of its flight, struggling as he drowned in the sea of machinery. With his endless magic, he only lasted for a while.

Finally, the flickering magic shield could no longer withstand the attacks of the Apostle Weapons and shattered.

Chi! Chi! Chi!

The next moment, laser beams penetrated his body, leaving charred wounds on his body, and turning his body into a beehive.

However, although Mages were fragile, the life force of a peak Beyond Grade A was not so easily destroyed.

Han Xiao waved his hand, and a few Apostle Weapons escorted the heavily wounded Dylan into the broken conference room. They then arrived in front of the many Beyond Grade As who had been watching the battle.

Everyone looked at the miserable look on Dylan's face and grinned in secret. Dylan had no friends.

Sun Hunter floated over to Dylan's head, grabbed a bunch of hair, and pulled it off. "Aren't you very arrogant? Why don't you talk some more?"

"He was beaten up by you. I hope he can learn to keep a low profile in the future." Beiger shook his head.

Aurora could not bear to see him like this. She grabbed a ball of life energy and asked, "Do you need me to heal him?"

Han Xiao waved his hands and said casually,

"There's no need. I was just about to kill him."

As soon as he said that, the atmosphere changed slightly, and the smiles on everyone's faces disappeared.

They had thought that Han Xiao only wanted to teach Dylan a lesson, so they had been enjoying the show. However, now that they knew that Han Xiao wanted his life, their expressions turned serious.

"You want to kill him? Although this guy is quite annoying, it's not enough to take his life, right?" Sun Hunter's tone was doubtful.

Oulou agreed and said with surprise, "This guy is quite strong. Since he's willing to join the battle, why kill him? Furthermore, you'll have to revive him sooner or later. Isn't this unnecessary… Don't tell me you don't plan to revive him ‽"

For a moment, many people spoke up, expressing their objections.

Although they hated him, most Beyond Grade As did not want to kill him, not because they had any relationship, but because it involved their own interests. Although the Sanctum Revival was their lifeline, no one wanted to see Black Star kill a Beyond Grade A just because of this.

Han Xiao looked around and was not surprised at all.

The truth of the Sanctum Revival was a double-edged sword. The Beyond Grade As tolerated him because he was strong enough, but it did not mean that they had become obedient.

From the start to the end, these Beyond Grade As were all beasts that had never been tamed.

The chance of eternal life was very tempting. Some Beyond Grade As could let go of their pride, but they would not completely give up their dignity and bottom line. It was best for everyone to live in harmony, and everyone was willing to listen to his orders within the bottom line. However, if he went too far, then the Beyond Grade As would not submit to him and remain indifferent.

The purpose of participating in the battle in exchange for the revival quota was to unite against the outside world. It was a reasonable request, so everyone could accept it. However, it did not mean that the Beyond Grade As would obey all orders unconditionally. Although everyone cherished the opportunity to live forever, they had not become subordinates to be completely controlled by others.

Once the truth of the Sanctum Revival was revealed, it would no longer be a private matter but public interest in the eyes of the Beyond Grade As. It could be controlled by one person, but it could not be completely privatized.

If they wanted to use this channel to gain absolute control over the Beyond Grade As, the result would most likely be the Beyond Grade As working together to snatch the Sanctum Revival control.

They could either fight alone or rope in a group of Beyond Grade As to deal with the rebels. This way, it would be the route of the Celestial Star Alliance.

Han Xiao was well aware of this, and he did not plan to control everyone.

"Dylan has destroyed the internal unity many times, so he's an unstable factor. This time, he brought others to leave the association, which has already proved his instability. What if he had accidentally leaked the information? Seeing that he took the initiative to come back, I'll reduce his responsibility. However, for the sake of the war, I plan to send him to the Underworld temporarily and let him enjoy the normal revival treatment after the war ends.

Everyone, please bear witness to prevent me from going back on my word in the future."

Hearing this, everyone quietened down and exchanged looks.

They were against killing for no reason, but at the same time, they felt that Black Star's words made sense.

Thinking back to Dylan's performance, letting this foul-mouthed guy enter the Underworld for a while might be a good choice. The world would be quite peaceful.

Thinking of this, everyone retreated and did not stop him.

Seeing this, Dylan was in complete despair. He coughed out a large mouthful of charred blood, and his aura withered.

"Since no one has any objections, I shall take action."

Han Xiao turned around and signaled the troops.

Puchi!

The next moment, Psionic Prime's spear stabbed the back of Dylan's head and destroyed his last chance of survival.

Hila immediately raised her hand to capture Dylan's soul, then disappeared from where she was with Aurora. They entered the Underworld and transformed Dylan's spirit body.

Han Xiao looked at Kasuyi, pointed at the hole in the ceiling, and said, "Don't forget to get someone to fix the conference room."

With that, he changed into King and teleported away.

Seeing the mechanical army dragging away Dylan's corpse, the Beyond Grade As present were all shocked.

After thinking about it for a while, everyone felt that Black Star was deliberately killing Dylan in front of them to show his might. Black Star's hidden intent was that although he did not want to use the revival quota to control the Beyond Grade As, he did not want them to think that they could do whatever they wanted with the Sanctum Revival. He was not going to pay for the mistakes of others.

Originally, they had received the unlimited revival quota promised by Black Star through participating in the battle, and they were all very excited. Now that they had finally calmed down, some dangerous thoughts that had been sprouting in their minds were put on the reins.

The group composed themselves and dispersed.

...

In the Underworld Dimension.

Dylan's soul was suspended midair, Hila and Aurora were manipulating the power of the Underworld and continuously pouring it into Dylan's body to modify the form of his spirit body. Meanwhile, the Nine Great Hero Spirit Kings were watching from the side.

With a flash of light, Han Xiao teleported over. The moment he appeared, he attracted Dylan's furious gaze.

"Black Star! I took the initiative to return and join the battle, but you killed me. You and I are irreconcilable!"

Dylan cursed and gritted his teeth.

Han Xiao did not mind and clicked his tongue.

"You looked like you were half dead just now, but you look very energetic after your death."

"You're shameless! You're shameless! I believe you're really blind! I…"

Before he could finish, Hila silenced him with an expressionless face.

Han Xiao shrugged, turned to look at Sorokin and the others, and said, "This guy will be the tenth Hero Spirit King in the future. Teach him a little more and let him reflect on what it means to cause trouble with words."

With the rise in seniority, Sorokin was in a good mood.

"How strong is this guy?"

"Peak Beyond Grade A Mage, once the Elf Race's Holy King. His combat strength is quite good, and you might not even be his match. He is just a little bit weaker than me," Han Xiao said casually.

"The quality of the rookies this time is not bad," Sorokin replied.

Han Xiao ignored him and turned to look at the roaring Dylan.

This way, the Underworld Hero Spirit Kings would become one of the Ten Great Generals. With such a 'lively' fellow, Sorokin and the others' lives would be more 'colorful'.

Without looking at the Heroic Spirit Modification Ceremony of the two sisters, Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at the mission list. Dylan's Beyond Grade A Challenge Mission was shining brightly.

"Mage… I wonder what abilities I can draw…"

Chapter 1377: Shaken; A Ridiculous Ability

On the other side, the direct Beyond Grade As left the venue together, still thinking about how Dylan had died.

"Black Star is really domineering. He killed a peak Beyond Grade A just like that."

Reeve clicked her tongue and snorted.

"He wants to set a good example. It's quite unlucky for Dylan to have been chosen to establish dominance, but he deserves it."

Clotti looked straight ahead and said with a calm tone.

"I saw those revivors running away in fear just now. Isn't Black Star afraid of scaring them away?"

"If they run again, they'll have to follow in Dylan's footsteps. Also, will they be willing to leave?"

Clotti shook his head.

This time, Oulou rubbed his chin and said with a worried expression,

"Black Star is in control of this channel and has tied up almost all the Beyond Grade As with his benefits. The power of the association can no longer be restricted, and the problem of the Beyond Grade A imbalance can no longer be solved…"

Hearing this, many of the direct descendants were worried about the future of the three Universal Civilizations.

It was the war period now, so Black Star provided recovery services to the advanced civilizations. However, in the long run, if they could get rid of the pressure from the foreign enemies, they did not know if Black Star would still be willing to sell the recovery slots. At that time, they might lose the benefits of the Sanctum Revival, and the difference in strength between them would only grow.

Now that the association had an independent political position and astonishing strength coupled with the contributions and reputation of participating in the war, it was very difficult for the three Universal Civilizations to do anything else. They had dug a grave for themselves and even if they had tears in their eyes, they had to jump into it. No one knew how the upper echelons would deal with such a behemoth of an organization.

"The only way to break out of this situation is probably to develop the Sanctum Revival. It's a pity that I don't know how long it will take."

Oulou sighed.

The Sanctum Revivals now had a fatal attraction, and some direct descendants in the crowd were tempted. After all, the treatment of the two was worlds apart.

While everyone was worried, Hilbert did not say a word, but his eyes constantly twinkled.

As a 'retiree' who had completed his 'military service' and felt that he had fulfilled his duty to the three Universal Civilizations, he was very interested in the treatment of the association. When compared to the benefit of the Sanctum Revival, the 'retirement treatment' that he had paid using his life was worth nothing.

Although he had the patience to wait for the three Universal Civilizations to come out with their own Sanctum Revival, with his understanding of the three Universal Civilizations, he knew that it would not be a free lunch. In his opinion, the three Universal Civilizations would probably set some terms as restrictions, such as continuing to serve the civilization.

However, this would only work in an ideal situation where there were no competitors. Now that there were relaxed revival rules of the association for comparison, Hilbert felt that even if the three Universal Civilizations managed to revive the Sanctum, they would most likely have no choice but to reduce the price. They would not dare set conditions that were too harsh since the existence of the association would force them to increase the benefits for their descendants.

With this in mind, Hilbert glanced at everyone with a disapproving look.

It was really funny. These people were still here "worrying about the country and the people" but did not know that the existence of the association was also their blessing.

"Struggling for the interests of the entire Beyond Grade A class… he has been carrying out the purpose of the association."

Hilbert's eyes flickered with admiration.

Since he had already 'retired', joining the association was not a bad choice…

...

Two days later, in the Army Commander's office.

Han Xiao sat on his large chair, casually scrolling through the virtual screen to check the reactions of the Beyond Grade As in the past two days. He was quite satisfied.

After he revealed the truth about the Sanctum Revival, the morale of the Beyond Grade As was high. They were originally a little relaxed, but now, they were even more determined, and their fighting spirit was unprecedentedly high. Even their training had improved a notch.

"Although this kind of cohesion can only be triggered through such a request, it's enough."

Han Xiao knocked on the armrest of the chair, deep in thought.

He did not pursue the so-called absolute control but only wanted to achieve his goal. Therefore, he did not have any intention of 'taming' a portion of the Beyond Grade As. Up till now, he had already made his stance clear through his actions. With the benefits that he had offered, there was no need for him to use any more methods.

Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and chuckled.

"This should be the most united Beyond Grade A group in history. If only we could always be united."

As he spoke, he shook his head and laughed. After all, it was an unrealistic fantasy. They were divided internally and had different ideals. Only benefits were eternal. It was destined that only benefits could bind everyone to a place.

…Oh, not everyone. Almost all the surviving Beyond Grade As had been attracted over, but there were still exceptions. The Avengers from Pangon had never contacted the Holy Accord and did not say that they had returned to participate in the battle.

Their civilization had been destroyed, and their hatred was much deeper than Dylan's. They had long decided to sacrifice their lives for revenge. Although the Sanctum Revival was tempting, it would not make them give up on revenge.

The main reason was that they knew that as long as they did not give up on revenge, Black Star would not revive them to let them continue causing trouble. Pangon did not want to come back and implicate the association, so he simply ignored them.

The front line did not lack these few combatants, and Han Xiao did not want to revive these troublesome fellows, so he let them be. He did not call them back on purpose, not wanting to give them a way out.

"Tsk, they're pretty 'firm' about their ideals. Hopefully, you guys can keep it up."

Han Xiao curled his lips.

These avengers had set their sights on their goal and were not 'tempted' by the Sanctum Revival. However, with Han Xiao's position, he no longer had any admiration for them. Everyone had their ambitions. The choices of Pangon and the others as well as Dylan did not matter to him.

He was satisfied that these people were sensible and did not bring him any trouble.

Sitting in this position, he had too many responsibilities. He did not have the time to indulge others in war, class benefits, and dealing with the three Universal Civilizations. Everything had to be focused on the goal. Whoever caused trouble for him, he would not hesitate to stop them. All the difficulties and reasons were meaningless. Why should he understand other people's difficulties if they would not understand him first?

Therefore, for the past two days, Dylan had been cursing and swearing in the Underworld, but Han Xiao could not be bothered to talk with him.

Previously, Han Xiao had deliberately promised to let him go in front of everyone and get them to monitor him before deciding how to deal with him. This had given him hope, so no matter how he behaved, as long as Han Xiao could hold on to this point, the former would have no choice but to do his job obediently.

However, this guy has provided me with an interesting ability…

Han Xiao calmed himself down, opened the interface, and looked at the skill list with a weird expression.

Two days ago, he had already settled the mission reward. Perhaps it was because Harrison had spent all the luck that he had accumulated over this period, but he did not get anything good from touching the 'backup Feidin' this time. They were all ordinary skills, except for one…

[Taunting Habit]: After you activate the skill, it will be easier for the other party to misunderstand your language. -50% increase in Favorability, +100% decrease in Favorability. When you communicate with the enemy in battle, the enemy will have a higher chance of targeting you. (Judgement probability depends on Charm, Luck, and Favorability. The lower the related stats, the easier it is to become the target of hatred). No Energy consumption, buff lasts for 3 minutes each time you activate before it can be deactivated. No cooldown.

"No wonder this guy is so annoying. He probably never turned this skill off before, right?"

Every time he saw this ability introduction and thought about Dylan's daily performance, Han Xiao could not help but ponder.

Was it because of Dylan's habit of having a foul mouth that resulted in this ability, or was it because of this ability that caused Dylan to have a foul mouth? This was a question of whether the chicken or the egg came first.

Putting these factors aside, Han Xiao was quite satisfied with the effect of the skill.

The Taunt skill was not a common skill but was rather rare in the Star Sea. The biggest difficulty for players to fight a BOSS was that intelligent beings did not have a rigid aggro system. If they wanted to pull monsters, they could only use tactical cooperation. There was no rough and simple taunting method.

The most common ability to attract aggro was the mental guidance of Mages or Psychics, hinting to the enemy which targets they wanted to hit, but it was often rendered immune due to the BOSS mental resilience.

"There really are all kinds of strange things in the vast universe. Even chatting can create some decent skills… I have to use my skills more in the future."

Han Xiao raised his brow.

My style is becoming more and more like a qualified MT. I feel that if this goes on, my Galaxy Chief Mechanic title will change to become the number one tank in the universe!

Chapter 1378: For The Lucky, Even Their Advanced Missions Are Different

On the other side, in the Super Star Cluster conference room.

"The Sanctum Revival… what a terrifying power. Hehe, the three Universal Civilizations are probably in a terrible state."

Compared to the heavy atmosphere of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders, the Super Star Cluster leaders were overjoyed.

As the rulers of the explored universe, the three Universal Civilizations were hostile to all existences that could shake their rule. As the pursuers, the Super Star Cluster Alliance hoped for some factors that would affect the current status quo to appear.

Originally, Black Star had only relied on the one-time Sanctum Revival to bring the association to such a level. Now that he had finally shown the true effect of the Sanctum Revival, the Beyond Grade A Association instantly became many times more difficult to deal with. The more unhappy the three Universal Civilizations were, the happier the Super Star Cluster Alliance would be.

"Black Star obtained an independent political position from the three Universal Civilizations, akin to that of an advanced civilization. With Black Star's strength and the association's strength, the galactic society might be able to form a stable tripartite structure in the future. We, the three Universal Civilizations, and the association will balance each other. This is good news for us."

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization breathed out in relief.

"It should be the Pseudo version of the Tripartite. We still have a ways to go before we can catch up to the three Universal Civilizations, but the association has the Sanctum Revival, and we have a lot of resources. If we cooperate more closely, we won't have to fear the suppression of the three Universal Civilizations. The galactic society is no longer under their control, "Someone corrected with a smile.

One of the Modo Three Kings said with a depressed voice, "It's too early to say all this. The premise is that the three Universal Civilizations win this war. Otherwise, all of this will be empty talk."

"That's true. With the enemy before us, we can't celebrate too early." Someone nodded in agreement.

At this moment, the leader of the Star Arc Civilization knocked on the table, before speaking out.

"In about eleven years, the World Tree will attack the mainland. At that time, we will see if we should evacuate the explored universe. This period is enough for us to make preparations and keep it a secret. Don't let anyone know of our plan."

Hearing this, everyone nodded.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance had always been considering the possibility of migrating with the help of the war. This was a plan that they had long decided on. During the interception war, they had secretly started to build secret stargates in their respective civilizations, connecting them to the Super Star Cluster Civilizations at the border. Once they started to migrate, they would be able to directly arrive at their departure point from their capital territories.

At the same time, they used taking refuge as an excuse to gather most of the population and manage. As long as they started the plan, they would be able to migrate everyone efficiently. A large number of resources were also secretly stored, and some of the shipyards under them had been secretly mass-producing starships during the interception war to prepare for the long-distance migration.

Everything was in full preparation. The Super Star Cluster Alliance had planned to start after the World Tree invaded their territory. They would observe the situation and decide if they wanted to escape.

"If the three Universal Civilizations are defeated, Black Star and the others will not be destroyed together with them. They will retreat. At that time, we might have a chance to take over the Beyond Grade A Association…"

Someone whispered.

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization rubbed his finger and shook his head. "Hmm, you can't say that. If we migrate to another area, we will become the new ruler. An existence like the association will also become a threat to us. Therefore, if the three Universal Civilizations explode, it's best that we don't contact the association. It's not bad to live our own lives."

He sounded like he was saying, "Let's split our luggage and go our separate ways. You go back to your Quicksand River, and I go back to my hometown." Everyone could not help but laugh.

Although they were envious of the Beyond Grade As and the Sanctum Revival channel of the association, they knew that they would not have the chance to obtain such benefits.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance did not have the confidence and base strength of the three Universal Civilizations, and they were even more afraid that the Beyond Grade A Association would take over their territory. After all, their strength was weaker than the three Universal Civilizations. If they entered a migration period without any rules or regulations, the Beyond Grade A groups that could continuously revive would have the power to overthrow their regime. Therefore, if everyone had to evacuate one day, then parting ways would make them feel more at ease.

"Speaking of which, Black Star is truly a talent. He successfully fooled the three Universal Civilizations, and the current situation we see now has his shadow behind every step. In just a few decades, the Beyond Grade As already possess such strength, breaking the stalemate. It's not an easy task."

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization sighed softly, his tone filled with admiration and fear.

Although their relationship with Black Star often changed, from a personal perspective, the leader of the Star Arc Civilization and most of the Super Star Cluster leaders present mostly admired Black Star.

Everyone had carefully read Black Star's file. If they had not witnessed everything with their own eyes, they would never have imagined that a bumpkin from the surface civilization would rise from the bottom and reach the top in just a hundred years.

It was a pity that such a person was not born in their civilization. If not for the fact that Planet Aquamarine was under Black Star's protection, they would have dissected this planet to see why there were three Beyond Grade As.

The leader of the Star Arc Civilization changed into a more comfortable position and sighed. "I don't have any hopes for the association now. I just hope that they can sell us more revivals… Speaking of which, the Sanctum revivals are unlimited. Will Black Star lower the price for us now?"

Everyone tilted their heads and pondered.

At the training base, the Calamity Grade combat training ground.

Energy surged, and light flashed. Five figures surrounded Hadavy. All kinds of attacks landed on his body and exploded into light fragments. They could only leave faint marks on his tough body and could not break through his defense.

The continuous sound of explosions mixed with Hadavy's laughter.

"Hahahaha—useless, useless, useless! Your attacks are nothing compared to His Excellency Black Star's Apostle Weapons. There's no way they can break through my defense!"

Just from the tone of his voice, it sounded like he was fighting against five Calamity Grades alone. However, upon closer inspection, the five Calamity Grades were beating Hadavy up like a rubber ball.

On the spectator stands in the sky, many Calamity Grades looked down at the trembling training ground with strange expressions.

"He can still be so arrogant after being beaten up. Looks like he has learned the essence of what makes up the Army Commander."

"This guy is indeed the Black Star Guard that has followed His Excellency Black Star for decades."

Everyone chatted casually.

The Black Star Army had once harvested hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds, and most of the spectators were members of the army. However, not only were they watching the show, but they were also waiting to beat Hadavy up.

After decades of training by Han Xiao, Hadavy's Esper Ability had been developed to an astonishing level. He was used to being beaten by a Beyond Grade A Apostle Weapon, and normal Calamity Grade attacks were nothing to him. Even the weaker Calamity Grades would be able to break through his defenses.

Thus, Hadavy became a human sandbag in the training base. Many Calamity Grade students were willing to use him to test how far away they were from the Beyond Grade As. As long as they could beat Hadavy to the point that he screamed, it would mean that they were half a step away from the Calamity Grade.

The beating lasted for quite a while, and the five attackers stopped while panting. Hadavy immediately got up from the ground and pretended to pat the non-existent dust on his body. He shook his finger at the five of them and snorted.

"That's it? I don't feel anything yet. Let's practice a little more and try to make me feel like dying next time."

"Why do you always say such ambiguous words?" A Calamity Grade wiped his sweat and could not help but complain, "Is this the organizational culture of your Black Star Army?"

"A crooked stick will have a crooked shadow," another person agreed.

"Horsing around is one thing, but spouting nonsense is another. Don't joke about my dear Army Commander," Sylvia, who was participating in the siege, said to her friend.

Hearing this, Hadavy looked at her and patted his chest.

"You quit your job as Chief Administrative Official, and you've been training behind closed doors for so long. Why haven't you made any progress? I think you'd better not waste your time training here. You definitely won't become a Beyond Grade A."

Hearing this, Sylvia turned her head and said with a face full of disdain, "You have the cheek to say that about me. With your single ability, even if you become a Beyond Grade A, you will still be at the bottom."

"At the very least, I have the ticket to immortality."

Hadavy looked like a dead pig that was not afraid of boiling water. Ever since the truth of the Sanctum Revival was revealed, such words could no longer hurt his heart.

To enjoy the revival of the Sanctum, he did not even play his favorite Wayne Cards anymore. Lagi had called him a few times, but he had rejected him.

Speaking of which, the number of people playing cards had decreased by 99% recently. Only Lagi was still pulling people in, but the frequency had also decreased. People often saw Lagi training in the magic training ground as well. His training duration had increased by ten times!

This was a sight that was hard to come by in ten years. Many of the officers who knew him were shocked and felt encouraged.

Even Lagi was working hard, what right do you have to be lazy?!

This time, a few more Calamity Grades jumped down from the sky and landed on the ground.

"Alright, stop chatting. We're still queuing. It's our turn. Hadavy, do you want to take a break?"

Hadavy patted his chest and said in a booming voice,

"What are you resting for? These people are useless. I'm still thirsty. Come, face me!"

"I told you not to be ambiguous!"

The group roared.

While the Calamity Grade Supers were sparring, Feidin, who was deep in training, suddenly opened his eyes. A gleam flashed past.

In that instant, it was as if some invisible boundary had been broken. A deep shiver from the depths of his cells started from his brain and slowly spread through his entire body inch by inch as if every cell was crying out in joy and desire.

Immediately after, the cells in his body started to stir, like water that was being heated up.

"This feeling… I'm going to be promoted?!"

Feidin was pleasantly surprised. He could not be wrong about this feeling of being elevated to the next level. However, the feeling this time was different from the previous Promotions. This time, it was dozens of times stronger, causing his body to tremble uncontrollably. His psychic energy also gushed out uncontrollably, sweeping around the room like a storm.

At this time, the Soul Swapper on him suddenly sensed something and began to vibrate at a high frequency. Black ripples appeared on the Soul Swapper. The Soul Swapper was contaminated with Psychic energy, and a subtle fusion was formed. The originally formless and colorless Psychic energy seemed to have been drawn to the edge of the Soul Swapper, and as if being traced out, the edges turned black.

Before Feidin could even react, he realized that his psychic energy seemed to have reached into an unknown realm, and countless voices began clamoring from his soul.

"Ah!"

Feidin cried out in pain, feeling as though his head was about to explode.

Amid the pain, a piece of information appeared in his mind. He realized that he had sensed an unknown existence, and a strong intuition was guiding him. The path to ascension was here.

It was a pity that Han Xiao did not see it at the moment, or else he would have sighed. He was very familiar with this rare treasure!

As expected of a child blessed by the heavens, even the Promotion Mission was different from the others. If he was here, he would have to interview Feidin and see what it was like to be one of the three thousand faces of the Goddess of Luck.

Chapter 1379: Opportunity for Sublimation, Soul Terminal

"You said that not only did you sense the opportunity of sublimation, but the Soul Swapper also changed causing your psychic power to mutate?"

In the private workshop, Han Xiao turned around and looked at Feidin with a strange expression.

"That's right, I'm also very surprised. The Soul Connection level has increased by a level, and part of the Soul Swapper's characteristic is added to my Psychic powers. In addition, I can vaguely sense the existence of a secondary dimension, and my intuition leads me there."

Feidin shook his head in resignation.

What's with that helpless expression of yours? Why do you find it so troublesome when you've had a fortuitous encounter? Is this what it means to be favored by the heavens? How beautiful.

Han Xiao said in his mind.

Speaking of which, he had used [Bold Explorer] to look at the origin of the Soul Swapper before, and it was not that rare. It was an artificial product, but it might have formed a connection with a secondary dimension when it transformed into a Space Wonder.

He guessed that once a suitable person touched the Beyond Grade A sublimation, they would be able to activate this hidden benefit. The possibility was quite high.

No wonder the Soul Swapper was so eager to be pampered by Feidin. It turned out that it was because it saw the opportunity to unlock its new form in Feidin.

Han Xiao then poked Feidin. Feidin's main purpose for coming to report was to accept his 'physical examination'.

The moment he poked, combat information popped up on the interface.

Han Xiao looked at Feidin and realized that Feidin had a new energy attribute that involved the soul. At the same time, he had two new talents. One was the bonus from the Soul Swapper's mutation, which increased his Psychic Strength and other attributes. The other talent was a question mark and was still in a gray frozen state.

This was literally the scenario of sitting at home, talents descending from the sky… Tsk, what was this?

Han Xiao coughed and said,

"Since it's your intuition that leads you to that secondary dimension, you can go over and take a look. Did you get a sense of direction or specific coordinates?"

"Coordinates," Feidin replied with a nod.

"Oh, that's convenient. There's no need to spend too much time on the journey. However, most people get a sense of direction. Your coordinates should be the information recorded by the Soul Swapper. Let's set off after I pack up."

As he spoke, Han Xiao prepared to put away the technology he was studying and summon the carrier.

However, Feidin shook his head and rejected.

"Black Star, I have a feeling that this is my own training. If you follow me, I won't have any sense of danger. I'll go alone."

Han Xiao paused and said,

"Since you have such a request, that's fine too. I'll give you a King, and you can bring another Throne. If you encounter any problems that you can't solve, just ask me for help…"

Seeing that Feidin still wanted to say something, Han Xiao waved his hand and interrupted him.

"You're my good friend. I can't possibly let you take the risk without any backup plan. That's my bottom line."

"…Alright then." Feidin smiled helplessly.

Han Xiao took out the equipment and a small carrier that was specially used in secondary dimensions. He got the mechanical assistant to bring them to the departure area. Feidin thanked him and followed along.

After watching Feidin disappear, Han Xiao looked away and shook his head.

To a Calamity Grade, the secondary dimensions were still quite dangerous. Han Xiao was worried about Feidin's safety and wanted to accompany him. However, Feidin wanted to clear the dungeon alone, and it involved the opportunity of Beyond Grade A sublimation. He respected Feidin's premonition.

However, with Feidin's luck, he would most likely be able to turn any misfortune into good luck. Whereas, with Han Xiao's luck black hole, there might be some twists and turns. It would be a good thing if he did not go.

However, Han Xiao would not sit back and watch this treasure put himself in danger. He had secretly given Feidin an Observer's Mark just now and planned to monitor the risk. After all, Feidin had coordinates unlike Harrison, it would not waste too much of his time.

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the research device that was analyzing the new technology. He temporarily stopped the progress.

Every Beyond Grade A had their own training plan. Han Xiao had brought out more blueprints from the Sanctum this time, and he was researching these technologies during this period while also optimizing and raising his attributes. To Mechanics, this was called optimizing the allocation of resources. Putting the attribute points in a more cost-effective area could also increase his combat strength.

After entering the First Sanctum this time, his authority had increased to level nine, and his memory capacity had increased again. Furthermore, there were fewer gaps in the message board, but the last few paragraphs were still mostly empty.

The last time, the valuable information about the 'Information Form Stripping Plan' had appeared in the fourth last paragraph, but this time, the last paragraph caught his attention. Han Xiao could not help but recall.

[…The previous Iteration███ planned route should be correct, but because of some flaws and failures, we decided to add a controlling terminal on███to reduce the processing cost of ███. However, what will the controlling terminal become after the mutation of ███…]

In the days after he left the Sanctum, he had been pondering over this piece of information. It seemed that the last Iteration had agreed with the previous Iteration's plan and made some improvements.

Generally speaking, a civilization that was facing the Great Reboot would not place all its hopes on the path of its predecessors. After all, the failures of their predecessors had already proved that their plans were not effective, and they could only provide some experience.

However, the previous Iteration was actually willing to believe in the past Iteration's plan. If not for the fact that this plan had its merits, the subsequent civilization would not have made such a decision. This way, the plan that had improved the two Iterations was very valuable as a reference. Han Xiao was also secretly interested.

"I'll have to enter the First Sanctum a few more times in the future. I wonder how much authority I need to unlock these two messages."

Han Xiao calmed himself down, left the workshop, and returned to the office on the top floor. He first looked down at the combat training of the other Calamity Grades before entering the field of vision of the Observer's Mark.

...

At the private space dock, the mechanical assistants quickly finished the adjustments in the small carrier.

Feidin sat in the pilot's seat and recalled for a while. He then entered the secondary dimension coordinates into the navigator and started the shuttle engine. He immediately felt the spaceship tremble.

"Locking the secondary dimension coordinates… preheating the shuttle engine… activating the internal space stabilization device…"

The artificial intelligence of the spaceship kept reporting, and a large number of navigation parameters appeared on the screen.

Feidin set the autopilot, took out the Soul Swapper, and pressed it against his chest. He took a deep breath to calm himself down.

Not long after, the spaceship completed its self-examination before the voyage and the vibration suddenly disappeared. Feidin felt his body suddenly become heavy, as though he was pressed onto his seat by a strong force. The scene of the dock outside the window also shattered in an instant, turning into endless streams of light, and the spaceship entered the traveling mode.

After an unknown period of time, the spaceship shook again and exited the traveling mode. The scene outside changed.

This was a pitch-black space with no end in sight. A gray nebula vortex with an immeasurable area was slowly spinning outside the window, right above the spaceship. He looked up, but he could not see the entirety of the vortex. He could not help but be shocked.

A gigantic white pillar of light shot out from the center of the vortex, extending all the way out of sight.

At the same time, wisps of gray airflow floated in from all directions and were pulled by the nebula vortex. It was like a hundred rivers converging into the sea, all fusing into it. This was the main material that formed this vortex.

Before Feidin could even exclaim in surprise, he discovered something special. Being in this space, his mental strength seemed to have become more active, and the Soul Swapper was also vibrating slightly.

"What is this place…"

Feidin looked around, but there seemed to be no signs of life around him. He released his psychic energy, which was too active and difficult to control, and captured a gray stream of air that passed by him to see what it was.

After checking carefully, Feidin's expression suddenly changed.

"This is… a soul ‽"

He turned around and looked at the endless gray airflow in disbelief.

This nebula vortex was made of souls ‽

This time, Feidin suddenly thought of a piece of information and muttered,

"In the visions of some psychic ability users, when a living being dies, their soul might seem to have completely dissipated, but in reality, there are still undetectable bits and pieces left behind. One part will turn into the Psychic Current, and the other part will drift in the universe.

There should be some places like this in this world that—took in the soul residue from the entire universe, filtered it, crushed the residue extracting the remaining thoughts inside, condensed them into the universe consciousness, and sank them into the 'bottommost layer of the pan-consciousness' dimension. Some psychic ability users called these places 'Soul Terminal', 'Spirit World Sanctuary', and 'Ruins of End'.

However, no one has ever found a similar secondary dimension. Could it be that the legend is real?"

Feidin was shocked. The more he thought about it, the more he felt that this might be one of the legendary 'Soul Terminals'.

During the development of the Flickering World, Black Star had brought a group of officers to travel around. Feidin had once met a Heart Sucking Demon from the 'bottommost layer of the pan-consciousness' dimension and turned it into his own nutrients to strengthen his psychic energy. Thus, he had paid special attention to this theoretical conjecture.

The three Universal Civilizations knew the coordinates of the bottommost layer of the pan-consciousness, but there were countless Heart Sucking Demons there, and they had extremely strong xenophobia. With their current technology, it was very difficult to build a stable outpost there.

The Heart Sucking Demons, on the other hand, fed on the universe consciousness. Therefore, Soul Terminal was equivalent to their kitchen. The soul residue here was all 'ingredients' that had not been processed.

"The Soul Swapper guided me here. Could it be related to this dimension?"

Feidin thought to himself.

The effect of the Soul Swapper had long exceeded what was envisioned when it was first created. Perhaps the Soul Swapper had such a strange effect because it could transform into a Universal Treasure…

After guessing for a while, Feidin carefully sensed the gray airflow around him and smiled bitterly.

The gray airflow was the soul residue, and the center of the nebula vortex was constantly smelting the residue and 'serving food'.

Heart Sucking Demon was a great supplement to the mind, but the side effects required a lot of time to resolve.

The soul residue was even more complicated. Although he could absorb the soul energy within it to refine his mental strength, most of his energy had to be used to deal with side effects such as split personality and schizophrenia.

Furthermore, the energy contained in the soul residue was almost undetectable. The conversion efficiency was extremely low, and the amount of energy invested far exceeded the output.

As for the universe consciousness after the smelting process, it had already removed the soul energy, and the side effects were even more violent. It was not beneficial to him at all.

"Speaking of which, this place is suitable for Hila. Her Power Of The Dead can quickly purify the soul energy. This might be her holy land of cultivation…"

Feidin mumbled to himself and was stunned.

He almost forgot that he had the Soul Swapper. If the target was only soul residue, the Soul Swapper should be able to separate the remnant thoughts and soul energy and purify it, right?

Doesn't that mean I can absorb these countless soul dregs without any side effects ‽

Feidin immediately understood and was pleasantly surprised.

Is this why the Soul Swapper guided me here ‽

After cultivating here for a while, there was an 80% chance that he could advance. His intuition told him that this was indeed the opportunity to advance!

...

"Amazing…"

On the other side, Han Xiao, who was peeping, had a complicated feeling.

I thought that my cheat was already amazing, but you are even more over the top!

To think that the fortuitous encounter from decades ago and now would be connected. The power of the Advanced Luck Glow was truly terrifying.

Compared to the Luck Glow owners who needed to rely on him like Harrison and Nero, Han Xiao felt that Feidin's Luck Glow was the most impressive.

Not only did he have a fortuitous encounter, but he also benefited his teammates… It was not in vain that they treat you as the Chief mascot to touch for luck!

Chapter 1380: Beyond Grade A Feidin

While Han Xiao was feeling bitter, Feidin, who was in the Soul Terminal, had already started to work.

Feidin took out the Soul Swapper and activated its ability. Instantly, an invisible suction force appeared, and the soul fragments in the surrounding area suddenly slowed down toward the nebula vortex. In the end, they changed direction and flew toward his starship.

The nebula vortex had a natural gravitational force toward the soul residue, and Feidin's actions were akin to 'snatching food from a tiger's mouth'. However, this secondary dimension did not seem to have any dimension consciousness, so no one bothered about him.

Soul residue was absorbed by the black mirror in the Soul Swapper. The remaining thoughts were extracted and refined into pure soul energy.

Feidin used Soul Connection to extract the results of the Soul Swapper and used his psychic energy to wrap it around and bring it into his brain to digest. He only felt refreshed and did not have the memory or emotional impact that he usually suffered when using his psychic energy to probe others' thoughts. He could feel his psychic energy being cleansed, and the cells in his body were cheering.

He could feel that his body was gradually transforming, like an extremely thirsty person continuously drinking clear and sweet spring water. He was brimming with a sense of fulfillment from head to toe, giving him a feeling that was even more comfortable than spiritual bonding, making him involuntarily lose himself in it.

While his body and mind were closely connected to the Soul Swapper, the psychic energy around Feidin's body was tainted with a deeper black color, and he received a new enhancement from the Soul Swapper. His characteristics became stronger, and he became more refined. This gave him a thrill that made his soul tremble.

"Hu…"

Feidin could not help but let out a comfortable sigh. It was as though he had entered a state of unconscious cultivation, and all the cells in his body were gradually jumping toward the Beyond Grade A level.

With him as the center, a gray vortex that was countless times smaller formed, reflecting the enormous nebula vortex. The large and small vortex rotated at the same speed and in opposite directions.

After confirming that Feidin was not in danger, Han Xiao did not disturb him and continued his research.

Soon, a month passed.

Han Xiao arrived at the training base square early in the morning.

Not too long ago, Feidin had finally ended his one-month-long training, and he had already broken through to the Beyond Grade A realm. Only then did he remember to send a message saying that he was coming back, so Han Xiao waited there.

The Calamity Grade students who happened to pass by saw him standing there, and they could not help but look at him with curiosity.

Not long after, there was a flash of light, and the shuttle carrier appeared out of thin air. It jumped back to the main universe from the secondary dimension world and landed on the square where the coordinates were set.

The hatch opened, and Feidin walked out. The moment he saw Han Xiao, he smiled happily and walked over.

Compared to a month ago, his aura had undergone a huge change. Just walking alone made the hearts of all the Calamity Grade students tense up, and they felt an instinctive pressure. It was the pressure of a high-level life form.

At this moment, the Calamity Grades immediately understood what was going on. They were shocked and immediately crowded around Feidin.

"Feidin, you've already become a Beyond Grade A ‽"

"I haven't seen you in the base all this time. I was still curious about where you went. I didn't expect you to undergo sublimation without saying anything. Not bad!"

"Quick, quick, quick. Tell us how it feels."

Feidin was surrounded by a large group of people, so he could only stop and look at Han Xiao with a helpless smile.

His charisma attribute was extremely high, and his personality was the type that would not offend anyone, so he had quite a good relationship with people. Even after becoming a Beyond Grade A, he did not have the mentality of being superior to others and did not push the crowd away.

The Calamity Grades present were still calling out to their friends when they saw figures covered in streams of light jumping around the base. At the same time, there were a few transportation doors beside them. A large group of Calamity Grades who had received the news rushed over and crowded around. There were more and more people, and the scene was as noisy as a market.

Outside the crowd, Han Xiao coughed and suppressed everyone's voices.

"Feidin has indeed advanced to the Beyond Grade A realm. He is the first student to break through during the training period. It has only been two to three months since the training started. This is a very good start."

Upon receiving the information, everyone could not help but reveal the looks of envy as they congratulated Feidin.

A wave of congratulations instantly resounded. Some were sincere, some were sour.

Feidin sighed and explained.

"Everyone, I was able to advance successfully because of some opportunities. I'm afraid my experience is not suitable for everyone, so there's no point in referencing it."

Of course. When an ordinary person advanced to Beyond Grade A, which one of them did not feel constipated? Silver Shadow even went into seclusion for close to a hundred years during his transformation. Only a cheater like you could do it as easily as eating or drinking…

Han Xiao thought to himself.

This time, Feidin saw the regret on everyone's faces, thought for a while, and smiled.

"However, I can let everyone experience my strength after my Promotion. I can also replicate my senses during my Promotion…"

As he spoke, he closed his eyes and spoke softly. A melodious psychic voice immediately swept out and covered everyone present.

The spirits of the Calamity Grade students were refreshed, and they instantly received Feidin's comprehension of his Promotion. At the same time, they also realized that the beautiful psychic voice that resounded through their souls had triggered their emotions, and they were subconsciously immersed in it.

The next moment, a sense of motivation rose from the bottom of their hearts. Everyone's heart was filled with the desire to train. They wished they could go into seclusion and train hard right now. It was as if they had used stimulants and became rather energetic.

Han Xiao purposely let go of the mental barrier and tested Feidin's Psychic abilities. Seeing the combat information on the interface, he could not help but raise his brows.

Feidin was proficient in the path of mental power. The fortuitous encounter this time had allowed his abilities to undergo a huge transformation. His Psychic Song had been integrated into the special nature of the Soul Swapper, and his Psychological Resistance penetration had increased tremendously. Now, he could more efficiently trigger the emotions and desires of living beings, achieving a strong hypnotic effect. Every time he triggered different emotions, the target would enter a similar state.

At this moment, everyone's enthusiasm was a manifestation of this. Feidin used his Psychic voice to stimulate everyone's motivation, and what appeared in Han Xiao's status bar was the effect of increasing his efficiency in acquiring experience. On others, it would increase their cultivation efficiency!

Han Xiao instantly thought of the role Feidin could play. Although Feidin's current level was not high and he was not good at fighting head-on, he could bring a large area of buffs or debuffs to his teammates or enemies. This was more useful than his combat capability.

"A strong support is much more valuable than an ordinary Beyond Grade A. Just this ability alone is enough to make him very popular and he won't be at the bottom. Most importantly, he can increase the training efficiency of others without any side effects. With his help, more Beyond Grade As might be born…"

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

His gaze suddenly paused and he realized that there was an extremely eye-catching figure among the energetic crowd. His face was still scrunched up, forming a sharp contrast with the people around him.

This figure was like a firefly in the night, so bright and outstanding. Who else could it be but Lagi?

Han Xiao was curious. "Hey, Feidin, this doesn't seem to work on him."

Hearing this, Feidin turned to look at Lagi and was stunned.

"That's not right. This move shouldn't be ineffective against Calamity Grades, right…"

As he spoke, Feidin sent out another psychic voice to encourage Lagi.

Lagi's spirit instantly soared, and he was no longer hunched. His posture was tall and straight like a javelin, and his entire aura changed drastically. He was heroic, and his eyes were wide open.

"Isn't this effective… Hmm?"

Before Feidin could even finish his sentence, Lagi's state only lasted for a few seconds before his aura suddenly deflated like a balloon. In the blink of an eye, he returned to his original state of being dispirited and weak.

"You…"

Feidin opened his mouth in confusion.

This kind of invigoration would usually last for a few days, but why did it disappear after a few seconds on Lagi?

He did not give up and wanted to try again, but Lagi stopped him.

"Stop torturing me. This is all in vain. Sigh, even if you become a Beyond Grade A, you won't be able to free me. Let me rot in the corner alone…"

Tsk, what familiar trash, what beautiful Lagi language…

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat. He sized Lagi up and made a bold guess.

"Hmm, I think I understand now. After all, your invigoration is only similar to hypnosis, not brainwashing. It can't change the personality of others, so the emotions that trigger different targets are also different… Maybe Lagi is exempt from this kind of mental invigoration?"

As he spoke, Han Xiao felt that he had guessed the truth.

It had to be that Lagi's sense of worth was too f*cking firm, and the temporary invigoration would only be broken down in an instant. It was like drinking chicken soup and making up his mind to work hard the next day, but still lazing around the next day.

Feidin also felt that it made sense and asked, "How about I try to stimulate his dispirited emotions and see if you're right?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

"Better not. He's already dispirited enough. If you add fuel to the fire, I'm afraid he'll commit suicide on the spot."

"…Reasonable."

Feidin was speechless.

The Calamity Grade students received the experience that they wanted. Seeing that Han Xiao and Feidin still had something to discuss, they all left and went to train their abilities. Very soon, only the two of them were left in the square.

Without anyone else around, Han Xiao walked up to Feidin and patted his shoulder.

"Congratulations, you've already left your name in the Sanctum. As long as I'm still alive, death will stay away from you."

Feidin smiled and said, "My fortuitous encounter this time came from the Soul Swapper. If not for you, I wouldn't have been able to obtain this Universal Treasure. Thanks."

"Why are you being so polite to me?" Han Xiao waved his hand and said, "By the way, you don't have a nickname yet, right? Let me think of one for you. Why don't we call you Singer? How fitting."

Singer was Feidin's nickname in his previous life. Although his life experience was completely different this time, Han Xiao felt that this nickname was still suitable for Feidin.

"Alright, let it be Singer then."

Feidin smiled and expressed that he accepted the title. He then hid his smile and explained everything that he had experienced.

Although he guessed that Black Star might already know, he still told him.

After hearing Feidin's explanation, Han Xiao smiled and nodded.

"I understand. This is your opportunity. Even if you become a Beyond Grade A, you can still use it to quickly increase your strength. You have to make good use of it."

"Of course. By the way, remnant souls will also be beneficial to Hila. I can only digest the soul residue with the help of external objects, but Hila has a natural ability to do that. Her growth rate might even be faster than mine. Ask her what she thinks. Anyway, the soul residue there is inexhaustible, and the parts I can digest are not worth mentioning."

"Must be tough for you to think of her as well. I think she would be very happy to do so."

The more Han Xiao looked at Feidin, the more he admired him, and his hands grew a little itchy.

Suppressing his impulse, Han Xiao coughed and said,

"I'm going to inform Hila now. She's still training in the Underworld, and I'll need you to bring her there. After all, you found this place. Without your permission, I won't give the coordinates to anyone else."

With that, Han Xiao changed into King and teleported away.

Feidin watched Han Xiao leave and clenched his fists. An unknown emotion echoed in his heart, and he sighed softly.

"You have provided me with protection for almost a hundred years. Now, it's finally my turn to help you…"

Chapter 1381: Hila's Hidden Cultivation, Experience Filled Up

With a flash of light, Han Xiao arrived at the Underworld Dimension. The moment he entered, he saw Hila fighting Aurora.

In the pitch-black sky, two enormous energy spheres, one red and one gold, stuck closely together like two connected suns. The scarlet power of the Dead pressed forward step by step, continuously squeezing the space occupied by the Life power, like a ruffian bullying a cowering girl.

A graceful figure floated in the middle of the energy cluster filled with Power Of The Dead. Hila's red hair danced in the energy surge, and her expression was calm.

On the other side of the golden light, Aurora's blonde hair was dancing wildly. She clenched her fists and raised them in front of her. Her cheeks were red, and she was pumping out all her life energy to resist Hila's suppression.

"Eh? An elder sister bullying her younger sister, I can't just ignore this. Do you need help? I can help you bully her back."

Han Xiao glanced at it, raised his brows, and shouted at Aurora.

Hila turned around and glanced at him. After pausing for a moment, she retracted her power of Death.

The scarlet sun in the sky rapidly shrunk and disappeared, returning to her body.

Aurora, who was on the other side, suddenly felt no pressure. It was as if one of them had suddenly let go when the two of them were pushing each other. The life force that had lost its resistance could not help but spurt out, and a golden tsunami immediately appeared in the sky.

She hurriedly restrained her energy and slowly guided it back into her body. The golden sun quickly disappeared, leaving Aurora gasping in midair, looking like she was about to collapse.

Hila frowned and stared at Aurora with her sharp eyes. "Your control is still too weak. Rest for a while and continue training."

Hila then turned to Han Xiao and explained,

"We're not fooling around. Extreme pressure can speed up the growth of her life energy, broaden her upper limit, and help her increase her strength. This is one of the special training I've prepared for her."

Han Xiao shrugged. He knew that this was training, so he was just joking.

At this time, Aurora also turned back into her petite figure and flew in front of them. The redness on her face that she had suppressed earlier had yet to fade, and she looked a little silly and embarrassed.

"I lost the last battle because I was not strong enough. I felt that I could no longer wait idly for my life force to automatically increase. It was too slow, so I specially requested my sister to give me special training. I will improve as much as I can."

"Not bad, very hardworking."

Han Xiao smiled and praised her. He raised his hand and rubbed Aurora's head.

Aurora enjoyed it and even raised her head slightly to approach Han Xiao's palm.

This time, Hila floated over with an expressionless face. She slapped Han Xiao's hand away and said, "Why are you looking for me? If there's nothing else, leave. The special training is not over yet. Don't disturb us."

Han Xiao rubbed the back of his hand, which had turned red from the slap, and smiled. "I'm here to tell you some good news. Feidin has already become a Beyond Grade A."

Hila's eyes flickered, but she was not surprised. She nodded calmly.

"It's indeed a good thing. Please congratulate him on my behalf. However, it was only a matter of time before he reached this level."

"Other than that, there's another surprise for you. Feidin has found the legendary place where souls return to the dust, the Soul Terminal. He knows that your ability can devour souls to strengthen yourself, so he wanted me to ask if you're interested in taking a look."

Hearing this, Hila's expression changed, and her eyes widened slightly. She finally had an emotional reaction.

She also knew about the legends of the Soul Terminal. The power of the dead was nourished by the soul, and she also yearned for this legendary place. However, this was only a guess. There was no eyewitness report of the Soul Terminal in history. If what Black Star said was true, Feidin should be the first person to discover it.

"Of course I'm interested! When are we going over?!"

Without any hesitation, Hila blurted out and instantly threw the thought of Aurora's special training out of the window.

"Let's go now. Feidin is already waiting for you at the training base."

"Then what are we waiting for? Hurry up!"

Without hesitation, Hila took out a King suit and quickly put it on, signaling Han Xiao to activate it with Mechanical Force.

Han Xiao could not help but laugh. He also changed into a King and activated his Mechanical Force.

With a flash of lightning, the two of them disappeared.

Ten minutes later, Feidin brought Han Xiao and Hila to the Soul Terminal.

Looking at the inexhaustible soul fragments here, Hila revealed a rare look of shock and surprise. For a moment, she forgot how to speak, staring at the enormous Soul Nebula Vortex in a daze.

"How is this place? Does it help you?" Feidin asked.

Hila regained her senses and nodded. Her voice trembled with emotion,

"These soul dregs are very beneficial to me. My intuition tells me that this is the best place for me to cultivate!"

"As long as it's useful. Since there's no one here, you can stay as long as you want," Feidin said with a smile.

"Thanks."

Hila patted Feidin's shoulder and rubbed it, repeating what Han Xiao usually did. Her eyes were fixed on the countless soul fragments, her eyes were burning.

At this moment, she decided without hesitation.

Until the World Tree enters the mainland, I will stay here. No one can take me away!

It was rare for Hila to be excited, but she felt like she had forgotten something.

At this moment, a despondent voice sounded in her mind.

"Sis… what about my special training?"

Errr, I told you I forgot something…

Hila's expression froze, and she coughed.

"Ahem, things have changed. I won't be going back for a while. You can practice by yourself first."

This tone was more or less like a parent who had no choice but to coax a child when they were busy with work. It gave off the feeling of 'you go play by yourself'.

"Humph! I'll train myself!"

Aurora shut off her mental voice.

I was abandoned just like that?

You promised to help me cultivate, but you ran away. Stupid Sister, I'm ignoring you!

The mental communication was cut off, but Hila did not care. She could not wait to get out of the spaceship.

Crash!

The Power Of The Dead gushed out, forming a scarlet tornado. It swept over the soul residue in the surroundings, crushing and disintegrating them, turning everything into pure soul energy that was swallowed into the Power Of The Dead to strengthen her Esper Ability.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

With such an opportunity, Hila will also be on the path of leveling up. I estimate that in ten years… no, in less than ten years, a new peak Beyond Grade A will appear. When she reaches this level, her combat strength will be greatly enhanced. With her strength, as long as she grows stronger, it won't be a problem for her to resist two or three peak Beyond Grade As of the World Tree.

He rubbed his chin as he watched this scene. He secretly nodded and had high hopes for Hila.

Hila and Feidin stayed behind to cultivate, while Han Xiao returned to the training base and continued to train everyone according to the original plan. He began to research more on the Sanctums to the point that he was unable to extricate himself from it.

Feidin would come back every few days to give the students a buff.

Everyone was immersed in training every day, and their sense of time had become dull. In the blink of an eye, more than half a year had passed in the intense training.

The battle at the frontline was still going on intensely. The World Tree Army continued to advance despite the harassment of the three Universal Civilizations.

For the past half a year, the forums had been flooded with relevant information, and countless players were enthusiastically exchanging combat intelligence.

As for Han Xiao and the other Beyond Grade As, they were training at the back and had withdrawn from the frontline. They made use of the calm before the storm to increase their strength. Because they were not in the players' sights, there was not much to talk about the Beyond Grade As in the past half a year, hence they faded into the background.

The intensity of the war was equivalent to the frequency of combat missions. Many players in the frontline who were part of the suicide squad earned a fortune. Batch after batch of players reached the version limit of Lv180. Some of the extra experience was used to upgrade their skills, and some of it went to Han Xiao through consumption in the Black Star Army.

Thanks to the high rewards of the suicide mission, the players earned experience faster, which also indirectly shortened the time Han Xiao needed to accumulate experience.

It had not even been a year, but Han Xiao had already gathered enough experience to level up to 360. His efficiency was higher than expected.

After so many years, he finally had the chance to advance again. Han Xiao did not hesitate and chose a good day to come to an uninhabited planet in his territory. He was prepared to invest all his experience to level up and reach the threshold of a new Promotion.

Chapter 1382: The Difficulties of Promotion, The Universe's Vastness

A meteor tore through the dark universe and landed on a dark brown planet, on a barren mountain peak.

Flowing flames scattered, revealing Han Xiao's figure. He looked down at the endless dark brown land, then looked up at the sky with the mysterious aurora and nodded.

"Let's level up here."

Han Xiao focused, opened the interface, and poured all his hard-earned experience into leveling up. His level, which had been stagnant for a long time, finally shot up like a rocket. The interface notifications kept popping up.

[Divine Throne Mechanic] leveled up to Lv41 .+500 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +18 END, +25 INT. You have received 20 Free Attribute Points, +1 Awakening Point.

...

[Divine Throne Mechanic] leveled up to Lv60 (max) .+2,000 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +18 END, +25 INT. You have received 20 Free Attribute Points, +1 Awakening Point.

You have reached the upper limit of the main class. You have triggered the Class Advancement mission—[Godly Craftsman].

[Godly Craftsman]: Have over 10000 blueprints. Accumulate 100 different Universal Treasure-level mechanical equipment.

You have reached level 360. You have triggered the Promotion Mission—[God Slayer's Trial].

[God Slayer's Trial]: Completely kill five Beyond Grade As who possess God's Trait Transformation, one from each of the five major classes - Pugilist, Esper, Mechanic, Mage, and Psychic.

"Wow, so ruthless."

Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

The difficulty of the mission this time was countless times more difficult than the previous Promotion and Class Advancement. The difficulty was on a completely different level. Just the requirement of [Godly Craftsman] to create 100 different types of Universal Treasures was enough to make normal Mechanics dumbfounded. Even Han Xiao was still a distance away from this number. Although the Sanctum provided enough blueprints, he had yet to create all of them.

In addition, [God Slayer's Trial]'s requirement to kill five peak Beyond Grade As was extremely dangerous, and there was the word 'completely' in it. Han Xiao estimated that the individual lifeforms of the World Tree and the Underworld who could revive could not be counted. It was most likely that the deaths would not be counted if they did not enter the Sanctum, and the targets would probably have to be chosen from normal people.

Unfortunately… no matter how harsh the mission was, he had the Mission Completion Card!

Han Xiao had accumulated some Mission Completion Cards over the years to avoid this kind of Promotion Mission. Even if these two missions were more difficult, he would at most be surprised and not feel troubled.

"These two missions are too much. Luckily, I can skip them."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief and used the Mission Completion Card seriously. The two mission names turned into a 'completed' status with a golden font.

He originally thought that this would be like before, as soon as he completed the Promotion mission, it would be equivalent to a successful Promotion. However, the situation this time seemed to be different from the past, and the interface popped up with an unexpected message.

Lv 360 Promotion Mission completed!

You can choose to advance at any time.

Remarks: This Promotion is extremely risky. There is a 90% to 96% chance that the Promotion will fail. If it fails, you will have to complete a new Promotion mission before you can advance again. At the same time, there is a chance that an unknown mutation will occur during the Promotion. There is a risk to your life.

Recommended to complete the conditions below before choosing to advance.

In this Promotion, your life form will be extremely unstable, and it will be extremely easy for you to mutate. What may happen will not be limited to infinite proliferation, gene collapse, cell independence, and cosmic assimilation. Therefore, you will need to use certain special items to stabilize your life form. This condition will be triggered during Promotion. Promotion success rate+33.3%, malignant mutation rate -33.3%.

For this Promotion, you will need some external help. The strength of a single person will always be limited and one-sided. You will need four Supers of different classes as assistants, and they must activate the God's Trait Transformation of their Super system. The higher the level of the God's Trait Transformation, the better the support effect. This condition will be triggered during Promotion. Promotion success rate+33.3%, malignant mutation rate -33.3%.

For this Promotion, you need a Beyonder's Vestige as a catalyst. When a Super who has completed the God's Trait Transformation attempts to reach a higher level, they might die from a malignant mutation. The life essence, soul consciousness, and core energy that dissipates during the Promotion will condense into the Beyonder's Vestige and cannot be observed by normal life forms. Only Supers who are currently in this state will be able to obtain the corresponding perception. This condition will be triggered during the Promotion. Promotion success rate+33.3%, malignant mutation rate -33.3%.

Remarks: If all the conditions are not met, even if the Promotion succeeds, the grade will not change. If three conditions are completely triggered during the Promotion, the Apotheosis Promotion will begin.

"It's actually like this…"

Han Xiao read the messages on the interface, and his eyes sparkled.

Before today, he did not know if he would be able to reach a new grade after the level 360 Promotion. Everything was just a guess. Now, he finally confirmed that he could indeed reach the new grade after this Promotion. Otherwise, there would not be so many changes.

This made him a little excited.

Han Xiao focused his mind on his body and could clearly feel that every cell was in a 'critical' state. As long as he wanted to, he could undergo his Promotion anytime.

However, after looking at the warning notification on the interface, Han Xiao was also afraid that something would happen to his Promotion. He looked down at the content of the three conditions, and they were all in a gray 'not triggered' state.

He tried to use the Mission Completion Card on these three conditions but they did not complete like the Promotion Mission. The hint was that the Mission Completion Card was ineffective on the target.

"As expected, it won't work. It seems like there's no way to pull a fast one."

Han Xiao frowned before letting go. He was not too surprised. When he saw the three conditions, he had already guessed that the Mission Completion Card might not be useful on them.

The Mission Completion Card was a special item used on the interface, and it did not have a physical body. Its function was to skip the mission content and obtain the most basic reward on the interface. It would not change the external environment or create something out of thin air.

These three prerequisites required physical objects to assist in advancement. The Mission Completion Card could not change them, and these three conditions did not exist in the form of a mission.

However, the Mission Completion Card had skipped the previous Promotion Mission and saved him a lot of time. Furthermore, if he failed the Promotion and triggered a new Promotion Mission, he could still use the Mission Completion Card to pass it without spending any energy.

Of course, it was best to complete the Promotion in one go. Han Xiao naturally did not want to fail. Since he could not take a shortcut to break through to the new level, to increase the safety of his Promotion, he could only focus on studying the three conditions carefully. Very soon, he had some ideas.

The first requirement was a special 'stabilizer'. It was probably because this Promotion would result in a life form reorganization, which was more intense than the past Promotions, which was why it was 'extremely unstable'. It was like melting a piece of steel and casting it into another shape, requiring a mold.

Han Xiao had a few ideas about this. Special items in the Information Form could be used as 'molds', but they would most likely require Universal Treasures. Normal Information Form objects might not work.

The other choice was to obtain the enhancement of some Universal Treasures with the 'Stable' trait. Han Xiao knew of a ready-made one, which was the church's National Treasure with the 'Unbreakable' trait. It should be able to achieve similar effects.

"However, this thing is on Wuornos, and it's a precious treasure of the Arcane Church. I wonder if they're willing to temporarily lend it."

Han Xiao shook his head.

The second condition was that he needed the help of the other four peak Beyond Grade As to advance.

If it was a civilization with insufficient individual strength, they might not even be able to gather enough people. However, the three Universal Civilizations should be considered prosperous in the universe, so there were enough strong people to choose from.

With his connections and the Sanctum's cohesiveness, it was not difficult to find four assistants. This should be the easiest of the three conditions.

However, the meaning of cooperation revealed by this condition made Han Xiao feel a little emotional.

Having grown to this stage alone, it seemed like this was the limit. Advancing seemed to no longer be a matter of one person. If one wanted to become a stronger individual, they needed more external help. The development of civilization also affected whether an individual could advance further.

In the vast universe, a person's strength was ultimately limited. Without external help, it would be very difficult to continue moving forward.

"So there is a limit to individual life forms?"

Han Xiao shook his head.

In addition, the requirement of gathering the other four classes also reminded Han Xiao of a saying from his previous life, which was that the five Super systems represented the five aspects of the true 'God'.

The Pugilist class represented the 'divine body', the Psychic class represented the 'divine soul', the Mage class represented the 'divine authority', the Esper class represented the 'divine ability', and the Mechanic class represented the 'divine weapon'!

This kind of statement was widely spread, but there was no actual evidence. However, after seeing this condition, Han Xiao felt that this statement might not be entirely false, at least there was some connection.

"Could it be that the new level combines the five elements?"

This thought subconsciously flashed past Han Xiao's mind, but he quickly shook his head and denied it. He felt that he was wrong.

The difference in the Energy Attributes of the five major systems was unlikely to be broken. Even if he broke through to the level of a 'True God', he would probably be a Specialist, so it should be impossible for him to be omnipotent.

Compared to the other four classes, he felt that the Mechanic class that represented the 'divine weapon' seemed to be special.

The development history of every civilization was the advancement history of tool evolution. This represented the fire of wisdom and the sprout of civilization. To a certain extent, knowing how to use tools was the biggest difference between intelligent life and wild beasts, and to the so-called 'Gods', it probably had a similar meaning.

If 'God' only used the power of the other four elements to fight, they would not be too different from fighting with their bare hands. At most, their moves would be different, and only magic and Esper abilities would have some special effects. However, using the so-called 'divine weapon' was equivalent to an ordinary person picking up a sword or firearm. The threat was completely different.

For example, if there were two max-level heroes—one unequipped, and the other fully equipped with ultimate equipment. Even if their skills were different, their strength would not be on the same level at all. In the many fairy tales that Han Xiao had read in his previous life, the status of 'magical equipment' was extremely high. It even represented one's strength, especially when it came to the primitive worlds.

In his opinion, the 'divine weapon' represented by the Mechanic class was most likely such a concept. Otherwise, the advantages of the Mechanics in the later stages would not be so obvious in front of the other four classes.

Han Xiao calmed himself down and collected his thoughts.

He had some ideas about the first two conditions, but the last condition made him a little frustrated.

The Beyonder's Vestige came from a peak Beyond Grade A who had failed to break through and died. In the explored universe where the three Universal Civilizations were located, the only Beyond Grade As who had similar experiences seemed to be the two sisters of life and death.

However, Onicelu had said that the two sisters of the previous generation were pursuing the true meaning of death, so they had actively died. Han Xiao did not know if that was an act of trying to break through to a new level.

Even if it was true, the bodies of the two sisters from the previous generation had already been burned by Onicelu like firewood, and the two Esper Abilities that held their Information Form were inherited by Hila and Aurora. He did not know if this was considered the so-called 'Beyonder's Vestige'. Even if it was, how should he use it? Could it be that he needed to extract their Esper Abilities?

Wait, if that was the case, if Hila and Aurora grew to this level in the future, wouldn't the third condition be completed for them?

"Tsk. Comparisons are odious."

Han Xiao's eyelids twitched.

He had once tried to use the Mark of The Underworld as a medium to revive the two sisters through Sanctum Revival, but he had failed in the end. They might still be alive, or they might have held back the Information Form and integrated it into their Esper Abilities, causing them to lose the Sanctum Revival. Now, Han Xiao had another guess—when a peak Beyond Grade A failed to break through the new level and died, would they be able to accept the Sanctum Revival?

Perhaps the information form records in the Sanctum had changed because of this, or the ones who failed to break through had survived in another unknown way, such as this so-called Beyonder's Vestige…

No one had stepped into the next level, and everything was filled with mystery. Han Xiao could only guess blindly.

"However, the introduction said that only peak Beyond Grade As in my current state can sense the Beyonder's Vestige. I'll go to the Underworld later to verify it. If it's not, I'll probably have to search the entire universe. If it's the worst-case scenario…"

Han Xiao's eyes darkened.

The worst-case scenario would be that there was no such thing as Beyonder's Vestige in the current Iteration. No one died if they failed to break through to the next level. If that happened, he would have to think of another way.

In any case, he had already decided to trigger as many conditions as possible. He had to overcome all difficulties.

After all, the remark mentioned that as long as one condition was missing, it would only be a regular Promotion, and there would be no way to break through. According to his understanding, this meant that he would not be able to obtain the bonuses of a new grade, and he would not be able to pull apart the fundamental difference like a Beyond Grade A and Calamity Grade Super.

Han Xiao calmed himself down and exhaled.

"No matter what, I have to test my perception of the Beyonder's Vestige."

After saying that, he calmed his mind and searched for the Beyonder's Vestige through the throbbing of his critical state.

Very soon, Han Xiao felt that his consciousness had fallen into an indescribable mystery. It was as if there was a thick fog in front of him, and blurry shadows could be seen in the fog.

After an unknown period of time, Han Xiao suddenly caught a flash of light. His eyes widened, and he finally found this feeling. The fog dissipated, and everything became clear.

Initially, he thought that his senses would be completely empty, and he would not be able to sense much of the Beyonder's Vestige. However, the moment he entered this perception vision, Han Xiao was shocked, and he knew that he was wrong.

Buzz!

In an instant, dozens of sensory sources appeared in his perception and spread out in all directions. However, he only knew the direction and not the distance. They were all Beyonder's Vestiges!

Han Xiao's eyes widened in shock.

Did this mean that there were at least dozens of peak Beyond Grade As from the unknown regions in the entire universe who had reached his level before and died because they were trying to reach a new level ‽

Han Xiao had mixed feelings.

The center of the story that I knew in my previous life was the three Universal Civilizations, but that did not mean that this was the center of the universe.

No matter how strong you were, there would always be someone stronger. At the places you could not see, how many more powerful civilizations were still thriving in the universe and how many things were happening?

No one in the explored universe had broken through to a new level. Was the vast unexplored universe the same?

Is this Iteration only at the early stage?

After a long time, he sighed.

"…The universe is really vast."

Chapter 1383: Deal

Han Xiao sighed, calmed himself down, and shook his head.

No matter how vast the unexplored universe was, or how many powerful unknown civilizations there were, it had nothing to do with him for the time being. The most important thing was to deal with the current problem. The focus was still on the war between the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree.

As for the problem of Iteration, it was useless to think too much about it. He could not deal with it for the time being.

"Although I can sense the existence of the Beyonder's Vestige, I only know the direction and the distance is unknown. This is like finding a needle in a haystack."

Han Xiao pondered.

However, the perception vision was dead, but the person was alive. It was not impossible to calculate distance. After all, the direction of the perception could barely be seen as a straight line. As long as one constantly changed their positioning, through the deviation of the perception line, one could still roughly estimate which one was closer.

However, at the scale of the universe, it was unknown how long it would take to shift the direction of one's perception. It would most likely be based on Star Systems and Star Clusters. Although this method would take some time, it was still an effective method.

The only problem he had to worry about was that if the nearest Beyonder's Vestige was not in the vicinity of the explored universe, it would take an unknown amount of time.

"No matter what, there are at least initial solutions for all three conditions. Let's act according to this plan."

Han Xiao was relieved.

The three conditions were of varying difficulties. The second condition was the easiest. He just had to communicate and activate the Face Fruit[1]. As for the third condition, he did not know how long it would take. He decided to start with the first condition and contact Wuornos.

Han Xiao immediately found Wuornos' private number and called him.

In the previous battle, the two of them had gotten to know each other through fighting. After the battle ended, they exchanged private numbers.

The bell rang twice, and Wuornos' projection appeared on the screen. He was wearing a solemn robe as if his daily prayers had been interrupted.

"Black Star? What's the matter?"

Wuornos asked with an emotionless tone.

Han Xiao smiled but did not immediately get to the main topic. "It's been a while since we last met, and I suddenly miss you."

"Is that so?"

Wuornos' expression was calm, and he was not swayed. He only looked at Han Xiao calmly and did not say anything, as if saying 'is our relationship that good?'

Han Xiao stroked his chin and said with interest, "Speaking of which, I've been curious recently. As the strongest member of the Direct Line, why didn't the church let you participate in the interception battle?"

"This is an internal secret. I can't tell you. If you're here to persuade me to join the battle, then forget it," Wuornos' tone was calm, "Do you have anything else?"

Tsk, so mysterious. Is the church worried that you will die in battle and lose their National Treasure?

Han Xiao thought to himself.

Seeing that Wuornos' attitude was neither cold nor warm, he did not continue to beat around the bush and spoke of his main goal.

"I came to you this time because I have something to discuss with you… I want to borrow the church's National Treasure."

Hearing this, Wuornos' eyes flashed, but he did not reject it immediately.

"What do you want to do with it?"

"I want to try to break through to the next grade. I feel like the church's National Treasure will come in handy." Han Xiao did not hide this goal.

"Oh? Are you going to try to take this step? As expected of the most talented Super in history…"

Wuornos' eyes lit up. He was not surprised but delighted. He sized Han Xiao up and smiled.

He had always thought highly of Black Star and felt that Black Star was the most likely person to open a higher level.

As long as a pioneer took a path, future generations would be able to follow it. Whether they succeeded or failed, they would become important references for future generations. Therefore, Wuornos was very happy to know that Han Xiao was breaking through to a higher level.

"From my personal point of view, I'm very happy to help you. Maybe you can become a pioneer in the path of individual strength exploration, and I can also benefit from it. There's no reason to reject you…"

Wuornos smiled.

However, before Han Xiao could reply, he changed the topic and shook his head.

"However, the church's National Treasure is not my private property. If you want to borrow it, you'll have to seek the Arcane Church's approval. If they don't agree, I won't be able to lend it to you."

Hearing this, Han Xiao was not surprised and nodded.

"Of course, I understand. Help me tell the upper echelons of the church that the conditions can be negotiated. I need you to help me convince the upper echelons of the church."

"…Alright, I'll speak for you."

Wuornos nodded and did not refuse.

Other than the upper echelons of the church, no one else could order someone like him to do things. However, seeing that Black Star was trying to reach a new level, he did not mind helping him.

The two of them chatted for a while before Han Xiao hung up.

The result of the initial negotiations was still acceptable, and Wuornos did not have any objections. In that case, he only needed to deal with the upper echelons of the Arcane Church.

Of course, the upper echelons of the church would not give in so easily. He had to take out some of the chips that they cared about. All he had to do now was wait for the church to come and negotiate.

...

On the other side, the Arcane Church, the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods.

After Wuornos received Han Xiao's call, he quickly contacted the Pope.

With his identity, he could speak to the Pope directly. Very soon, the projection of the Pope appeared on the screen.

"High Priest, what's the matter?"

The Pope was a little surprised. Wuornos seldom took the initiative to look for him. Usually, he was the one who called and gave the order. He was a little surprised to suddenly receive the call.

Wuornos had no intention of chatting and went straight to the point. "Black Star contacted me just now to borrow the church's National Treasure. I contacted you to discuss it."

The Pope was slightly stunned. He looked at Wuornos in surprise and almost could not believe his ears.

"Lend the National Treasure to an outsider ‽ Do you know what you're saying ‽"

"Black Star said we can negotiate."

Wuornos' tone was calm.

The Pope suppressed his emotions and asked with a frown,

"…Why does he want to borrow the National Treasure?"

"Black Star said that he wants to borrow the power of the National Treasure and attempt to break through to a new grade of individual strength."

"New grade? You mean above Beyond Grade A ‽"

Hearing this, the Pope was shocked.

This was big news. As the leader of the current Beyond Grade As, if Black Star could successfully establish a new level of individual strength, it would have an unknown and profound impact on battle with the World Tree.

In truth, because of Black Star's record-breaking growth speed, the three Universal Civilizations were all prepared for Black Star to reach a higher grade, but they did not expect it to happen so quickly. After all, no matter how strong Black Star was, he had only stepped into the Beyond Grade A realm for a few decades. When compared to the lifespan of a Beyond Grade A, he was too young, at the stage of a baby or a kid.

"…You want to help him?"

The Pope's tone sank.

Even if he wanted to borrow the National Treasure, he had to seek Wuornos' opinion. Since he had come to help Black Star pass the message, he had most likely already agreed. This made the Pope a little unhappy.

Wuornos looked straight ahead and said calmly,

"Why not? Isn't it beneficial for our side to have an expert that goes beyond the norm?"

"That may be the case, but you know the significance of the National Treasure and the threat that Black Star poses…"

The Pope paused. Although he did not finish his sentence, his meaning was clear enough.

Due to the revelation of the truth behind the Sanctum Revival, the three Universal Civilizations were even warier of Han Xiao. Although the war was the most important now, they did not want to see Black Star continue to become stronger, especially since it was an unprecedented new grade. No one knew how powerful the strength at that grade was.

Furthermore, he had more considerations. During the exploration era, after the first Primordial One successfully broke through, the other Beyond Grade As appeared one after another. No one knew if Black Star stepping into the higher level would stimulate the growth of the other Beyond Grade As, and the importance of individual strength would increase.

Wuornos did not take it to heart and slowly said, "Based on my experience, it's not that easy to break through to a new grade. Black Star is still in the experimental stage, and he can't succeed without failing a few times. It's still unknown if the National Treasure will come in handy, and his chances of failing are very high."

The Pope narrowed his eyes and did not speak.

Seeing this, Wuornos paused and continued,

"…So, I feel that lending out the National Treasure might not give Black Star any benefits, but we will definitely be able to benefit from him."

"Then what do you think we should propose?" the Pope asked.

"What I mean is to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. It has been sealed for too long."

"Hmm… it's not impossible."

Hearing this, the Pope narrowed his eyes and pondered.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter had long been frozen by Han Xiao using the Spacetime Amber. Originally, it had been snatched away by the Federation of Light and returned in a joint operation. However, the Arcane Church's research department was also unable to unseal it. They could only see that it could not be used. Currently, only Black Star could unseal it.

Releasing this Universal Treasure was still a little tempting. This was a powerful weapon that could kill individual strengths. It was useful both internally and externally.

This time, Wuornos struck while the iron was hot and said slowly, "I know you're worried about accidents, but the National Treasure has already fused with me. Even if Black Star has other intentions, he won't be able to do anything. The risk is very low, and in the current situation, the chances of Black Star turning against us are very low."

As a member of the Arcane Church, he had a lot of authority, but he rarely made suggestions and usually did not care about anything. However, at this moment, he took the initiative to speak up for Han Xiao. He really wanted to facilitate the cooperation between the two parties and observe Black Star's method to break through to a new grade.

Wuornos was rather curious about why Black Star felt that the church's National Treasure would be able to help him break through to the new grade.

He had been in possession of the National Treasure for so many years, but he had yet to discover it had this use. Could it be that the church's National Treasure had some other function that he did not understand?

...

In the Underworld Dimension, a light flashed, and Han Xiao teleported over.

At this time, the two sisters were not there. Hila was cultivating in Soul Terminal. At first, Aurora was still stubborn and focused on cultivating, but later, she could not help but go to the Soul Terminal and let Hila supervise her special training while cultivating.

Therefore, of the four Beyond Grade A officers of the army, three were in the Soul Terminal, and only Lothaire was outside, training Karlot.

Han Xiao activated the Beyonder's Vestige vision and quickly scanned the Underworld.

"There's no Beyonder's Vestige here… Looks like I'm overthinking. I'll check with Hila and the others later."

Han Xiao shook his head and sighed.

After he finished chatting with Wuornos, he immediately came here to look for clues. He planned to start by looking around him. If the outstanding people around him did not have the Beyonder's Vestige, he would then calculate the locations.

Beep beep beep—

This time, the communicator rang again. It was Wuornos.

"He called back so quickly? It's only been a few minutes?"

Han Xiao picked up the call.

Wuornos appeared on the screen and said, "Black Star, the Arcane Church wishes to make a deal with you. We can lend you the National Treasure once, but you have to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. Also, the Sanctum Revival will be free for the next three times."

"Woah, three free times is way too much. I'm only borrowing the National Treasure once. This price is too high. I think unsealing the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is enough."

Han Xiao did not mind the Sanctum Revival being free a few times, but since it was a negotiation, he had to fight for it.

The church's request for the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was one of the few possibilities that he had come up with. Due to the war and other factors, he had already planned to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, so using it as a bargaining chip was just right.

The two of them negotiated for a while and quickly came to a consensus. The price would be unsealing the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter and 30% off for the next three Sanctum Revivals.

"It's settled then. Let me know when you need to borrow the National Treasure."

"Alright. I might need your help with something else too. We'll talk when the time comes."

"Sure."

Wuornos hung up immediately.

Han Xiao put down the communicator and pondered.

"This guy is really efficient. He's also very passionate about the higher levels, but he's so enthusiastic about helping me break through to a new grade. Could it be that he wants me to be a lab rat… Heh, no matter what he thinks, as long as I confirm that the church's National Treasure can be used as a 'stabilizer', the first request will be resolved. This is a good sign".

Han Xiao revealed a relaxed smile. Luckily, he had the bargaining chip of Ten Thousand Deity Scepter in his hands and never used it. Otherwise, it would not have been so easy.

[1] This is a slang used in China, based on the anime One Piece that has a Devil Fruit for all kinds of skill. In this case, it's for Face, since giving face is important to the Chinese Back

Chapter 1384: Beyonder's Vestige, Remnant Consciousness Body

After finalizing the conditions for borrowing of the church's National Treasure, Han Xiao spent a lot of time carefully calculating the distance of each Beyonder's Vestige, but the result shocked him.

He had originally thought that all the Beyonder's Vestige might be in the unexplored area of the universe. Because it was too far away, he could only estimate the distance. However, he did not expect to actually locate one of the sensory sources. It was very close, and surprisingly, it was in the Ancient Star Desert!

This surprised him greatly.

The most frightening thing was that all the Beyonder's Vestige were too far away. If that was the case, who knew how long it would take. He was all prepared to go on a long journey, but he did not expect a surprise. In this case, it would be much easier to achieve this Promotion requirement.

However, on top of being happy, Han Xiao was also very curious about which brother had left this legacy.

After obtaining the location data, Han Xiao did not delay and immediately set off for the Ancient Star Desert to find his target.

...

Ancient Star Desert, a desolate universe belt.

This was a space zone without any celestial bodies. Suddenly, there was a flash of dazzling starlight in the distance. A stream of hyperdrive light shot over from afar and stopped in the area, revealing Han Xiao in his mechanical suit.

"The location is near here. Speaking of which, there doesn't seem to be anything special here. Is there really no problem with the perception?"

Han Xiao thought to himself as he observed his surroundings. He only felt that this area was ordinary and did not have anything worth paying attention to. He did not notice anything unusual with normal Beyond Grade A perception as well.

He calmed himself down and activated his Beyonder's Vestige perception vision to sense his surroundings. The originally normal environment suddenly changed.

A white mist of light appeared out of thin air, slowly changing shape, floating and moving, looking very inconspicuous.

"This is Beyonder's Vestige?"

Han Xiao was surprised.

If not for the fact that his senses were pointing at this ball of light, he would have thought that he was mistaken. The appearance of the Beyonder's Vestige was very different from what he had imagined. He had thought that it would be more gorgeous.

He focused his eyes and looked carefully. Suddenly, his eyes moved, and he realized that the fog was actually made up of particles with a very strange microscopic form. He had mastered so many techniques, but he had never seen such a particle before. He felt a strange sense of harmony from it, which made him think of the word 'perfect'.

"It's said that the Beyonder's Vestige condenses the life essence, soul consciousness, and core energy of the dead during their advancement. It's equivalent to turning everything of a Super into this particle and retaining it in this form. This particle form might be the key to a higher level…"

Han Xiao murmured.

As a researcher, he did not touch this Beyonder's Vestige immediately. Instead, he first recorded this particle form and stored it in an encrypted database. If anything happened during this trip, he could study it himself in the future.

After doing this, Han Xiao calmed down and let out a long breath.

"Done… Let me see what secrets the Beyonder's Vestige has."

As he spoke, Han Xiao reached out his hand and tried to touch the target. However, his hand passed through it as if the light was just a mirage.

He raised his brows and tried to use his energy to guide it again, but it was still ineffective. The Beyonder's Vestige was still unaffected and continued to float.

With the attitude of experimenting, Han Xiao tried all kinds of methods, but the results were the same. Even [Bold Explorer] did not work. Only then did he finally confirm that there was no way to capture the Beyonder's Vestige.

"It seems like even if the external environment changes, Beyonder's Vestige will not be affected. Only living beings in my critical state can come into contact with it…"

Han Xiao recalled the experience of activating his perception vision back then. He felt the rhythm of the cells in his critical state, which was similar to meditation. His mind kept sinking into the deep sea of his consciousness.

After a while, Han Xiao suddenly felt a change. It was as if a ripple was spreading in his body, echoing throughout. It gave him a slight electric shock on the cell level, forming a resonance.

Han Xiao opened his eyes and touched the Beyonder's Vestige once again. This time, he finally felt something solid. It felt like his palm was inserted into the core of a star, and it was extremely hot.

This Beyonder's Vestige finally reacted. The light fog wrapped around Han Xiao's arm and climbed up bit by bit. A suction force came from within, as though it wanted to slowly swallow him up. If it had been indifferent just now, it was now passionately surrounding him, not wanting Han Xiao to leave its body.

Just as Han Xiao was experiencing this feeling, this Beyonder's Vestige seemed to have been stimulated. It suddenly shrank, then exploded with a loud bang. A dazzling light instantly gushed out and covered Han Xiao's entire body.

His vision instantly turned into a white world.

"What is this?"

Han Xiao suddenly lost his sense of position and immediately tried to retreat. However, he realized that no matter how he moved, he could not walk out of this white world. The white light around him extended endlessly, as though there was no end to it.

"Was I brought to the alternate dimension?"

Han Xiao was shocked. He activated the King mechanical suit in his body and prepared to teleport.

However, at this moment, a spiritual body covered in blue light suddenly appeared from the void and floated not far in front of Han Xiao. Only its outline was visible, and the details of its appearance were covered by the dazzling blue light.

An ancient sigh followed.

"You're finally here…"

"!!"

A living person ‽

Han Xiao was shocked. He stared at the blue spiritual entity and was shocked.

Just as he was about to ask about this person's identity, a terrifying mental shockwave suddenly broke through the mental barrier and rushed into his brain!

At this moment, a sharp pain exploded from his brain and shook his soul.

Han Xiao pressed down on his head and clenched his teeth. He felt as if someone had thrown his brain into a blender.

He hurriedly opened the interface and saw that his health was depleting at an unbelievable speed.

The damage notifications popped up and entered Han Xiao's vision. He immediately understood the situation.

It was not that easy to obtain the Beyonder's Vestige. If he wanted to absorb it into his body, he would have to endure an extremely high burden. While obtaining someone else's inheritance, he would have to accept their 'debt'.

According to the different causes of death of the Beyonder's Vestige's owner, the burden was also different. It was equivalent to the inheritor having to take the test and undergo a weakened version of the malignant mutation. It was the same type of danger as the Beyonder's Vestige's owner when he advanced.

This Beyonder's Vestige's owner died due to cosmic assimilation during his Promotion. The remaining soul consciousness had already partially fused with the universe consciousness, which resulted in a strong mental load. It contained the psychic impact of the universe consciousness, and its power was stronger than any Beyond Grade A mental attack that Han Xiao had ever experienced.

At this time, the spiritual entity finally spoke again.

"Since the impact has already begun, there's no way to stop it. Either we succeed or we die."

Han Xiao used all his strength to activate his recovery ability. Enduring the pain, he forced himself to focus and asked, "Who are you?"

"I'm just a product formed by my remaining soul consciousness. I'm no longer me. All that's left is my incomplete memories and personality, as well as the obsession that supports my existence," the spiritual entity said calmly.

"Are you the predecessor of this Beyonder's Vestige?"

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

He had thought that the original owner had completely disappeared, but he did not expect that there would still be a remnant consciousness. Could it be that the other Beyonder's Vestiges were also the same?

At this time, the spiritual entity shook its head and said,

"I died when I was trying to break through to a higher level, but for some reason, I did not die completely. I continued to exist in this form. So, this is called Beyonder's Vestige…"

He did not have the interface like Han Xiao, and did not know the reason and could not explain what had happened to him, nor did he know the secrets of the Beyonder's Vestige.

"What's your name?" Han Xiao could not help but ask. He was still curious about which Beyond Grade A in history this person was.

"Tyrsius," the spiritual entity replied.

Han Xiao quickly recalled and realized that there was no such person in history.

"Which era's Beyond Grade A are you? The exploration era or the Galaxy Calendar?"

"Beyond Grade A?" Tyrsius was confused. "What's that?"

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment before realizing something.

"Have you heard of the three Universal Civilizations? The Crimson Dynasty, the Federation of Light, and the Arcane Church…"

Tyrsius shook his head. "I'm from Planet Cree, a wanderer of the universe. I've never heard of the three Universal Civilizations."

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat.

If this part of his memory was not incomplete, then this guy was not a Beyond Grade A from the explored universe, but a guest from the unexplored universe. The reason he appeared here was probably that the Beyonder's Vestige had slowly drifted over after his death.

However, at this moment, Tyrsius suddenly paused and said thoughtfully, "Wait, I seem to have some impression of the Westsandling Civilization that you mentioned. I think I passed by a Star System civilization like this."

Hearing this, Han Xiao was shocked.

Westsandling was the Federation of Light's real name. If what this guy said was true, then he might have guessed wrong. This guy did not float over after his death, but he is an extremely ancient existence that had come to this region before the Federation of Light rose.

Han Xiao's heart sank slightly. After receiving the Beyonder's Vestige perception, he had a vague guess that this might not be the early stage of the Iteration, and the origin of Tyrsius seemed to confirm this guess.

Right at this moment, the mental shockwave passed its peak and finally subsided. Han Xiao immediately felt much better. Although it was very dangerous, he could still endure it with his tankiness.

Han Xiao felt much more relaxed. Just as he was about to ask Tyrsius more details, he suddenly realized that Tyrsius' figure had become blurry.

Tyrsius seemed to have expected this and took the initiative to explain.

"I died in the cosmic assimilation. If you can endure the burden, everything I left behind will be yours. When you succeed, it will be the day my remaining consciousness dies."

"You…"

"I died a long time ago, and this is also a relief for me. The steps to a higher level are often forged by the deaths of the predecessors, so don't worry about it."

Tyrsius was rather open-minded.

Hearing this, Han Xiao had a strange expression.

To him, Tyrsius was just a stranger who had suddenly popped out of nowhere. He did not have any relationship with him, so he naturally did not feel anything. He just felt that this encounter was a little unexpected. He still had many things he wanted to ask this guy.

Furthermore, he doubted if this remnant consciousness would really disappear if he absorbed the Beyonder's Vestige.

After all, one had to be wary of others. Han Xiao did not completely believe the other party's words.

Chapter 1385: Coordinates

Just as he was about to say something, Han Xiao suddenly realized that a set of coordinates had appeared in his mind. It was a message from Tyrsius.

Han Xiao looked at Tyrsius in doubt.

"What coordinates did you give me?"

Tyrsius shook his head and sighed.

"My hometown is my lingering obsession. Although I was born on Planet Cree, I left very early. When I was young, I surpassed all my predecessors, broke all records, and became the strongest person in the entire civilization. My civilization could no longer provide me with any help. To pursue a higher level of individual strength, I left the galaxy alone. This journey lasted countless years.

There were no worthy opponents in my hometown. I tried to find someone of my standard in the entire universe, hoping to learn from them. In my life as a wanderer, I spent most of my time with the desolate universe. I rarely met people, but I had seen strong and weak civilizations come and go. I would only make an appearance when I met powerful Supers, other than that, I would not interfere with the normal development of these civilizations. During that time, I only focused on the road ahead of me and wanted to become stronger and stronger. Even till the day I died, I did not return to my hometown even once.

I've been dead for many years and have been trapped here. I did not have any perception of the outside world and have long accepted reality. However, the only thing I can't let go of is my hometown. I have nothing to do here and the only thing I can comfort myself with is the incomplete memories of the past. It's just that my initial firm pursuit of a higher level and the wonderful experience of wandering the universe has become fainter, yet, the childhood times spent in my hometown have become more and more clear.

Back then, I could have chosen to stay and help build my hometown, but I was unwilling to do so. I wandered for the sake of a higher goal. But now, I miss my hometown more and more. So many years have passed, and I don't know how my hometown is now. You have inherited my Beyonder's Vestige, so if it's convenient for you, I request you to go over and take a look for me. The coordinates I gave you are the location of Planet Cree. I hope you can take care of them for my sake."

After hearing his explanation, Han Xiao raised his brows with a strange expression.

"Don't you know that it's best not to allow foreigners to come into contact with other civilizations? You don't know anything about me. Aren't you afraid that I'll bring people to invade if you give me the coordinates of your hometown?"

Tyrsius smiled faintly.

"You're the only person who has come in all these years. I'm about to die, so who else can I give it to if not you? Let's take the risk. There's nothing guaranteed in this world. Otherwise, I wouldn't have fought against my sense of danger to pursue a higher level and end up dying… Also, I don't think you're an invader."

"Making such a conclusion after only seeing me once is too hasty." Han Xiao shook his head. "I can help you take a look, but I won't promise anything. Also, I don't think a powerful Universal Civilization needs my care."

"You're mistaken. My civilization isn't particularly developed."

Tyrus sighed.

"You can withstand the impact of the cosmic assimilation, and I can feel how strong you are. On the other hand, I'm sure you think I'm very strong, but in fact, when I left my hometown, I was far from this state. At that time, it was very difficult for me to destroy a planet, and all my strength came from constantly breaking through while wandering… The experience I accumulated should have been brought back to my hometown, giving birth to more experts, but unfortunately, I died, and all these plans came to an end."

Hearing this, Han Xiao started to calculate.

It sounded like when Tyrsius first started wandering, his strength should have been between a high Calamity Grade and an ordinary Beyond Grade A. The latter was more likely, and he had ascended to the peak of the Beyond Grade A realm step by step during his long and lonely journey. He had felt the existence of a higher level, and he had reached this step without any experience.

Looking at it this way, Tyrsius is also an extremely talented individual, probably not inferior to me… ahem, not inferior to all the genius Supers in the history of the three Universal Civilizations.

If what the other party said was true, then their civilization should be like a remote village, not as strong as he had imagined. However, a genius had appeared there, just like how Planet Aquamarine had produced him.

If Tyrsius had managed to return to his hometown with his experience and insights, there might have been another civilization with a relatively advanced individual strength in the universe.

Thinking about it this way, the Supers born in the three Universal Civilizations were lucky. There were many strong people here, and there were many opponents that they could exchange pointers with. As for a small civilization like Tyrsius', if they wanted to find opponents, they could only travel far away and be a lonely Pathfinder.

While he was thinking, the interface suddenly pinged.

[You have triggered the mission: Shadow of the Past!]

[Mission Introduction: In order to explore the path ahead, Tyrsius wandered the universe alone and never returned to his hometown. He wants you to take a look on his behalf.]

[Mission Requirements: Arrive at Planet Cree]

[Reward: 2,000,000,000 Experience, 1 Character Summon Card]

"I got a Mission…"

Han Xiao's heart skipped a beat.

He did not know if his nature was so open and sincere, or if he felt liberated, or if he had special feelings for his successor.

Tyrsius' figure was getting fainter and fainter, almost disappearing. He did not mind and only smiled.

"It seems like my time is almost up. After so many years of loneliness, I'm satisfied to have someone to talk to at the end of my journey…"

Han Xiao looked at him muttering to himself. Although it was an unexpected encounter, this first time was also the last. Originally, Tyrsius' wandering knowledge was a precious channel to understand more unknown civilizations, but there was not enough time.

However, at this moment, Tyrsius seemed to have thought of something, before whispering,

"By the way, let me give you a piece of advice. If you meet a civilization called the World Tree one day, you'd better run as far as you can…"

Han Xiao was stunned, his face changing rapidly.

However, before he could ask about the details, Tyrsius' figure completely disappeared, leaving only a faint sigh.

"I've never left anything for the civilization in my life. What a failure…"

The blue figure in front of Han Xiao turned into light particles and disappeared.

At the same time, the mental burden that was getting weaker and weaker finally stopped.

The white alternate space in front of him suddenly collapsed, and Han Xiao was left in a daze. He realized that his vision had returned to the main material universe, and he was still there, having not moved at all.

The Beyonder's Vestige had already fused into his body and was fully assimilated, but it did not have any further reaction with him.

Even though Han Xiao had gotten the Beyonder's Vestige, he did not feel too excited about that, only secretly feeling a headache.

"To stop speaking halfway at the most crucial point, you really need to be beaten up. You should have told me about the World Tree Civilization earlier…"

Han Xiao was resigned, he had no choice and could only complain.

After all, Tyrsius did not know that they were fighting the World Tree Civilization. If not for the other party mentioning it, he would not have known that Tyrsius had met the World Tree Civilization before.

"It sounds like this guy has seen the aggressiveness of the World Tree. Maybe they have crossed paths before. Would the World Tree still remember this guy?"

Han Xiao pondered.

Very soon, he shook his head and put this matter aside for the time being. He turned around to study the Beyonder's Vestige in his body. This was his main goal.

After absorbing the Beyonder's Vestige, his strength did not change at all. He could only sense its existence at any time as if it was simply absorbed by his body.

This vestige should only be activated during the Promotion and become a catalyst for his Promotion. He roughly guessed that regardless of whether the Promotion succeeded or not, the Beyonder's Vestige would be consumed. This was a one-time use item.

"The higher levels require the skeletons of the predecessors… Tsk, turn into a salary and burn yourself to benefit the future generations. No matter what, I owe you a favor."

Han Xiao exhaled.

Although he was dead, Han Xiao still remembered this favor. The next time he entered the Sanctum, he planned to see if he could revive this guy, but the chances were very low.

As someone who left a Beyonder's Vestige, Han Xiao did not know if he had left an Information Form like the two sisters in the past. Even if he died now, he might not be able to benefit from the Sanctum Revival. Han Xiao only planned to do his best.

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and smiled.

"Speaking of which, in the explored universe, this is the only piece of the Beyonder's Vestige that was the easiest to obtain. If Wuornos reaches this level one day, he can only search for other Beyonder's Vestiges."

Han Xiao was amused.

Since Wuornos was so willing to help him advance, he might have intended to use him as a guinea pig to explore the path, but he did not know that the only advanced material in the area was lost to him.

Perhaps Wuornos did not have a notification on the interface, so he could not dig out the sensing of the Beyonder's Vestige, or maybe he did not enter the critical state and was still stuck on the mission. Anyway, he had been practically camping below a treasure unawares. In the end, he lost that treasure to Han Xiao instead.

Feeling the Beyonder's Vestige in his body, Han Xiao smiled. Although he was a little surprised, he still managed to obtain a Vestige in the end. It went better than he had expected. It was not in vain that he had gathered so many mascots in the army.

This way, out of the three advancement requirements, he would only have to find four pretty boys to help him.

Han Xiao's nerves finally relaxed. He then started to think about the coordinates of Planet Cree sent by Tyrsius.

"There will definitely be risks if I rashly come into contact with an unknown civilization. Although Tyrsius said that his civilization isn't strong, that's all in the past. Now that so many years have passed, they might have become a powerful Universal Civilization. Furthermore, we can't rule out the possibility of Tyrsius lying…"

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao still felt that he had to go and take a look. He could come and go as he pleased with the King, thus he planned to send out his Lord's Avatar like a real Mechanic to take a look. He did not plan to take the risk himself.

On one hand, he wanted to complete the mission and see what would happen next. On the other hand, he felt that the civilization of Tyrsius might be a potential ally, and they might be able to fight the World Tree together. After all, the World Tree's style and mechanism could be said to be the public enemy of most intelligent civilizations.

...

Two days later, in a certain Federation of Light military base in the Ancient Star Desert.

A Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was slowly heating up, and a Lord's Avatar shell was waiting in the teleportation area. Han Xiao was watching from afar in the base with the respectful senior officer beside him.

Han Xiao's Face Fruit had already reached the Large Success stage. There was no chance of being rejected if he borrowed the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device from the Federation of Light.

Looking at the two gigantic mechanical rings spinning rapidly and turning into a halo, Han Xiao could not help but sigh.

"Your Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device is truly a convenient invention. As long as you have the coordinates, you can go anywhere in the universe."

"Indeed. This is the highest technological achievement of our Federation of Light." The base commander straightened his back with pride.

"Impressive. Can I bring it back for research?"

"This… Please don't make things difficult for me." The senior officer was stunned and smiled bitterly.

Han Xiao smiled and did not tease this officer anymore. He activated his Lord's Avatar.

At this time, the power of the teleportation device reached its peak. Suddenly, light exploded, and the Avatar disappeared.

Han Xiao's vision changed, and he arrived outside the atmosphere of a planet. Before him was a dark green planet.

Satellites were floating in the orbit of the planet. They did not seem to have any problems on the surface, but with a quick glance, Han Xiao could tell that these satellites had not been repaired for many years. They had all been corroded and turned into scrap metal. Vegetation covered the entire surface of the planet, and with a rough glance, he could not see any signs of a civilization city. Furthermore, there were no signs of life. It gave off a desolate feeling of decline.

Only a single brown metal tower was eye-catching. Looking down from outer space, it looked like this planet was wearing a small pointy hat. Looking at the ratio, one would know that this metal tower was extremely huge when looking at it from surface level.

It looked very rough, like countless metal objects of different shapes stacked together. The structure was loose, like a huge garbage mountain.

"This is Planet Cree? Looks like something happened…"

As Han Xiao was pondering, his pupils suddenly constricted, and he quickly adjusted his vision mode. His sight expanded rapidly, and he locked onto a small black dot that was slowly moving halfway up the metal tower.

It was a robot covered in rust, carrying a metal fragment that was many times larger than itself on its back. It slowly climbed up the steep path toward the top of the metal tower. In Han Xiao's vision, it was the only moving thing.

Han Xiao controlled the Lord's Avatar to descend in front of the robot and revealed himself.

However, this robot did not seem to notice him and walked past him. When he passed by, Han Xiao could still hear the robot repeating the same word over and over again.

"Bury it… Bury it…"

Chapter 1386: Calamity of Technology, Psionic Wave Transmitter

"It looks like a low-level artificial intelligence… no, it might also be a mechanical body without any artificial intelligence. Furthermore, its technology level is low, not exceeding the upper limit of a Star System civilization…"

Han Xiao watched as the robot passed by him. With his experience, he could tell the technology level of this robot with a single glance.

He raised his hand slightly and aimed at the back of the transport robot. A magnetic force was released from his palm.

Buzz!

The robot flew backward uncontrollably and attached itself to the Lord's Avatar's hand. It was unable to move, and only its hands and feet could still move. It was like a turtle whose shell had been grabbed.

A few tiny blue snake-like electric arcs followed the arm of the Lord's Avatar and quickly swam to the surface of the robot's body, entering its body through the gaps in the armor. He immediately read the current state of this robot. Only its basic functions were still operating with difficulty. Most of its parts were severely damaged, almost to the point of being scrap.

At the same time, the item introduction popped up on the interface, and Han Xiao took a look.

[7-5 Transport Robot]: Arthur Civilization's common transport-type bionic robot. Low artificial intelligence, possesses strong biochemical tendons and engineering mechanical components. Has magnetic devices and simple self-defense weapons. Commonly used for land transportation.

Remark: This machine is manufactured in Meg Corporation's Workshop No. 5 of Planet Cree. Product Number: TOV-2144G87M—"Good machine, beauty pageant!"

"An ordinary transport robot?"

Han Xiao was curious. He used his Mechanical Force to hack into the unprotected chip and quickly copied the logic code and memory log.

The basic codes that the other party used were not related to the explored universe, but they were not difficult for Han Xiao. He easily analyzed them and understood most of them.

A series of deciphered codes appeared in Han Xiao's quantum network vision. He quickly browsed through them and realized that the basic logic was the transportation robot code format that had no abnormalities. It should have had low artificial intelligence, but because there was no one to maintain it for a long time, there were some malfunctions in the data, causing the artificial intelligence level to decrease. It could barely maintain the core logic and carry out a long-term order.

This order was to bury a special machine, but in the database of a low artificial intelligence transport robot, there was naturally no detailed explanation of the purpose of this machine and why it was buried.

From the data of this transport robot, Han Xiao could only see the appearance and position of this machine. It looked like the peaks of two pyramid-shaped objects were connected, like an hourglass placed horizontally. The location was below this metal tower.

The memory log, on the other hand, was intermittent. Due to the malfunction, there was a large number of gaps, and there were not even timestamps. He could only tell the time by the height of the metal tower in the transportation robot's memory. The height in the earliest memory file was about a quarter of the current height of the metal tower. This robot was already alone at that time.

Most of the memories of the transport robot were of 'building' this metal tower. The other memories were of searching for spare parts in the warehouse of the abandoned factory, changing the heavily damaged parts of its body, and charging them.

"Why does this look so familiar…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin. He felt like he had seen something similar in an old movie in his previous life.

Other than these things, there was nothing else of value in this robot. Han Xiao turned off the magnetic device, and the robot fell back to the ground. The metal fragment on its back also fell to the side, following the metal tower.

The transport robot stayed on the spot for two seconds and did not bother about Han Xiao. It turned around and walked down the mountain as if it was looking for new 'building material', as though nothing had happened.

Han Xiao watched it disappear before looking at the interface.

At this time, the [Shadow of the Past] mission had been completed, and Han Xiao immediately calculated. There was a small amount of experience and a Tyrsius Character Summon Card. The ability was called 'Mind Cleanse', and its effect was to expel one's negative status. It could only be used three times at most, which was quite useful.

At the same time, a new mission popped up.

You have triggered the mission [Secret of Extinction]!

Mission Introduction: You agreed to Tyrsius' request and came to his home planet, Cree, but something seems to have happened here.

Mission Requirements: Find out the reason behind the extinction of Arthur Civilization.

Reward: 5 Billion EXP, 1 Awakening Point

"This civilization is extinct?"

Han Xiao was stunned.

He immediately felt that the destruction of the civilization was most likely related to the unknown mechanical device that was suppressed under the metal tower.

However, Han Xiao thought about it and did not bother. With a flash, he turned into a stream of light and escaped. Very soon, he stopped in front of an abandoned factory. It was the headquarters in the memory of the transport robot.

It looked like a large mechanical factory, but it was covered in vegetation. The surrounding ruined buildings were all covered by dense trees.

Han Xiao looked at it, and with a wave of his hand, a gale swept away the vegetation and dust on the factory door, revealing a sign written in unfamiliar words.

"This is probably the factory of that Meg Corporation, the place where that robot was produced…"

Han Xiao could not understand the language of this civilization and guessed.

He walked in with large strides and saw that the scrapped assembly lines were neatly arranged, with some unfinished transport robots hanging on them. It looked like they had suddenly stopped working.

Han Xiao looked around and realized that all the energy equipment in the factory had been destroyed. The damage seemed to have been caused by an electromagnetic pulse. The only thing that was still working was a charging station, but the wires buried underground had been dug out and connected to a small, crude generator.

He had originally wanted to see if the factory mainframe had a more detailed database, and it would be best if he could find the star map of this civilization's territory. However, the chipset of the factory mainframe had also been destroyed and could not be turned on. Furthermore, all the data had been wiped out, and nothing could be found.

"From the looks of it, all the equipment in this factory seems to have been damaged by an impact that can destroy electrical and energy devices. They were instantly destroyed."

Han Xiao summoned his mechanical army and searched the entire planet. Very soon, he found the remains of cities covered by plants. All the energy and electrical devices were in the same state.

Furthermore, not only were there no intelligent life forms on this planet, there were no beasts or insects to be seen either. It was as though all life forms other than plants were extinct.

In addition, in some city residences, there were bowls and plates of food on the table, and clusters of rotten clothes were scattered on the ground. All signs indicated that the life forms on the entire planet seemed to have disappeared at the same time.

"What happened? Everyone disappeared overnight. It seems like that transport robot was the only survivor…"

Han Xiao was even more curious.

He turned around and returned to the metal tower. His entire body was wrapped in the repulsion force field, and he immediately entered the bottom of the tower. He walked forward with large strides, and the pile of metal waste in front of him was smoothly pushed to the side, creating a path.

Not long after, he walked to the central area and saw a pile of construction debris. It had been crushed by a mountain of trash, and there were all kinds of experimental equipment scattered around. It seemed to have once been a research base.

A scanning light shot out from the Lord's Avatar's eyes, and it immediately saw a large space underground. It looked like an underground base in the past, but it was also crushed by the huge weight above and filled with metal scraps.

After scanning for a while, he finally locked onto the target. The hourglass-like unknown device was pressed into the trash pile, making it difficult to distinguish it.

Han Xiao released his Mechanical Force, and this unknown device slowly floated up and into his hands. He then left the metal tower and returned to the outside world.

Mechanical Force seeped into the unknown device, and Han Xiao could feel the internal structure. He realized that he could not understand this technology, and many parts had been damaged and destroyed after being buried for a long time.

Han Xiao looked at the item introduction.

[Psionic Wave Transmitter—Prototype (Damaged)]: Function unknown.

"Psionic Wave?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and started to think.

He had a feeling that this concept of 'psionic waves' was not the same as the 'psionic waves' and 'psionic impact' of the explored universe. He did not know what was going on at the moment, but he could roughly guess how the Arthur Civilization went extinct. Research involving psionic energy had always been extremely dangerous, and many civilizations had been doomed because of it.

After pondering for a few seconds, Han Xiao used [Bold Explorer] on this thing. The last time he used it on Beyonder's Vestige, the notification was that it was ineffective on the target and did not successfully cast it, so it did not enter a seven-day cooldown period.

Buzz!

Han Xiao's vision suddenly changed, and he arrived at a research institute.

The psionic wave transmitter was suspended in midair, covered by a transparent container. There were tubes connected to it, and below it was a huge pile of equipment. Countless researchers in uniform were busy adjusting the parameters.

A senior officer who looked like the person in charge waved his hand and said something. The other researchers pushed the lever and activated the switch. Energy flowed into the psionic wave transmitter.

Not long after, the space on both sides of this hourglass-shaped device began to vibrate. The air distorted like invisible ripples, but it was restrained within a small area.

All the researchers present were overjoyed.

However, the next moment, something happened!

The ripples on both sides of the device suddenly broke through the constraints, and a light blue ring-shaped shockwave spread out, passing through the inner wall of the container and quickly sweeping across the entire room. All the devices exploded, and the energy devices were instantly paralyzed. The entire room immediately turned black.

The researchers that were swept by the shockwave were all killed in the blink of an eye, turning into ashes without a sound, leaving only empty clothes on the ground.

At this moment, Han Xiao's vision suddenly zoomed out and arrived at the outer space of the planet that overlooked the entire planet. It turned into a macro perspective, and he saw a blue shockwave explode on the surface of Planet Cree, sweeping across the entire planet. The brightly lit cities instantly darkened, and countless unaware citizens turned into dust.

No one on the entire planet survived!

However, this was not the end. Han Xiao could clearly see that this light blue shockwave that destroyed all electrons, energy equipment, and life forms did not weaken. It spread far into the universe with Planet Cree as the center, quickly disappearing from his sight.

After seeing this, Han Xiao's vision returned to normal, and the effect of the skill ended.

"As expected, it's because of this thing. I thought that Tyrsius was lying to me, but his civilization really isn't that advanced. They can even destroy themselves by researching psionic energy, but it doesn't seem right to say that their technology isn't good. The psionic wave transmitter they created is probably some kind of advanced technology…"

Han Xiao fiddled with the device in his hands in shock.

After watching the video, he had a rough idea of how this device worked.

The Primordial Psionic Energy itself could assimilate, devour, absorb, and transform various forms of energy. Once it exploded, it would expand endlessly, swallowing everything.

However, the psionic wave transmitter created by the Arthur Civilization could destroy certain forms of energy without devouring any matter. It could also absorb some of the energy to maintain its own expansion. A normal psionic energy explosion was a solid energy cluster, but this 'psionic wave' was just a ripple.

However, there were also some things that Han Xiao did not understand. He did not understand why the other materials were not damaged, but the life forms were destroyed. In short, there were still many unknowns about this technology.

"It seems to have a lot of research value. Maybe it can become an important combat technology for me."

Han Xiao was in a good mood. He did not have any plans for this trip, but he did not expect to gain something unexpected.

He had a feeling that this psionic wave technology was more powerful than he had expected.

The [Secret of Extinction] on the interface also showed that it was completed. The normal way was to look for clues everywhere, but he had the [Bold Explorer] and completed the mission.

The experience reward did not matter. One Awakening Point was better than nothing. However, it was very easy and did not take much effort. The biggest reward was this special psionic wave technology.

Just as Han Xiao was feeling happy, he suddenly heard a familiar voice beside him.

"Discovered a stranger approaching the mission target. Permission to use a stun gun!"

Han Xiao turned around and saw that the broken transport robot had returned to the foot of the mountain. It raised its mechanical arm toward him, and two firearms shot out from its wrist. Without saying a word, it pulled the trigger at Han Xiao.

Ka ka ka…

Han Xiao had long known that these two rusty firearms were useless, and they could not shoot anything at all. However, the transport robot did not seem to have noticed it, and it continued to pull the trigger in vain.

Han Xiao raised his brows, took a step to the left, and the muzzles of the transport robot followed him. He took another step to the right, and the muzzles turned around again, facing him.

Looking at the robot pulling the trigger, Han Xiao felt that it was a little cute.

"Forget it, I won't dismantle you."

Seeing that it was not a threat at all, Han Xiao ignored it. He summoned more exploration-type mechanical soldiers and waved for them to leave, searching for other planets in this universe to see if there were any survivors of the Arthur Civilization.

He wanted to find the history of this civilization as well as the records of Tyrsius' deeds. After all, there were still many things that he had yet to understand. However, he could just let the mechanical soldiers do this for him. After all, he was a Mechanic and he did not have to do such troublesome things himself.

After doing all this, Han Xiao looked back at the transport robot. Seeing that it was still pulling the trigger, he could not help but smile.

"Speaking of which, I don't know what kind of luck this little guy has to be able to survive the psionic waves. He might be the only survivor of the entire Arthur Civilization. Since I promised Tyrsius to take care of his hometown, I can't ignore you…"

Han Xiao thought for a while and suddenly released a stream of Mechanical Force, which landed on the transport robot. The robot froze on the spot, and its appearance and structure changed rapidly. It gradually turned into the shape of a human, and the rust fell off.

At the same time, wave after wave of mechanical particles poured out from Han Xiao's hands and landed on the other party's body. The material of the mechanical suit was quickly strengthened.

Not long after, the transformation stopped. The appearance of this transport robot had changed drastically. It was covered in silver armor and had a streamlined shape. Its body was slender and long, and energy circuits that emitted a faint fluorescent light could be seen on its body. It was as if it had gone from a chibi to a realistic concept art.

"That's enough."

Han Xiao nodded and retracted his Mechanical Force.

He gave life to this transport robot, turning it into a mechanical life form. At the same time, he had greatly improved the other party's body and added many new functions. He had also stored some knowledge of the Star System Civilization's technology tree into the other party's database.

However, he did not rewrite the core logic of the other party. He only perfected the other party's intelligence on the original basis and did not leave his mark on the other party.

With his current abilities, the first-generation Mechanical Life that he had personally modified had extremely high-performance bonuses.

Han Xiao did not plan to take this robot with him because he owed Tyrsius a favor. As for whether this robot would be able to grow a new flower of civilization on the ruins of Planet Cree after receiving his gift, that was not his concern.

Looking up at the soaring metal tower, Han Xiao had mixed feelings. After knowing the situation, this metal tower seemed to have a special meaning.

In his eyes, this metal tower that looked like a building that had become the tombstone of a civilization.

"The advancement of technology is also a disaster…"

Han Xiao sighed. He then glanced at the transport robot before changing into King and disappearing with the psionic wave transmitter.

The transport robot did not seem to have noticed anything. It stood there in a daze for a long time before finally coming back to its senses. It looked down at its body, which had changed drastically, and seemed very confused.

The electric current on the motherboard seemed to have created sparks in its mind. It murmured to himself,

"What… am I?"

Chapter 1387: Race Evolution!

A few days later, in the Black Star Army territory.

Five figures were floating above a desolate planet. Four of them were staring at a black-robed figure.

"Black Star, are you kidding me? You want us to help you break through to a higher level?"

Kasuyi was surprised.

"Do I look like I'm joking?"

Han Xiao asked in return.

After returning from the Arthur Civilization, he immediately contacted four peak Beyond Grade As and invited them to help him with his cultivation. Wuornos had agreed long ago to represent Espers. The other three classes were Kasuyi, the old dragon, and Sierron, who did not have a deep relationship with them.

The Pugilist class was relatively weak at the high end, and there were not many strong people. Putting aside the Revivors, Sierron was already one of the rare cards. Although Han Xiao preferred Karlot at his peak, he had yet to grow fully, there was no need to wait for him. He just needed to find Sierron to make up for the loss.

In the past, during the Hila Rescue War, he and Sierron had some conflicts, but after experiencing all kinds of storms together with the association, their relationship had returned to normal. This guy was not a direct descendant of the Universal Civilizations and had always been on the side of the association. Now that he was also a vice president, he could be trusted.

"You can always do unexpected things."

The three of them shook their heads helplessly.

When they received Han Xiao's invitation a few days ago, they were all equally shocked. They did not expect Black Star to be able to reach a higher level without saying anything, opening up the path of individual strength.

At first, they thought that Black Star was joking with them, but after confirming it, again and again, they realized that Black Star was serious.

Because they had a good relationship with each other, although the three of them were surprised, they agreed to the invitation and prepared to help. What surprised them was Black Star's method of advancement.

"Speaking of which, what can we help you with? Shouldn't this sort of thing be done alone?" Milizaus was confused.

In his mind, breaking through to a higher level and ascending to the next level was something that one could only do by themselves. Since when did one need help?

"Of course, I have my reasons." Han Xiao did not explain the reason, and it was difficult for him to explain.

Wuornos pondered.

"The five of us have different Super systems. Could it be that your idea is to combine the five elements…"

Han Xiao interrupted him and waved his hands.

"Why are you asking so many questions now? Since you're already here, just follow the plan and wait for the final result."

Hearing this, Wuornos stopped talking. However, he kept thinking about it in his mind and was secretly surprised by Han Xiao's performance.

He was very puzzled. The method to reach a higher level should be a mystery to everyone, and Black Star did not look like he had tried it many times. However, why did this guy look so confident? Why did he have such a thought? He borrowed the Church's National Treasure and asked a few people for help…

Furthermore, attempting a promotion should be risky. Why was Black Star using such a bold method? Was he not afraid? Did he not sense the danger of this Promotion?

Various thoughts flashed through Wuornos' mind. In the end, he shook his head and did not intend to remind Han Xiao.

In any case, this was Black Star's Promotion. He looked very confident, so there was no need for Han Xiao to kindly remind him. He would just wait and see. Even if Black Star failed, the experience would still be able to broaden his horizons.

Thinking about this, Wuornos pressed his palm against his chest and phased through it. He took out a ball of soft white light and threw it at Han Xiao.

"This is what you want. I'll lend it to you."

Han Xiao reached out to take it. He looked down at this Arcane Church weapon. It was different from what he had expected. It was just a ball of light.

Its main user was beside him, so it was not convenient for him to study it closely. Han Xiao pressed the Arcane Church device on his chest, and the white light quickly fused into his body. A special energy immediately surged out and covered his entire body. He felt that his cells in his critical state immediately became much calmer.

Han Xiao glanced at the interface. The first Promotion requirement had turned golden, and it was now labeled as "Activation Triggered".

"Then I shall begin."

Han Xiao nodded at the others and floated a distance away before landing on the surface of the planet.

Watching his figure shrink into a black dot, Sierron turned to look at the people around him and asked,

"Do you think he will succeed?"

"If it was that easy, I would have entered a higher level long ago."

Wuornos shook his head and said calmly.

Buzz!

At this time, in everyone's perception, space suddenly shook, and a shocking energy wave burst out from the planet!

In just an instant, the entire planet exploded into a huge hole, and the molten fluids in the core gushed out and scattered across the galaxy. Then, the planet suddenly exploded!

Bang!

Amidst the debris and light, Han Xiao's voice did not move at all. It was continuously emitting shocking energy waves, and his aura was rising rapidly.

"It's starting!"

The eyes of the four of them focused, and they immediately followed the plan. They released their energy. It passed through the fragments of the planet and entered Han Xiao's body.

Han Xiao was bathed in the light, and the cells in his body started to go berserk. He felt like his body was going to separate and reform at any time.

However, the Church's National Treasure floating in his chest released fluctuations at a fixed frequency, engulfing his entire body and allowing his body to maintain its original structure.

Strangely, though the different energies sent out from his four helpers should have been ejected, at this moment, they were not repelled. Instead, they seemed to have been absorbed and quickly merged into his cells.

At the same time, the Beyonder's Vestige that had been dormant for many days suddenly glowed brightly and started burning fiercely, releasing all the energy. It immediately caused the speed of advancement to spike and soar rapidly.

The feeling of pain and exhilaration assaulted Han Xiao's mind time and time again. He struggled to control his vision and glanced at the interface, only to see that the notifications were flooding in.

[Level 360 Promotion has been activated!]

[You have reached the prerequisite for Promotion: 3 / 3]

[You have activated the Apotheosis Promotion!]

[The new Grade can be unlocked!]

[Due to the Apotheosis Promotion, +160 Basic END Bonus increased to +480! Current 1 END = 1170 Health = 1180 Stamina]

Your [God's Trait Transformation·Machinery] has reached the maximum level. You have been awarded an additional Life Level Promotion!]

[Detecting your race: Black Star Race (Exclusive race, irreplaceable)]

[Detected that your evolutionary route (Void) has reached the limit, there is no higher Life Level to promote to]

[Detected that you are undergoing Apotheosis, conventional optimization is cancelled —— would you like to proceed with evolving your Exclusive Race?]

[….. Evolution confirmed, [Black Star Race] has now evolved to become [Black Star God Race], your life level has been promoted, your genes strengthened. You have obtained additional Attributes: +2140 STR, +1705 DEX, +2600 END, +3440 INT, +3052 MYS, +1024 CHA and +26200 Energy. The bonuses provided by your Energy Attribute Realm has been strengthened]

[Your Black Star God Race exclusive talent [Mechanical Genius] has been enhanced]

[Mechanical Genius: The bonus Machinery Affinity has been increased from x1.55 to x1.65, Machinery Creation Performance increased from 70% to 80%, all Mechanic related skill levels increased from +3 to +4]

[Your God's Trait Transformation·Void is at the maximum, you have received a bonus Life Level Promotion!]

[Your race has been detected: [Black Star God Race] (Exclusive race, irreplaceable)]

[Detected that your evolutionary route (Void) has reached the limit, there is no higher Life Level to promote to]

[Detected that you are undergoing Apotheosis, conventional optimization is cancelled —— would you like to proceed with evolving your Exclusive Race?]

[….. Evolution confirmed, your [Black Star God Race] has now evolved to become [Black Star God Race·Royal Bloodline]. Your Life Level has been promoted and genes strengthened. You have obtained the additional Attributes: +2780 STR, +2410 DEX, +2600 END, +3440 INT, +3052 MYS, +1024 CHA and +26200 Energy. The bonuses provided by your Energy Attribute Realm has been strengthened]

[Your Black Star God Race exclusive talent [Mechanical Genius] has been enhanced]

[Mechanical Genius: The bonus Machinery Affinity has been increased from x1.65 to x1.75, Machinery Creation Performance increased from 80% to 90%, all Mechanic related skill levels increased from +4 to +5]

Originally, there was no chance for a Race Evolution at level 360, but the two God's Trait Transformation metamorphoses brought about two additional Life level promotion opportunities.

Boom!

The surging energy was so dense that it almost solidified. With Han Xiao as the center, it gushed out in all directions, spreading far and wide. It had already reached the level of a cosmic energy surge, and almost all the Black Star Army's outposts in this area sounded an alarm.

Scorching energy flowed through his body, and all the cells in his body rapidly advanced toward a higher level of life. It was as if his cells had developed an independent consciousness, but it did not cause great changes under the support of the Church's National Treasure.

An endless stream of energy gushed over from all directions, and Han Xiao almost turned into the core of a nebula. His entire body was filled with heatwaves, and he felt like he was swelling up like a balloon.

He tried his best to maintain his thoughts and stared at the notification on the interface.

The improvement he got this time was extremely powerful. If he did not have the special Race Evolution brought about by the Apotheosis, the simple genetic optimization he got during an Advancement would not have brought about such a high amount of attribute increase.

However, the notifications of his two Race Evolutions had yet to end.

[Your exclusive race has been upgraded to [Black Star God Race]. You have received a new talent: Mechanical Divine Body!]

[Mechanical Divine Body: +1500% Machinery Affinity, your Mechanical Force Attribute has been enhanced. Your skills [Emperor's Gift] has been upgraded to [Ode of the Gods], [Apostle Life Creation] has been upgraded to [God's Emissary Creation], [Tinder Awakening] has been upgraded to [Allspark], and [Dimension Factory] has been upgraded to [Godly Stronghold].

(TL Note: Appreciated that the author thought of putting the Allspark in a mechanic novel. 10/10)

[Your exclusive race has been upgraded to [Black Star God Race·Royal Bloodline]. You have received a new talent: Void Divine Body!]

[Void Divine Body: +1500 to Basic Attributes, you have been awarded 30 Awakening Points. All Void-related Racial Talents will be buffed, and you can open a second Void Dimension within your body to integrate with the original Void Dimension]

Han Xiao looked at the introduction of these two talents with a hard-to suppress glee in his eyes.

The four Mechanic abilities had undergone a special evolution. Among them, [Ode of the Gods] and [God's Emissary Creation] were enhanced based on basic values. The exact effects did not change, only the name of his Apostle Weapons were renamed as Mechanical Oracles.

As for [Allspark] and [Godly Stronghold], they had some functional changes.

[Tinder Awakening] was originally an ability used to create mechanical lives, and it needed to be actively cast. However, after evolution, it now possessed a passive effect. So long as machinery was connected by Mechanical Force, it could temporarily become a mechanical life form and receive various enhancements attributed to mechanical life forms. The effect would disappear if the Mechanical Force was cut off, but prolonged usage could solidify its status permanently, changing it to become a mechanical life-form forever. This way, the efficiency and scale of creating mechanical life forms would be raised to a new level, and the consumption would also be much lower.

In addition, the function of [Godly Stronghold] was to open a secondary dimension in his body as a Dimension Factory. He did not need to summon the secondary dimension portal any longer. This was akin to having the late game skills of a Mechanical Pugilist, which removed all its previous skills' side effects. Now, even if the environment outside was locked onto by the Space Stabilization Anchor, Han Xiao would still be able to launch a surprise attack.

[Void Divine Body] also had similar effects. It could open up a new Void Dimension within one's body and even swallow parts of the original Void Dimension to improve one's own Void Dimension.

The mechanisms revealed by these two talents seemed to indicate the formation of a universe within his body!

"Is this the difference between levels?"

Han Xiao was shocked.

Even now, the evolution had yet to end, and notifications were still being sent out continuously. Intense waves of pain assaulted his mind.

The power released by the Beyonder's Vestige was cleansing the cells over and over again, causing the cells to change time and time again. It gradually approached the special 'flawless' particle form, and the changes in his body became more and more intense, sometimes intense and sometimes mild.

At the same time, the four 'pretty boys' who were continuously supplying energy finally realized that something was wrong.

From Han Xiao's body, there was an aura that made them tremble from the bottom of their souls. It was as if they had met with an existence of a higher level on the food chain.

"Am I seeing things? Is this the suppression pressure caused by a difference in life levels?!"

Kasuyi's eyes widened in shock.

"It can't be wrong, this is the feeling…"

Milizaus' dragon beard fluttered, and his huge dragon eyes flashed with disbelief. He secretly swallowed a dragon breath that was about to come out.

Wuornos, who was originally quite calm, could no longer remain unruffled. He stared at Han Xiao's figure in shock.

Holy sh*t, could it be that this guy was so lucky, able to succeed in one go?!

Chapter 1388: Coexisting with the Heaven and Earth, All Things Are One with Me

No matter how shocked the four of them were, Han Xiao's evolution continued to advance.

The surging golden Mechanical Force formed a huge energy whirlpool, spinning and expanding. Han Xiao's figure was at the center, and he was already drowned by the endless light. As for this unlucky planet, it had been completely destroyed without a single trace left.

Boiling hot energy flowed through his body, and it was as if his cells and soul were burning intensely. He felt as if he had turned into a piece of steel, enduring the refinement time and time again.

Han Xiao endured the pain of the metamorphosis and stared at the notifications on the interface with his golden eyes.

[You have met the prerequisite: Activate the Apotheosis Promotion]

[Race Apotheosis activated!]

[Your life force has already reached the peak. You have opened a new world above the peak. The domain of True Gods is unfolding before you…]

[Your Racial Talent [Black Star God Race - Royal Bloodline] has received two exclusive Racial Talent slots.]

[Please select your preference for the exclusive Racial Talent]

Many options popped up on the interface—Attack, Resistance, Machinery, Attribute Amplification, and so on. They were all options that could be chosen by the two new exclusive Racial Talents.

When Han Xiao advanced to the Beyond Grade A realm, he had created an exclusive racial talent, [Mechanical Genius]. At this time, the Apotheosis of the race had given him two chances to create an exclusive talent, which was also a genetic talent that could be awakened in his descendants.

He thought about it and chose the ability strength increase and attribute enhancement. These two enhancements were more comprehensive.

As his new talents were not as enhanced as [Mechanical Genius], the effect would not be too strong.

After a few random draws, Han Xiao finally determined the effects of the two new exclusive racial talents.

[Divine Gene] : +10% Ability Power, +2% every Promotion

Current cumulative bonus: 46%

[Natural Elite] : +10% All Attributes. From Level 1-100: 4 Free Attribute Points every level up. From Level 100-200: 8 Free Attribute Points every level up. From Level 200-300: 12 Free Attribute Points every level up. Above Level 300: 16 Free Attribute Points every level up.

Current cumulative Bonus: 3360 Free Attribute Points.

"These two new talents are not bad. They both have growth potential."

Han Xiao was excited.

When he reached the later stages of his growth, he could receive all the accumulated bonuses at once. Therefore, these two new talents would be able to increase his strength.

Although his current attributes were almost all in the tens of thousands, 3,000 to 4,000 Free Attribute Points were still not a small number. Most importantly, he could freely allocate them, and the ability power was an important bonus that any class required. The increase was quite considerable.

[Mechanical Genius], [Divine Gene], and [Natural Elite] were the inherited talents of his race. Individuals with these three talents would undoubtedly have a higher growth rate. They would all be extremely talented Super seeds and could suppress Supers of the same grade.

"If only I could make a bunch of alternate accounts…"

A thought flashed through Han Xiao's mind.

I still don't have a descendant race, I feel like I can start thinking about reproducing.

While he was thinking, a follow-up notification popped up on the interface.

Two new exclusive Racial Talents have been confirmed.

Life form evolution, molecular structure improved, organ structure strengthened, metabolism changed…

According to the preference of [Black Star God Race - Royal Bloodline], you have received bonus attributes.

+795 STR, +680 DEX, +1030 END, +1146 INT, +1050 MYS, +742 CHA, +11200 Energy.

Energy level attribute bonuses changed

[Race Apotheosis] completed. Your grade has increased to X.

Grade S Bonuses disappeared.

You have received Grade X Bonuses.

Grade X Bonuses: +240 END, +75% All Resistances,+50% Highest Attribute,+30% Other Attributes,+1,500 Free Attribute Points,+60 Awakening Points.

Please select 2 from the 7 options below as Grade Talents.

Physical Resistance

Psychological Resistance

Power Bonus

Health

Explosive Power

Energy

Status Enhancement

"There really are new Grade talents!" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

This was an important factor in dividing the strength between two grades. One could choose two options when advancing to Beyond Grade A, and it was the same now. However, the effect would be stronger, and it could even be stacked with one's grade talents.

The power bonus was a must. As for the other option, Han Xiao preferred to increase his health. It seemed like he was the only one who had reached this level, so while the tankiness seemed to be enough, it was actually the basic bonus brought about by this Promotion. This END bonus could be gained just by completing Apotheosis Promotion, his current health was probably only at the intermediate level at this grade.

He could not guarantee that there would not be anyone else who would rise in the future. Furthermore, there might already be someone at grade X in the universe. At the very least, there would not be any mistake if he continued to develop the strength of dealing damage and tanking.

You have received Grade Talent [Godly Strength]!

You have received Grade Talent [Divine Cosmos Body]!

[Godly Strength]: You possess the strength of Gods. All your abilities will receive a huge enhancement. The bonus effect depends on the character's total Level.

Below Level 300: +8% every 10 Levels.

Above Level 300: +12% every 10 Levels.

Current Ability Strength Increase: 312% (This increase can be stacked with [Superhuman] and [Supreme Power] bonuses)

[Divine Cosmos Body]: Your body is extremely strong and contains unbelievable life force. Your life span will continue till the end of the universe. +1 END Bonus every 1 level.

Current Effect: +360 END Bonus (This increase can be stacked with [Eternal Body] bonuses)

"Such great bonuses!"

Before Han Xiao could get excited, even more violent energy burst out from his body, and all his cells began a new round of transformation. Han Xiao felt that every cell was becoming more and more agitated, as though they were all going to escape from his body.

However, as the Church's National Treasure shook, the struggle of the cells was suppressed, but it also brought him more pain.

However, even though he had completed the Race Apotheosis, the Promotion was not over yet. There was still the last transformation left.

Your Class Advancement Mission has been completed.

You have received a new class—[Legendary Mechanic]!

[Beyonder Mechanic] Lv.1 —+700 Energy, +8 STR, +8 DEX, +22 END, +30 INT. You have received 25 Free Attribute Points and 1 Awakening Point.

You have received talent [Transcendent Artifact]!

You have received the talent [Energy Base—God of All Machines]!

You have received talent [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality]!

You have acquired the ability [Mechanical Deity - Supreme Heavenly Venerate]!

You have learned [Virtual Creation (Pseudo)]!

You have acquired the ability [Life Transformation—Virtual]!

You have acquired the ability [Life Transformation - Myriad Machine]!

All your Virtual Technology skills or talents have been enhanced by 80%.

Han Xiao's breathing stopped.

The new class was also unfamiliar to him, and [Legendary Mechanic] did not have the upper limit of the class. This proved that this was the last stage of the Mechanic class. He could continue to level up, but there was no Class Advancement after that.

He looked at the various new abilities obtained from this Class Advancement and could not help but narrow his eyes. The effects of the skills were as flashy as the name, but the bonuses were astonishing.

Han Xiao wanted to analyze his new abilities in detail, but the pain of evolution came one after another, almost freezing his thoughts. It was not a good time to study them.

Seeing that the notifications on the interface had finally stopped, Han Xiao knew that he had obtained all the bonuses from this Promotion. He quickly calmed down and silently felt his evolution. The sense of time quickly became blurry.

After a full two days, the huge energy whirlpool finally seemed to have expanded to its limit. It slowly shrank back toward the center and entered Han Xiao's body.

On the other hand, Wuornos and the other three had been standing guard at the edge, watching Han Xiao's advancement from start to finish. They did not dare blink at all, afraid that they would miss a second.

Because this was the territory of the Black Star Army, Han Xiao had already informed them that no one was allowed to disturb him. Thus, even though this place had become the source of the cosmic-level energy surge, triggering the radar alarms of many organizations, no one had come over to watch.

After a while, the energy whirlpool returned to Han Xiao's body, and the dazzling light faded, revealing Han Xiao's current appearance.

He was floating in the air with his eyes closed as if he was still in a meditative state and had yet to wake up. There was a special aura around him, and his skin was glowing. A few light golden particles were slowly flowing around his body.

Seeing this, Wuornos and the others hesitated. They did not know what was going on with Han Xiao and did not approach him immediately.

This time, Han Xiao finally opened his eyes. The light on his body stopped, and he floated toward the three of them with a smile.

"My Promotion went very smoothly. Thank you, everyone."

Hearing this, the four of them were shocked.

Although they had already guessed it in their hearts in the past two days, they still could not help but feel a strong sense of disbelief when Han Xiao admitted it personally.

"You really succeeded? You opened up a higher level of individual strength ‽" Milizaus cried out.

"That should be the case."

Han Xiao nodded and released some pressure.

The four people present were stunned. They instantly felt a vast pressure and could not help but feel their hearts palpitate.

However, it only lasted for an instant before Han Xiao retracted the pressure from the difference in the hierarchy of life, allowing them to heave a sigh of relief.

After the unbelievable shock, they were filled with excitement and respect.

They were all peak Beyond Grade As, including Wuornos and Kasuyi, who thought that they were half a step away from reaching a higher level. Now that they could see the entire process of Han Xiao's advancement and see the successful case of him reaching a higher level, would this method work on them too?

Did Black Star specifically give them this benefit ‽

"I didn't expect you to succeed in one go… Congratulations."

Wuornos was extremely envious.

He had tried so many times, but in the end, he stopped because he was worried about the risk. However, Black Star had gone straight in and succeeded. Indeed, men and their constitutions could not be compared…

However, although Wuornos felt bitter, he was more excited and overjoyed. He felt that his insight was really good. He had indeed not misjudged Black Star. In fact, this guy was even more amazing than he had expected. He had rushed up to a higher level and pointed him in the right direction!

With Black Star scouting ahead, he would be able to replicate the success today.

The Church's National Treasure was his, and the Arcane Church did not lack direct members of five classes. The other two Universal Civilizations would more or less provide help to contend with Black Star. Therefore, among the Beyond Grade As, he was the only one who could easily replicate the method Black Star used today. He undoubtedly profited the most!

Although Black Star did not fail, which was out of his expectations and caused his selfish thought to fail, he still did not come for nothing!

Thinking about this, Wuornos felt extremely comfortable. He decided to prepare for his advancement when he returned.

However, at this moment, he suddenly remembered that the Church's National Treasure was still in Han Xiao's hands. He did not know how far Black Star's strength had progressed. If he had any evil intentions…

Wuornos' heart tightened, and he said slowly, "Black Star, can I have it back?"

"Oh, take it."

Han Xiao glanced at him and saw that he was nervous. He shook his head and smiled. He took out the Church's National Treasure and threw it back to Wuornos. He did not intend to take it for himself.

Since they did not cause any trouble and came to help him, he would not kick them to the curb after they outlived their usefulness. There was no need to offend them because of this. At most, he would just borrow it again. Furthermore, there was more than one 'Stabilizer'. After his Promotion, Han Xiao had some new ideas.

Wuornos took the Church's National Treasure and stuffed it back into his body. He secretly heaved a sigh of relief, but then he was overjoyed.

Kasuyi looked at the Church's National Treasure with a burning gaze before looking back at Han Xiao.

"Your Promotion is a good thing for the entire Beyond Grade A group. I wonder if you plan to publicize this method?"

"Keep it a secret for now. Just keep this matter to yourselves. Don't tell anyone about it for the time being to avoid disturbances. To be honest, this Promotion is quite dangerous. If it fails, you might not be able to revive with the Sanctum."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

He did not care much about this matter. The four of them only saw the surface. Even if they imitated his method, they would not be able to trigger the Apotheosis Promotion. This was because they lacked an important factor, Beyonder's Vestige.

Now that he had successfully advanced and was no longer in a critical state, he had also lost the ability to sense the Beyonder's Vestige. As long as he did not specifically remind them, others might not be able to activate this perception. Furthermore, without a detailed interface notification, others might not know what this perception meant.

The most important thing was that he had already used up the last Beyonder's Vestige that was left in the explored universe. Even if someone found out about the use of the Beyonder's Vestige, they would have to go to the unexplored area to search for it. Who knew how long it would take?

Hearing this, apart from Wuornos, Kasuyi and the others were shocked and suppressed the impulse in their hearts.

Milizaus suddenly thought of something and asked, "By the way, the new grade has yet to be defined in the Galactic Society. Why don't you give it a name?"

Sierron agreed. "Indeed, the title of Beyond Grade A is to commemorate the exploration era. Now that a new level has appeared, a new name is also needed. It will be recorded in history. You are the founder, and only you have the right to name it."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and did not reject. He immediately thought of the name of his class and raised his brows.

"How about… we call it the Transcendent Grade?"

"Sounds good."

The few of them naturally did not have any objections to a name and nodded.

"Then it's settled. The grade above Beyond Grade A will be called the Transcendent Grade."

Han Xiao smiled and nodded.

This time, Kasuyi could not hold back his curiosity and sized Han Xiao up.

"Black Star, what is the strength of the new level? How strong is it?"

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled.

"I'm very, very strong…"

As he spoke, he looked at his attributes panel, and a strange look flashed in his eyes.

Level: 360

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Black Star God Race - Royal Bloodline

Attributes: 33,810 STR, 29,423 DEX, 44,310 END, 81,744 INT, 26,854 MYS, 12,560 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 5,105

Awakening Points: 101

Health: 122,694,490

Stamina: 98,274,600

Energy: 481,200

Energy Lv.29 Bonus: +12,480 STR, +13,640 DEX, +17,200 END, +22,845 INT, +13,590 MYS, +11,427,000 Stamina Limit, +14,670% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 148,800 Ona

Grade: X

Grade X Bonuses: +240 END, +75% All Resistances, +50% Highest Attribute, +30% Other Attributes, +1,500 Free Attribute Points, +60 Awakening Points.

"You have cleared the fog in front of you. A brand new path extends under your feet. From now on, heaven and earth will exist side by side with you. All things are one with you… You are the universe!"

Chapter 1389: The Arcane Church: It Does Not Feel Like a Loss, We Might Have Even Profited

Retracting his gaze from the attribute interface, Han Xiao turned around and saw Kasuyi looking like he wanted to test out his Transcendent strength personally. He smiled and waved.

"There's no need for a spar. I've just stepped into the Transcendent Grade, so I'm not familiar with my strength yet. If I don't control it well, I'm afraid I won't be able to hold back and kill you. If that happens, I'll have to revive you and give myself more trouble."

Is this even human language?

Kasuyi tilted his head.

Seeing that Han Xiao had no intention of showing it, Kasuyi did not insist and could only give up on this thought for the time being. After all, there was still a long way to go, he would see it sooner or later.

Glancing at the four of them, Han Xiao smiled and said,

"Everyone, I still need to familiarize myself with my strength, so I'll take my leave first… By the way, Wuornos, just let me know when you're ready to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

With that said, he nodded and left. He disappeared from everyone's sight in a flash.

The remaining four looked at each other. The atmosphere was a little strange.

Black Star had shown them the way to become a Transcendent. This kind of secret was most valuable only if they held it alone. None of the four of them were willing to leak it out. If it was in the past, they might even have thought of killing each other. However, the times had changed. Black Star was above them, and the association had united the Beyond Grade As. There were still enemies outside, so they could only endure others sharing this secret.

"Don't forget Black Star's instructions. It's enough for us to know his method of advancement. Don't tell anyone else without his approval," Sierron said with a deep voice.

"Heh, do I look like someone who would spout nonsense?" Milizaus snorted.

"Black Star is the president, and we're also members of the association. Of course, we won't say anything, but the direct descendants of the civilization might ." Kasuyi narrowed his eyes and stared at Wuornos.

Hearing this, Milizaus and Sierron also turned to look at Wuornos with subtle expressions.

None of them had the motive to leak the secret, but Wuornos was a direct member of the church. If the upper echelons of the civilization asked him for this method, would he keep it a secret?

As a member of the association, the three of them considered it from the perspective of the faction. If the association was the only one who knew how to advance to the Beyond Grade, it would be a new bargaining chip to attract Supers, and they would be able to suppress the three Universal Civilizations in terms of individual strength.

Wuornos' face was calm, and he did not give in verbally. He said casually, "I will also try to advance. Even if I don't say it, they will know when the time comes."

"Tsk." Sierron snorted but did not retort.

Seeing that the three of them had nothing else to say, Wuornos did not stay any longer. He turned around and left in a hurry.

He only wanted to return to the Arcane Church as soon as possible, unable to wait to study Black Star's advancement method.

Kasuyi and the other two watched him leave without moving.

"The Church's National Treasure is in this guy's hands. With Black Star's successful case, the Arcane Church probably won't lend it to outsiders anymore…" Milizaus smacked his lips.

"Hmm, in that case, only Wuornos and the direct members of the church will be able to replicate the method that Black Star used. We can forget about it." Sierron nodded.

"Black Star is a Mechanic and has reached a higher level. Maybe he can find a replacement. We'll know when we ask."

Kasuyi's expression was calm.

Considering that the Arcane Church National Weapon was an indispensable tool for Black Star's advancement method, the few of them had the thought of snatching it. However, after thinking about it, they decided not to. Wuornos was not easy to deal with, and the three of them represented the association. They were not willing to create trouble for Black Star.

Now that Black Star had opened a new level, his position as the association's leader was even more stable. Originally, they were all on the same level, so even if they listened to his orders temporarily, they would not treat themselves as Black Star's subordinates.

However, as Black Star entered a new realm, their relationship subtly changed. It was just that the three of them had yet to feel the subtle change in their subconscious.

At this time, Milizaus suddenly thought of something and asked, "By the way, although the method of advancement has to be kept a secret, there's no need to hide the fact that Black Star has become a Transcendent, right?"

Kasuyi shook his head and said,

"Since Black Star did not give any special instructions, then there's no need to. Furthermore, there's no need to hide such a good thing. However, it's only limited to the upper echelons of the association. As for the three Universal Civilizations, they will most likely know about the situation through Wuornos, but they won't spread it around."

...

On the other side, the Arcane Church.

"What did you say? Black Star actually succeeded?!"

The Pope's eyes widened in shock.

Wuornos, who had come to report, nodded calmly and slowly continued.

"That's right. Black Star has already stepped into a higher level of individual strength. He named it the Transcendent Grade. I witnessed it with my own eyes."

"Didn't you say that stepping into the new tier is very difficult? You said that lending out the Void Spirit Kingdom's weapon would be no big deal, because how many times Black Star would fail?"

The Pope stared at Wuornos, both shocked and furious.

"Oh, I miscalculated," Wuornos said with an expressionless face.

"That's it?! Do you think you can get away with it with just this sentence?!"

The Pope glared at him, getting even more furious.

If not for the fact that you kept emphasizing that this deal would definitely be profitable, why would we lend the Void Spirit National Treasure to help Black Star advance?

Are you hooking up with Black Star and speaking for him to trick me?!

I really don't believe you!

"Then what do you want?" Wuornos glanced at him.

The Pope closed his eyes and took a deep breath to calm himself down. Only then did he speak.

"No matter what, this has already happened. Think of a way to salvage the situation."

Because of a wrong decision, he had helped Black Star reach a higher level of individual strength. He was filled with regret. If he had known, he would have rejected Black Star's request!

However, now was not the time to shift the blame. He was the one who had given the order, and he could not shirk the responsibility. The Pope quickly got rid of his anger, regret, and other emotions.

"On the bright side, at least we got the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back… provided Black Star doesn't go back on his word." The Pope shook his head.

"There's no need for him to go back on his word," Wuornos said calmly. "This Universal Treasure is no longer a threat to him."

"That's true…"

Hearing this, the Pope felt even more upset. He only felt that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was no longer that tempting.

This deal was a huge loss!

However, at this moment, Wuornos slowly said,

"However, it's not like I didn't gain anything this time. I watched the entire process of Black Star's advancement and have already grasped his method. I won't be as clueless as before. I can replicate this successful case and reach a higher level."

The Pope sat in silence for a moment before his eyes lit up.

Although the advancement of Black Star was beneficial to the war against the outside world, it would not be a good thing for the three Universal Civilizations in the long term. However, his direct descendant had now learned the method of Black Star's advancement. As long as they succeeded, he would have another Transcendent Grade Super on his side to fight Black Star, forming a new balance without having to worry about Black Star losing control!

More importantly, the ones who could use this method were the people of the Church. Even if the three Universal Civilizations were linked together right now, there were still segregated as civilizations. With this method, the Church could also suppress the other two civilizations in terms of individual strength!

The Pope was in a good mood. "How confident are you of success?"

Wuornos thought for a moment and nodded, "There's a seventy percent chance that I can reach the Transcendent Grade like Black Star."

"Okay!"

The Pope perked up.

The 70% chance was quite high! When they were chatting in the past, Wuornos had said that he was not confident at all. Now, the chance had increased countless times.

In that case, not only would helping Black Star not be a loss, but it would even be a small gain ‽

Thinking deeper, it was fortunate that Black Star needed to borrow the Void Spirit Kingdom's weapon this time. Otherwise, the direct descendants of the civilization would not have known about his secret advancement, and this advancement method would have been monopolized only by the association.

In that case, wouldn't the future be even more disadvantageous for the three Universal Civilizations?!

Thinking of this, the Pope felt much better and finally smiled.

"The Church will do its best to provide you with resources to help you reach the Transcendent Grade. If you need anything, just tell us. Don't hesitate!"

"Don't worry, I won't hold back."

Wuornos nodded.

The Pope thought for a moment and said, "Also, keep the matter of the Promotion method a secret for the time being. As for the success of Black Star's Promotion, I'll inform the leaders of the Federation of Light and the Crimson Dynasty. We have common interests in this, and we can't hide it from them. We need to talk to Black Star."

"Up to you. As long as it helps me."

Wuornos did not care about these miscellaneous matters. All he wanted to do was copy Han Xiao's advancement method. He could almost see the higher level that he had always dreamed of, waving at him.

...

A day later, in the territory of the Black Star Army, the exclusive machinery factory.

Han Xiao looked at the cloud of Mechanical Force in his palm, and his pupils constricted as though he was observing the microscopic world.

After a while, he suddenly clenched his fingers and crushed it into pieces, creating a golden shockwave.

"The last advancement of the Mechanic class. Its strength is truly unique…"

Han Xiao murmured.

Throughout the day, he was mainly testing out the new abilities brought by his Class Advancement. By now, he had more or less figured it out, and he was speechless.

[Beyonder Artifact] was a core talent. It was similar to the advanced version of [Spirit Instrument]. The success rate of developing and creating golden blueprints would increase greatly, and there was also a small chance of creating a Space Wonder.

The most important thing was that this talent unlocked an even higher grade for equipment, which was the red 'Divine Artifact' grade. However, this grade was not achieved through crafting but through strengthening the original machinery, greatly enhancing its effect. Furthermore, there was a limit to the number of Divine Artifacts, so one could enhance up to three Divine Artifacts.

However, the targets that could enjoy the bonuses could be changed. The mechanism was similar to the Apostle Weapons. If he wanted to strengthen the fourth machine into a Divine Artifact equipment, he just had to take back the bonuses of his previous Divine Artifact equipment.

[Energy Base—God of All Machines] was also a core talent, similar to Sorokin's [Spiritual Energy Foundation]. The effect of this skill was that the basic unit of energy production was no longer limited to one's cells. Machinery and virtual data could also generate energy.

If Han Xiao turned himself into a mechanical or Virtual Lifeform, or if he did any reproductive modifications to himself, there would be no difference from before, and his strength would not be affected. This meant that he could already exist without his physical body.

From this perspective, the fusion of Herberlon's body with machinery was just an incomplete version of this ability. The [Energy Base—God of All Machines] was the final ideal state.

In addition, this talent also gave him a high Machinery Affinity bonus, which was very shocking.

In addition, his new skill [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality] was not an ability brought about by Class Advancement but a talent that had reached Grade X. Just as Han Xiao had guessed, after entering a new Grade, his information form had also changed drastically, giving him the ability to revive automatically.

Be it life form or network data, as long as there were information carriers in the entire universe that recorded his deeds, as long as he was not forgotten by everyone, as long as someone still recited his name, he would not completely perish.

If he died, there would be no need for him to use the Sanctum to revive. He could automatically trigger an information state disturbance and revive in a certain region of the universe. This was close to eternal indestructibility.

Most importantly, the rebirth brought by this talent would not damage the integrity of his information. This meant that it was not like the Sanctum Revival, where every revival caused one to be weaker.

The only thing that confused Han Xiao was that the Sanctum was also an information carrier. If [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality] was usable for all situations, would he be able to survive through the later iterations?

He did not know if there were any Transcendent Grade existences in the past. If this conjecture was true, then those Transcendents should have been left behind, which should have made a greater impact on the current universe.

"If only I could test it out."

Han Xiao shook his head.

He felt that the Sanctum that was 'outside of the Three Realms was not part of the Five Elements'[1] probably did not belong to the information carrier that allowed his [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality] to take effect. The range of effect of this talent should only be limited to his current universe iteration and the secondary dimensions.

However, even so, it was still powerful enough. Just like what the attribute interface said, everything in the world was one with him. The information state was the source of his existence. As long as nothing went wrong, he could live till the end of the universe.

The three talents were all very useful, and the abilities were also extraordinary. Among them, [Mechanical Deity - Supreme Heavenly Venerate] was the advanced version of the Mechanical Deity… No, rather than saying that it was an advancement, it would be better to say that the original Mechanical Deity was just the prerequisite form of this skill.

The Mechanical Deity could change its structure on its own. Similarly, it also had the concept of a blueprint. Some Mechanical Deity with certain forms would have additional bonuses.

[Mechanical Deity - Supreme Heavenly Venerate] was one of the final forms of the Mechanical Deity. It was much more powerful than the advanced version of the Mechanical Deity that Han Xiao created. The two were worlds apart.

The skill introduction showed that the skills obtained from the three Mechanic branches were all different. [Mechanical Deity - Supreme Heavenly Venerate] belonged to the Virtual Branch, while the Armed Branch and Energy Branch's skills were respectively [Mechanical Deity - Universe Emperor] and [Mechanical Deity - Origin Divine Lord]. They corresponded to different final forms, all of which sounded extremely domineering.

Not only that, through his core talent [Energy Base—God of All Machines], he realized that when he transformed into a Mechanical Deity, he no longer needed a physical body as the core to provide Mechanical Force. He could directly turn the mechanical shell into his own!

This meant that if he truly became a Mechanical Deity, he would not even have to consume any energy. Even if he did not have the means to quickly recover his energy, he could still maintain his Mechanical Deity state indefinitely and live in this form!

In addition, [Life Transformation: Virtual] and [Life Transformation: Myriad Machine] had similar effects. These two abilities could change one's life form, and with the blessing of [Energy Base—God of All Machines], the body was no longer a shackle.

At the same time, these two skills could not only be used on oneself but also on others. As long as the judgment was successful, the target could be instantly transformed into a stream of virtual data or mechanical body, changing the form of the other party's existence. It could make an entire planet turn into a mechanical or virtual life form. This ability was infinitesimally close to the power of a God.

[Virtual Creation (Pseudo)] was even more unbelievable. According to the skill introduction, this ability was similar to the virtual transformation ability of the World Tree. It could turn the things created in the virtual world into physical objects, like a true god of creation.

However, the reason why this ability had a 'pseudo' suffix was that there were many restrictions. Firstly, it was impossible to convert items that did not exist in reality, things that he did not know, and things that went against the natural laws.

Secondly, the conversion would require an equivalent amount of resources. For example, the data of a mechanical army would have to be copied in the virtual world, and the corresponding materials would have to be prepared. However, using this skill meant that the process of manufacturing could be skipped, making it very suitable for mass production of soldiers.

Similarly, it was very useful in the manufacturing aspect. Even the Universal Treasures that he knew of could be mass-produced using this method. The success rate was almost 100%.

However, the third limitation was that the transformation was temporary. Once the time was up, it would disintegrate on its own and would not last permanently.

"This ability can be considered a Space Wonder in the eyes of ordinary people. It's called Virtual Technology, but it should be an information form ability. I need to study it more…"

Han Xiao exhaled.

Although [Virtual Creation (Pseudo)] was miraculous, because of these restrictions, it was not as powerful. But it still remained useful. Through [Godly Stronghold], it could also temporarily explode with a large number of soldiers, but it was still far from the true Space Wonder like the World Tree.

"However, this ability is quite similar to the World Tree. Will there be any connection…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he had a bold idea.

Maybe if the World Tree ate him, it would be able to make up for its deficiencies. On the other hand, if he rooted out the World Tree, he might be able to make up for the deficit of the skill…

[1] This is more of a wuxia/xianxia saying, that this object or person is an irregular and does not follow the natural laws of the world Back

Chapter 1390: Legacy Blueprints and the Showdown

Han Xiao shook his head and temporarily threw this thought out.

The location of the World Tree was still unknown, so it was best not to think too much.

He turned to look at the [Tyracles Mechanical Legacy] on his Talent interface. This ability would unlock new exclusive blueprints when he was level 360. Although he had a rich technological foundation, no Mechanic would complain about having too many golden blueprints.

Back when the [Tyracles Mechanical Legacy] was at Lv 320, it unlocked the King and the Emperor's Cape. The former was still very useful.

This time, he unlocked three golden blueprints at level 360. Han Xiao opened the blueprint introduction and looked at it.

[Blueprint - Dark Energy Gold Furnace Beast]: After the Saint Tyracles Race witnessed the greatness of the Mechanical Deity, they developed a series of special equipment specially designed for the Mechanical Deity.

[Blueprint—Emperor Skysplitter Blade]: After the Saint Tyracles Race witnessed the greatness of the Mechanical Deity, they developed a series of special equipment specially designed for the Mechanical Deity.

[Blueprint—Space Constants Modifier (Incomplete)]: The Ultimate Technology of the Saint Tyracles Race has yet to be completed.

"This…"

Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

Of the five gold blueprints brought by [Tyracles Mechanical Legacy], three of them were equipment specially made for the Mechanical Deity. He finally saw how passionate this race was toward the Mechanical Deity.

The Dark Gold Furnace Beast was an external special body. Its introduction was that it could share the power of the descent of the Mechanical Deity and had its own consciousness, serving as the mount of the Mechanical Deity. As for Emperor Skysplitter Blade, it was a large high-tech compound weapon. Its appearance was similar to a double-headed broadsword, and its blade was straight and wide. It had a lot of empty slots and could integrate different parts.

Han Xiao summoned the 3D model and briefly outlined the appearance of a Mechanical Deity. He then loaded the Emperor's Robe, Dark Gold Furnace Beast, and Emperor Skysplitter Blade. Although the image was majestic, he felt that it was becoming more and more familiar.

"It looks more and more like Lord Guan Yu? It's just that the weapon doesn't match… Wait, why does it look a little like Thanos?"

Han Xiao mumbled softly, not knowing what to say.

These Saint Tyracles scientists, who were fanatical about the Mechanical Deity, spent all their time researching and changing equipment. Did they think they were making mecha skins ‽

Furthermore, the names of these blueprints, these scientists from the Saint Tyracles Race more or less had eighth-grader syndrome…

Han Xiao had the technology foundation of Jayz's treasure and the Sanctum, so he did not lack gold blueprints for the Mechanical Deity. While these two blueprints were quite powerful, they did not provide much help. However, he realized that the Emperor's Cape, the Dark Gold Furnace Beast, and the Emperor Skysplitter Blade actually had set effects, which was rare.

When all three items were activated at the same time, they could trigger a special set effect called 'Tyracles' Frenzy'. With the enhancement of 1.1x in total Machinery Affinity, attack, defense, and physical performance, it was not bad.

What made Han Xiao excited was the last blueprint. The Saint Tyracles Race had a very deep understanding of space. This Space Constants Modifier, as its name suggested, could adjust the spatial structure of a region and change the universe constants.

The principle of this device involved the microscopic expansion of the universe and the collapse of the universe, as well as the technology of raising and lowering dimensions. According to the theory, it should have special effects such as extending or shrinking space, overlapping areas, intercepting or grafting spaces, and the changes to the area would be permanent. There was no time limit, and it was a strategic-level mechanical device.

For example, if the enemy was only three days away from him, this device could expand or shrink the strategic depth of the distance between the two sides. According to the limit of its effect, it could expand the three-day journey to more than ten days or even a few months, or it could even shorten the distance between them to an inch.

However, it was a pity that these were all theoretical conjectures. Before the Saint Tyracles Race could perfect this device, they were already destroyed by their enemies in the exploration era. If they could perfect this technology, the three Universal Civilizations might become the four Universal Civilizations or even the only civilization. However, there were no ifs in this world.

"Most of the technology left behind by the Saint Tyracles Race has been inherited by the Federation of Light. I wonder if they have this incomplete blueprint…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin and pondered.

The Space Constants Modifier was much more powerful than the World Tree's Lerbo Space Protection Belt. If the Federation of Light had this technology, they would have used it back then. However, he could not rule out the possibility that it was incomplete.

After pondering for a while, Han Xiao shook his head and stopped thinking about it.

Regardless of whether the Federation of Light had it or not, he had it. If not for the talent [Tyracles Mechanical Legacy], he would not have had the chance to obtain it.

Beep beep beep…

Just as Han Xiao was studying his new ability, his communicator suddenly rang. He received a message from the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations.

"Heh, it's finally here."

Han Xiao glanced at it and was not surprised.

The three Universal Civilizations would not be able to sit still after he opened up a new level of individual strength. They would come to talk to him sooner or later, but they did not come to him immediately after he advanced. They probably heard from Wuornos that he wanted to familiarize himself with his strength, so they did not dare disturb him.

After replying to a message, Han Xiao turned on his remote projection. His vision changed, and he was already in the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders. He saw three people sitting side by side.

The three of them sized Han Xiao up carefully. Their faces were expressionless, and no one knew what they were thinking.

"Ahem, Black Star, I heard that you have broken through the upper limit of the Beyond Grade A realm and entered a new level of power. Congratulations, you have pioneered a new path."

Marbruce forced a smile and nodded.

"It was just luck," Han Xiao said humbly.

"Is that so…"

Marbruce froze.

You seem to be the least qualified to say that…

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly smiled at the Pope and said, "By the way, I haven't thanked you for your help. It's all thanks to you guys agreeing to lend me the Church's National Treasure. Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to advance."

"..."

The corners of the Pope's eyes twitched.

Provocation, this was definitely provocation!

The moment he thought of this, he regretted it.

In his eyes, Han Xiao was mocking him for making a loss deal!

The Pope looked at Han Xiao's smile and felt extremely disgusted. He wished he could pick up the cup on the table and smash it on Han Xiao's head.

At this moment, Marbruce and Louis turned to look at him with a strange look in their eyes. They seemed to be blaming him for betraying their plan.

However, the two of them did not expect to see the Pope furious. The Pope took a deep breath to calm down, revealed an unfathomable smile, and said righteously,

"You're welcome. You've entered a higher level, which is beneficial to the battle. Of course, we won't be stingy."

Han Xiao raised his brows.

It seemed that Wuornos had indeed reported this to the upper echelons of the church, and he was probably eager to copy his method to advance. The Pope's behavior this time was obviously because he thought Wuornos would be able to step into the Transcendent Grade very soon, so he felt that it was not a loss and had some confidence.

'Tsk, don't blame me then. You were the one who couldn't help it…'

Han Xiao curled his lips.

Frankly speaking, when he invited Wuornos to help him advance, he really did not intend to trick him. At the very least, the Arcane Church's National Treasure and the five elements combined were all real advancement conditions.

However, Han Xiao did not plan to tell anyone about the secret of the Beyonder's Vestige. If Wuornos was determined to advance, he could only sit back and watch.

After all, Wuornos did not seem to want to participate in the battle. It did not matter to him whether he was dead or alive. In any case, even if he was dead, he could still display his use as Beyonder's Vestige. Han Xiao did not mind at all…

However, after fulfilling two Promotion conditions, the success rate of the Promotion would increase by at least two-thirds. As long as Wuornos' luck was not as bad as his, the Promotion would not be a problem… However, without the Beyonder's Vestige, he could only trigger the regular Promotion. When he completed the Promotion excitedly, he would realize that he had not broken through the limit of the grade. Han Xiao wondered what expression he would have.

Han Xiao calmed himself down and casually asked, "You guys contacted me to congratulate?"

"This is a historical event, after all. We would like to ask if you want to make it public to the galactic society."

Louis nodded and asked.

"There's no need to publicize it. We're still fighting. We don't know if the World Tree will steal the intelligence on the Internet in the future. It's enough for the upper echelons to know."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Seeing that the three of them had no objections, he suddenly turned to Marbruce and said,

"Speaking of which, I still need the dynasty's help."

"What is it?"

"I plan to send EsGod into the Underworld after some time and make use of him on the battlefield."

"This…"

Marbruce hesitated.

The dynasty had sealed EsGod for so long mainly because they wanted to study EsGod's body after his soul was destroyed. Marbruce did not want to agree to this request, and he was also not willing to see the Underworld gain more experts.

Seeing his hesitation, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"In exchange, I can provide you with a very interesting piece of information."

"What information?"

"Gaud's whereabouts." Han Xiao smiled.

Marbruce's pupils constricted.

Although he had guessed that it was Black Star who had caused Gaud's disappearance, he could not help but feel furious upon hearing him admit it.

Thinking about how they had been fooled by Black Star back then and caused a huge storm, Marbruce's face sank. He endured his anger and shouted,

"…So it was you!"

Han Xiao did not mind. He waved his hand and said, "Don't be angry. I have a reason for doing this. If you are willing to agree to this deal, I will tell you the reason and give you Gaud's whereabouts."

Marbruce clenched his fists.

Black Star only revealed his cards now, which was undoubtedly related to the recent advancement. There was only one reason for him to do so, and that was that the strength of a Transcendent was beyond imagination. He no longer had to worry about the revenge of the advanced civilizations, which was why Black Star could reveal this secret without a care!

The strength of a Transcendent was still a mystery. They only knew that it was higher than a Beyond Grade A but other than Black Star, no one knew how strong it was. The unknown was the most terrifying.

With Black Star's current confidence, it was clear that the strength of a Transcendent was no small matter. In fact, he had even chosen to show his cards at this time to show his might!

Thinking up to this point, Marbruce suddenly felt a strong sense of fear. The current situation did not allow for internal conflict. He had no choice but to suppress the anger in his heart and think about Black Star's suggestion.

After a while, he nodded expressionlessly and said coldly,

"EsGod can be given to you, but we have to exchange for Gaud. I only hope that your reason will satisfy us."

"Don't worry, you'll definitely be satisfied."

Han Xiao did not mind it.

He had chosen this moment to show his cards because he wanted to strike while the iron was hot. His strength had advanced, if he did not show anything and continued to maintain their original relationship, the three Universal Civilizations might feel that he did not have much confidence. It was time to take a step forward, to pressure them and squeeze more benefits out of them. At the same time, he would let the three Universal Civilizations see his 'unbridled' attitude, which would make them even more afraid of his strength after advancing.

Of course, the reason he did this was that the three Universal Civilizations could not do without the help of the association and because he did not need to fear the three Universal Civilizations anymore.

Some of the 'crimes' left behind in history could be brought up to the public since the three Universal Civilizations could no longer flip the table.

Furthermore, it was not a good idea to keep Gaud locked up. The matter had to be resolved eventually. He had to tell the dynasty what had happened. In the future, if Evans obtained the Energy Control Esper Ability, he could use it openly.

After glancing at the three of them, Han Xiao did not say anything. He deactivated the remote projection and disappeared from the room.

Only then did the three of them relax. They looked at each other with subtle expressions.

In this meeting, they mainly wanted to see if Black Star's attitude had changed after his Promotion.

Back when the Beyond Grade As first appeared, they also had a huge impact on the structure of the universe. Although they did not know how large the gap in strength with the new level was this time, it would definitely not be too weak. Black Star was already recognized as the leader of the Beyond Grade As, and now that he had taken a step forward, the three of them had no choice but to reconsider how they should treat Black Star.

Before the meeting, the three of them had already come to a consensus to react according to the situation. If Black Star's attitude did not change, they would treat him the same way they treated him in the past and treat him the same way in the future. They would pretend that the Promotion did not happen and not make any additional gestures.

However, Black Star's attitude made their plans fall through. Seeing how fearless he was, the three of them felt their hearts sink. They knew that the scales of cooperation between the two sides were going to tip toward the association again.

However, they could not do without Black Star. The three of them did not dare to do anything anymore and were completely helpless.

...

Two days later, the Beyond Grade A Association.

There were no empty seats in the venue. All the association members had been summoned to attend this temporary meeting.

Everyone looked at Han Xiao with shock, excitement, and disbelief.

In the past few days, a rumor had spread among the upper echelons of the association, claiming that Black Star had broken through the Beyond Grade A realm and opened a new level.

At first, not many people believed it, but as more and more association members learned about it, many of them became skeptical.

Han Xiao looked at everyone's expression and smiled.

"I gathered all of you today to announce something. From the looks of it, you should have heard about it in the past few days."

Hearing this, many people's eyes narrowed.

"Black Star, is that rumor true?" Manison frowned in disbelief.

Han Xiao looked at him, then at the others who were staring at him, nodded, and said with a sonorous tone,

"That's right. I've already stepped into the realm above Beyond Grade A, and I've named it Transcendent Grade. From now on, Beyond Grade A is no longer the limit of individual strength… Everyone, there's still a path ahead!"

Everyone was shocked!

Everyone stared at Han Xiao in shock, unable to speak. The room fell into a strange silence.

Chapter 1391: Meeting and Promotion

Looking at the stunned expressions on everyone's faces, Han Xiao knew that practicality was the most important thing. He released the pressure of his life level, and a solid aura gushed out. The air in the room seemed to have turned into a sticky gel, making it difficult for people to move.

A crushing pressure suddenly crashed into the hearts of the Beyond Grade As. Their expressions changed, and they instinctively became nervous. Their nerves tensed up, and the cells in their bodies began to pump out energy like wild cats facing their enemies.

Right at that moment, the pressure disappeared like a receding tide.

Only then did everyone come back to their senses. They could no longer sit still.

"Black Star, how did you do it ‽" Someone was extremely shocked.

"Quick, quick, tell us how to break through to the Transcendent Grade!" Someone could not wait.

"Who would have thought… who would have thought that there would really be a higher level? I thought that Beyond Grade A was the limit of individual strength…" someone mumbled.

The majority of the Beyond Grade As were in an uproar. This situation looked no different from when the Calamity Grade students pestered Feidin when he advanced to the Beyond Grade A realm.

Han Xiao waved his hand and casually said, "The failure rate of the Promotion is very high. I was just lucky."

Hearing this, Secret Master wisely chose to shut his mouth, not daring to refute.

To everyone, Black Star's Promotion was too sudden, and it was difficult for them to digest. Other than a few people who knew about it, most Beyond Grade As could not contain their panic and shock.

Throughout history, generations of geniuses had never been able to break through the limits of individual strength. Many people even thought that Beyond Grade A was the limit of individual strength. They did not expect Black Star to not only break through it but do it at such a young age.

Although they knew that Black Star was the most accomplished Super in history, the significance behind breaking this publicly recognized limit was completely different.

At this moment, in the eyes of everyone, Han Xiao was like a shining guide, a pioneer. His image had once again enlarged.

"You…" Manison hesitated.

Black Star had opened a new level without showing himself, which made him feel very complicated.

Originally, although Black Star was powerful, they were still at the same level. Although Manison was much more benevolent now, he still had some unwillingness to admit defeat. If there was a chance, he would still chase after the competition.

But now, the gap between the two of them had completely widened.

Manison was watching how Black Star caught up to him step by step and left him far behind. Even now, he could not even see Black Star's back. Even with his firm heart, he could not help but feel disappointed.

This time, Kant spoke.

"Black Star, you don't have to be humble. If not for you, this limit would still be an insurmountable obstacle in the eyes of the entire Beyond Grade A group."

His tone was filled with envy but also excitement.

The other Beyond Grade As were the same. Of course, some were envious and jealous, and many felt bitter. However, most of them still thought that they had a huge reliance now!

If an unfamiliar and neutral Beyond Grade A had reached the new level, they would be so envious that they would want to replace him. However, if this Pioneer was Black Star, they could accept it and be happy.

On one hand, Black Star's reputation among the Beyond Grade As had already reached an unprecedented level. On the other hand, he was the leader of the association and had obtained so many benefits for the Beyond Grade As. He had long become one of them.

Due to Black Star's methods and the temptation of the Sanctum, the Beyond Grade As had already formed a close community of interests. The stronger the leader, the more important their Beyond Grade A group would be in the universe.

Furthermore, Black Star was the source of the Sanctum Revival. The stronger he was, the more guarantee their revivals would have, so it was naturally worth everyone's happiness. Furthermore, many Beyond Grade As believed that Black Star, as the leader of the association, would more or less impart them with some experience of breaking through. No matter how they thought about it, there was nothing to lose.

After understanding all the details, most of the Beyond Grade As present became even more excited. They looked at Han Xiao with even more admiration.

Not only did Black Star bring the Sanctum Revival, but he also pointed out the direction of individual strength. Everyone felt that his leadership position had never been as legitimate as it was now.

Han Xiao looked at everyone's excited, respectful, and admiring expressions and smiled.

"It's fine as long as only we know about this. Don't spread it around. By the way, the upper echelons of the three Universal Civilizations already know about it, so don't worry about them… As for the advancement method that everyone is concerned about, I just happened to succeed. I still need to familiarize myself with the power of the new grade. When I have a stable method of advancement, I'll share it with you. Forget it for now."

Beyoni's eyes lit up. "Will you tell us all for free?"

"…Guess?" Han Xiao glanced at him as though he was looking at a lifelong daydreamer.

"I guess not." Beyoni smiled.

"You're smart."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

Hearing this, the Beyond Grade As present did not have any objections. The method to advance to the Transcendent Grade was so precious that even they would not easily reveal it, had it been them who had advanced.

Kasuyi, who was at the side, felt that Wuornos had already grasped the method to advance, so keeping this secret to the association did not seem to be of much use. However, he would not jump out to object.

With his current trust in Han Xiao, he felt that Han Xiao's every action had a deeper meaning.

This time, Beiger could not help but ask out of curiosity, "I wonder if we can take a look at the strength of a Transcendent…"

Before he could finish, Han Xiao interrupted him.

"The war is not over yet. You will see it sooner or later. I won't show it now."

Hearing this, everyone could only nod.

Han Xiao looked around and saw that someone still wanted to speak. He immediately said, "Everyone, today is just to announce this matter and let everyone understand the situation. The meeting will end here. Everyone, please leave. I still have some things to arrange."

Everyone was stunned. They originally had a belly full of questions to ask, but seeing that Han Xiao did not seem to want to answer, they could only swallow these questions.

The Beyond Grade As tactfully stood up and left the conference room with excitement that had yet to dissipate.

Now that they were no longer Supers of the same level, they subconsciously became more obedient to Han Xiao's orders.

Han Xiao watched as the Beyond Grade As left one after another, but there were still some who did not leave. Hila and the other army officers surrounded him with shock.

They had not received any conclusive news before this, so they were just as surprised as the others.

"Come, let's have a few rounds. Let me experience the higher level of strength." Hila went straight to the point.

"Go away. I'm not in the mood to abuse you today."

Han Xiao pushed her aside.

Feidin ignored this and sincerely congratulated, "Congratulations."

After saying that, he could not help but sigh. He had originally thought that he had slightly caught up to Black Star after advancing to the Beyond Grade A realm, but in just a brief moment, the gap was greatly pulled apart.

Han Xiao smiled and nodded. He did not say anything and only patted his shoulder.

This time, Ames walked up and smiled. "What do you plan to do next?"

"Plan? The same as before, continue to prepare for war," Han Xiao replied. He suddenly thought of something and said while rubbing his chin, "But in terms of private matters, I do want to reproduce."

Ames raised her brows. "With who?"

"Are you willing?"

Ames hesitated for a moment before shaking her head.

"Then I can only think of another way." Han Xiao spread out his hands with a tinge of regret.

"What are you going to do?" Ames narrowed her eyes.

"Let me see if I can use my cells to cultivate some test-tube babies through gene modification." Han Xiao turned to look at Aurora, who was a little confused, and said thoughtfully, "Also, if I use my blood and bones to fuse with her life energy, I should be able to mass-produce offspring."

"…Up to you then." Ames regained her composure, shook her head, and laughed. "Your idea of reproducing is really like a Mechanic."

"What do you mean 'like a'? I am a Mechanic." Han Xiao did not care. "Industrialization is the way to go."

War was imminent, and it would be too late for him to give birth one by one. He needed a batch of high-quality Supers who had inherited his Racial Talents, so there was no point in having too few.

To obtain a large enough descendant race, the usual method was to turn into a breeding pig and mate with the opposite sex of the native race. Only males could do this. However, Han Xiao was not interested in this. He was simply going to use the Mechanic method to mass-produce offspring. He did not need to capture the females of other races like the Beast Ancestor. He could reproduce without any gender and be self-sufficient.

Although the offspring raised with this method were more standardized, it was worth a try. After all, it was kind of a waste of resources to have such great Racial Talents but not make use of them. Anyway, he did not lack money or manpower, so raising an entire race was not a problem.

Han Xiao did not mention this matter anymore. He turned to look at Hila and said, "Don't return to Soul Terminal during this time. I am bringing you to do something."

"What?" Hila was curious.

"Kill EsGod," Han Xiao said.

Hila's eyes flashed, and she immediately understood what he meant. She narrowed her eyes and said, "EsGod is a very powerful combatant. If he enters the Underworld, he should immediately become the strongest among the Hero Spirits. Furthermore, without the restriction of the genetic chain, he might be even stronger than when he was alive!"

"That's right." Han Xiao nodded.

He had never underestimated EsGod. Even among the peak Beyond Grade As, EsGod, who was in his complete form, was an extremely powerful individual. What Han Xiao paid the most attention to was EsGod's Esper Ability—[Esper Silence]!

This was the nemesis of almost all Espers. Back then, he had used this Character Summon Card to cause EsGod to fail miserably.

Now that the war with the World Tree was blazing, he felt that it was time to let this trump card see the light of day again.

Feidin blinked and said with doubt, "Strange, the dynasty should not be willing to see the Underworld continue to grow. They actually agreed to this request?"

Han Xiao smiled and shrugged.

"That's because I gave them an irresistible reason."

Beep beep beep…

His communicator rang.

Han Xiao paused and took out his communicator. Suddenly, his eyes sparkled.

The few of them had been paying attention to his expression, and they could not help but lean their heads over to take a look.

"What happened? Why are you so happy?" Aurora was curious.

Han Xiao put away his communicator and laughed.

"My luck has changed in the past few days. I didn't expect double happiness. The army is going to have a new Deputy Army Commander!"

Everyone's spirits were lifted.

"Hadavy, Jotina, or Lagi?" Feidin guessed.

"None of them." Han Xiao smiled and shook his head. "This guy's name is Evans. Let's go and meet him."

Hearing this, everyone was shocked and looked at each other.

Evans? Among the Beyond Grade A seeds that joined later, there did not seem to be such a character. They did not know him. Could it be that he was secretly trained by the Army Commander ‽

On the other side, on a desolate planet in the territory of the Black Star Army.

Streams of light flashed past and Han Xiao, Feidin, and the others had already arrived outside the atmosphere. They immediately discovered the source of the energy fluctuations on the planet. It was a Calamity Grade Super undergoing the final transformation to the Beyond Grade A realm. They had all experienced this stage before, so they were naturally familiar with it.

Han Xiao adjusted his vision and looked through the vortex-like energy. He could clearly see Evans, who was at the center, and he could not help but smile with satisfaction.

First, Feidin became a Beyond Grade A, followed closely by Evans. Thinking about it, the time it took for Evans to become a Super was not as long as Feidin's, which meant that he had reached Beyond Grade A in an even shorter time.

The 'Second EsGod Cultivation Plan' that he had set up decades ago was now more than half complete. There was only one step left.

"I originally wanted to deal with Gaud after some time, but since Evans has already entered the Beyond Grade A realm, I can solve the problem with EsGod together."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Ancient Star Desert, Holy Accord Organization.

"What? Black Star has opened up a new level of strength ‽"

Oathkeeper was stunned.

As an important partner, he was not an outsider. Under Han Xiao's approval, Beiger had already sent the message to the Holy Accord.

Compared to the shock and excitement of the Holy Accord Beyond Grade As, Oathkeeper's vision turned black.

F*ck, I've completely become someone else's underling now. There's no hope of turning the tables!

Chapter 1392: A Taste of His Own Medicine

Han Xiao and the others waited for a while until the energy storm gradually stopped.

Evans' talent was too outstanding, and his advancement process was smooth. He successfully advanced to Beyond Grade A, and the energy in his body overflowed from his eyes. His eyes were like two small suns that slowly extinguished under his deliberate control.

He let out a long breath. The sudden surge in strength caused the breath he exhaled to be like a shockwave, creating a hurricane on the ground. The ground that had already been corroded by the energy into a ring-shaped crater, shattered into pieces.

After all, Evans had only advanced to Beyond Grade A, the power that he released during his Promotion would not be enough to blow up a planet. The only thing that would suffer was the surrounding area. It was as if the ground had been dug up by dogs.

Before he could familiarize himself with his new strength, Evans noticed Han Xiao and the others in outer space.

Without waiting for him to go up, Han Xiao landed in front of him with Hila and the others.

"Well done. I knew you would be able to reach this level easily. Your Promotion time is also earlier than I expected."

"This is all thanks to your nurturing. I originally planned to inform you after my Promotion and give you a surprise, but I didn't expect you to come personally. However, nothing in the army can be hidden from you."

Evans nodded and maintained his humble attitude, not affected by the sudden increase in strength.

Han Xiao squeezed his shoulder to show his appreciation, then turned around and saw Feidin and the others looking at Evans curiously. He could not help but smile and say,

"Come, let me introduce you guys. This is Evans. I've secretly trained him for decades… As for them, there's no need for me to introduce them. You should recognize all of them. They're all veterans in the army and my good friends."

"Hello." Evans nodded at everyone and bowed slightly.

Ames smiled and nodded. Hila nodded coldly, and Feidin and Aurora replied politely.

"Don't underestimate this guy." Han Xiao pressed on Evans' shoulder and said with a smile, "A few decades ago, he was just an ordinary person. The time he took to advance to Beyond Grade A from zero almost caught up to my record. His talent should be second among the Calamity Grade officers in the army."

"That powerful?" Aurora was shocked. "Then who's first?"

"I'm not telling you. You guys will know when he becomes a Beyond Grade A."

Han Xiao rubbed Aurora's nose and smiled.

He was naturally referring to Karlot. If Karlot was guided correctly from the start, Karlot's efficiency in becoming a Beyond Grade A might have even been faster than Evans'. However, he had wasted a long time in the dynasty before receiving his teachings, so he did not have the chance to break the record.

Aurora curled her lips, clearly dissatisfied with Han Xiao's secrecy. However, she could not do anything about it. She looked at Evans, blinked, and said, "Brother, what ability user are you?"

Hearing this, Hila and the others also stared at Evans. They were all very curious about what kind of ability it was that made Black Star think so highly of him and even secretly groom him for decades.

Facing the attention of the upper echelons of the army, Evans was not nervous at all. He slowly said, "My ability is to absorb other people's Esper Abilities for my own use."

"Oh, so it's absorbing… Hmm?"

Aurora subconsciously said half a sentence, but she was suddenly stunned.

Hila and the others were shocked and looked at Evans with a strange expression.

After a few seconds of silence, Ames said with uncertainty,

"Black Star… if I'm not mistaken, his ability is similar to EsGod's?"

"Not really." Han Xiao chuckled. "It's exactly the same."

Hearing this, the expressions of the group changed slightly. They quietly took a few steps back, not hiding their fear at all. At the same time, they looked at Evans and Black Star with even more strange eyes, finally understanding something.

This guy's ability is the same as EsGod's. Could he be EsGod's illegitimate son ‽

Where did Black Star find this guy?

No wonder they had to secretly groom him. If others knew that the Black Star Army was grooming a new 'EsGod', it would cause a huge backlash. The Army Commander was as bold as ever!

Everyone quickly thought about it.

Seeing the expressions of Hila and the others, Han Xiao knew what they were thinking. He shook his head and said,

"Don't worry, Evans is different from EsGod. He's a good guy, and he won't casually absorb Esper Abilities."

"Hehe."

Aurora pulled the corners of her mouth and laughed stiffly.

Hila was not moved, and her expression remained solemn. In a sense, Evans was the nemesis of all Espers. Although the Esper Abilities of the two sisters were very powerful, they were still things that could be taken away by the other party. The purpose of this guy's existence was more than his combat power. He was a trump card!

Evans did not mind the fear of the others. He had long accepted the fate brought about by this Esper Ability and acted as if he did not see their vigilance. He turned to Han Xiao and said with a smile that he was not used to, "Your Excellency Black Star, I have yet to congratulate you on stepping to a new level. This news stimulated me and helped me take the last step, which is how I completed the final transformation."

"Is that so? Looks like you owe me another favor." Han Xiao chuckled.

After he had advanced to the Transcendent Grade, he had asked Phillip to privately tell the two golden leeks, Karlot and Evans. Firstly, it was to stimulate them to work hard, and secondly, although the two of them were loyal enough, they still had to continue consolidating their position. It was naturally a good method to display their new strength.

Only these two people received such treatment. After all, they could not participate in the Beyond Grade A Conference. If he did not inform them, they would not know.

"You're already a Beyond Grade A, do you have any plans?" Han Xiao asked as usual.

"You don't have to ask me. I made my stand back then and stayed in the army to serve you. This is my only choice." Evans did not hesitate at all.

Hearing this, Han Xiao smiled and nodded.

"That's right… Speaking of which, the timing of your Promotion is quite coincidental. As I said, I'll give you a gift when you become a Beyond Grade A Super. I'll give it to you now."

"I'm looking forward to it," Evans said calmly.

Han Xiao snapped his fingers, and a large number of mechanical soldiers appeared, placing a Spacetime Amber on the field.

Everyone looked over and saw a coffin-like mechanical device sealed in the Spacetime Amber. No one knew who was inside.

Sweeping his gaze across the curious faces of the crowd, Han Xiao's lips curled up slightly, and he immediately removed the amber. The mechanical device slammed onto the ground, then quickly disintegrated, turning into tiny snake-like mechanical particles that swam back to Han Xiao.

The person locked up inside was revealed, falling onto the ground with a thud, still in the heavily injured state of being sealed.

With just one look, the faces of Hila, Ames, Feidin, and Aurora changed.

"This is… Gaud ‽"

"Why is he in your hands ‽"

For a moment, everyone was dumbfounded.

Back then, Gaud's disappearance had caused the dynasty to be furious and caused a huge commotion in the universe. Black Star had even been invited to solve the case and acted as a detective. The few of them had always thought that this had nothing to do with Han Xiao.

From the looks of it now, could it be that Black Star was the one who had called the shots ‽

Everyone looked at Han Xiao in shock.

How many things did this guy do behind the scenes? He really was a mastermind!

"Don't look at me like that. I did this for a reason. This kid has a lot of secrets on him." Han Xiao clicked his tongue and pointed at Gaud, who was on the verge of death. "He's a pure dynasty direct descendant. In fact, he's the main consciousness that EsGod separated. He always wanted to communicate with the World Tree, so I killed him. Don't think that I'm deliberately suppressing the dynasty's potential direct descendant."

"Heh, keep making things up." Aurora rolled her eyes.

Han Xiao glared at her and could not be bothered with her. He released a ball of Mechanical Force from his palm and turned it into a lightning chain, binding Gaud's hands and feet, holding him in midair.

"EsGod, how does it feel to see the light of day again?"

"Hah… hah… I don't know what you're talking about!"

Gaud panted heavily. He was still in a state of exhaustion. After being locked up for decades, he stubbornly guarded his thoughts and forced himself to remember the conversation between Han Xiao and him before he was sealed. Although he did not know why he was released at this moment, he remained cautious and did not want to give himself away.

Furthermore, he could sense that the people around him were all Beyond Grade As, and only Evans was a stranger. Furthermore, he had seen the information of Hila, Ames, and the others, so he could not take the risk.

Han Xiao shook his head.

"Hehe, I know you're still counting on the dynasty to save you, but it's been decades since you were captured, and the times have changed. Now that the World Tree has invaded, the three Universal Civilizations have reached an agreement with us to fight the foreign enemies together. Not to mention that you have ulterior motives, even if you're a pure direct descendant, the dynasty will not fall out with us."

Gaud's pupils constricted.

It had only been a few decades, and the World Tree had already invaded ‽

What happened during the years I was sealed ‽

Gaud clenched his teeth.

Currently, only the dynasty could save him. He would not give up his disguise just because of a few words. Even though he was shocked, he had no choice but to pretend that he knew nothing about the World Tree.

However, after thinking about this, Gaud had a flash of insight. He suddenly had the wrong idea about Black Star unsealing him.

That's right, Black Star knows that I have some information about the World Tree, and now that the war has broken out, maybe he wants to seek my help? And trying to force me to admit my identity as 'EsGod' is to find a reason for him to convince the dynasty?

It was a pity that he did not know if his main body had been released. Logically speaking, the first one that Black Star tried to unseal should be 'EsGod's' main body…

Gaud's eyes flickered.

The effect of [Esper Ability—Rebirth] was complete division. Gaud had inherited the main consciousness, and EsGod's main body was a new personality formed from the fusion of his remnant soul and memories. They were already two independent individuals, and the soul connection between them had been cut off long ago. Therefore, Gaud did not know the situation of EsGod's main body at all.

"…I still don't understand! What World Tree? I don't even know what it is. Don't think of getting information out of me!"

Gaud felt that he had guessed Han Xiao's intentions. He felt that the safety of this 'World Tree insider' was at least guaranteed, and he immediately felt more confident. He did not plan to admit his identity with just a few words and was prepared to continue his disguise.

Han Xiao glanced at him and guessed that this guy was mistaken. He shook his head and laughed.

"I think you misunderstood something. I don't need the World Tree information that you have. The main reason I unsealed you this time is that I don't want to waste your abilities."

Oh? Is he trying to recruit me ‽

Gaud's heart skipped a beat.

It doesn't seem impossible. The 'Energy Control' that I created with great difficulty will always be a Super High-Risk Esper Ability with unlimited potential no matter where it is. The chances of Black Star taking a fancy to my ability are quite high.

Gaud could not help but feel conflicted.

If Black Star really wants to recruit me, should I agree or reject him?

While he was hesitating, Han Xiao had already signaled Evans to come forward and smiled.

"He's my gift to you."

"I see, I understand."

Evans exhaled and placed his hand on Gaud's chest.

Gaud was stunned. He looked at the person in front of him, not knowing what Han Xiao was planning.

"What are you doing?"

"…Sorry."

Before Gaud could continue asking, a strange suction force suddenly came from Evans' hands. He could clearly feel his Esper genes being rapidly stripped away!

"What?!"

Gaud's expression changed drastically.

He was all too familiar with this situation. It was the situation when [Esper Ability - Copy] was activated!

The only difference was that he was once the person stealing other people's Esper Abilities, but now, he was the target!

"This is… why do you have this ability ‽"

Gaud could no longer remain calm.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled and said with a teasing tone, "EsGod, you can't be thinking that you're the only one in the entire universe who has this ability, right? The world is very vast… I've nurtured him for decades to prevent him from following in your footsteps. Now that he has become a Beyond Grade A, he has the right to take away the ability that you created with countless evil deeds. How about it? Are you surprised?"

"N-no… Impossible!"

Gaud could feel his Esper Ability disappearing rapidly. His eyes were bloodshot, and his mentality exploded!

He could be sealed and killed, but he could not accept the dream Esper Ability that he had spent countless years to create, becoming someone else's!

Gaud did not want to wait for death and struggled with all his might. However, he could not move at all under Han Xiao's restraint. Furthermore, he was already heavily injured and could not stop his Esper Ability from being absorbed by Evans, who was at the same level as him.

As the cells withered one after another, Gaud's struggle became weaker and weaker. He did not even have the strength to speak. He could only watch himself weaken step by step, gradually losing his ability to sense Esper abilities. All that was left was hatred in his eyes as he stared at Evans in front of him as if wanting to carve his image in his heart.

Evans was not moved at all. After absorbing for a while, he suddenly raised his hand and finally turned the 'Energy Control' into his own. This also meant that Gaud had completely lost this ability.

Gaud's body suddenly shook, and his breath quickly weakened. He opened his mouth and looked at the two of them weakly. His eyes were empty and dull.

His plans, his ambitions, everything was destroyed by Black Star…

At this moment, Gaud had already lost all hope in life, as if he had become a walking corpse that had lost all his dreams.

Han Xiao looked at him indifferently and released his restraints, allowing him to fall to the ground. He said casually, "Don't blame me. This is your retribution. You brought this upon yourself. You once took away the abilities of so many people. Today, I am just letting you have a taste of having your Esper Ability stolen."

Gaud lay motionless on the ground, staring blankly at the sky.

"Black Star, kill me."

"That's going too easy on you. You're still useful. I still need you as a bargaining chip to negotiate with the dynasty."

Han Xiao waved his hand, and mechanical particles shot out, turning back into an imprisonment device and enveloping Gaud. Gaud was unable to resist, and he was immediately locked up.

After doing all this, he turned to look at Evans, only to see that this guy's eyes were slightly closed, and he was familiarizing himself with his new Esper Ability.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled and said,

"How do you feel? Are you satisfied with this gift?"

As soon as he finished speaking, Evans slowly opened his eyes and clenched his fist. A ball of flames appeared out of thin air, constantly changing its energy form. Electricity, storm, nuclear energy, dark energy, and so on flashed past, finally turning into a dazzling psionic energy ball that was thrown out by him.

The dark blue light penetrated deep into the ground, and the group felt the ground swell up rapidly. The ground cracked, and the light from the lava escaped from the cracks, becoming more and more dazzling.

Boom!

The psionic energy that penetrated deep into the Earth Core suddenly exploded. Beams of light penetrated the Earth Core from the inside and turned the entire planet into a sieve. The next moment, the planet expanded and exploded into pieces!

Before the planet exploded, Han Xiao and the others had already flown into space and looked at the formation of a new asteroid belt.

Evans retracted his hand, turned around, and gave Han Xiao a deep bow.

"Your Excellency Black Star, this gift is too valuable. I will not let you down!"

He knew the value of this gift better than anyone else. With this Esper Ability, as long as he could grow, he would be invincible among Beyond Grade As!

This was a gift from Black Star, and it was also his hope. Evans felt extremely touched and wished he could sacrifice his life for Han Xiao.

Since you treat me like a state scholar, I'll be sure to repay this country with my life!

Chapter 1393: Destroying The Spirit

"There's no need for me to elaborate on the potential of this Esper Ability. Just this ability alone can match up to hundreds or thousands of Esper Abilities. Work hard and develop it."

Han Xiao smiled at Evans.

"Understood." Evans nodded, feeling the burden on his shoulders become heavier.

Hila and the others sighed at how lucky Evans was. Not only was he talented, but he had also received Black Star's nurturing and protection, so he did not have to grow like EsGod. He would definitely have a place among the Beyond Grade As in the future.

Everyone could not help but turn to look at Gaud, who was locked up, and pity flashed in their eyes.

Regardless of whether this guy had anything to do with EsGod or not, just this encounter alone was enough to make him miserable. He had thought that he would be free to do whatever he wanted after advancing to the Beyond Grade A realm, but he had been targeted by Black Star and had his abilities taken away. In the future, he could only watch others use his Esper Ability to soar in the universe and snatch away all the achievements that should have belonged to him…

The few of them did not have a deep impression of Gaud. Now that they thought of him, they almost used the word 'tragic' to replace his facial features.

"What do you plan to do with him? Leave him to the dynasty?" Hila suddenly frowned.

"I'll hand him over to the dynasty and explain his identity and origin. The dynasty will deal with the rest." Han Xiao did not mind.

Hila shook her head. "I don't think it's appropriate. If the dynasty executes Gaud, he might be able to regain his abilities through the Sanctum Revival. Since we've already become enemies, it's better to put an end to future problems."

"Tsk tsk, if we're talking about being ruthless, you're the one who's ruthless…"

Han Xiao raised his brows and waved his hands.

"With the revival mechanism of the Sanctum, Gaud will most likely be able to regain his ability. However, the quota for the revival of the Sanctum is now up to me. Whether he can revive or not is up to me. Even if the three Universal Civilizations master the revival method on their own in the future, it won't be a problem. Who knows what will happen in the future? If there's a situation, I can just send him to the Underworld and have another fighter."

Fortunately, Gaud was already locked up by the imprisonment device and could not hear anything from the outside. Otherwise, he would be even more hopeless.

This time, Han Xiao changed the topic and smiled at everyone.

"Alright, everyone knows each other now. After some time, I will promote him to the Deputy Army Commander and let him join the association."

"Isn't it a little too early?" Evans could not help but ask. "My ability is easily feared. Should I continue to hide my identity?"

"You're already a Beyond Grade A, so it's time for you to make a name for yourself. Besides, you're going to participate in the battle, so practicing your cooperation with others in advance is also useful." Han Xiao squeezed his shoulder and said, "Furthermore, with me around, you don't have to worry about the hidden arrows behind your back. Other than enemies, no one can do anything to you."

"Alright."

Evans nodded.

Training in secret for decades was naturally very difficult. Furthermore, he had just advanced to the Beyond Grade A realm, and it was time for him to make a name for himself. Although he felt that continuing to hide his identity was the best choice from Black Star's perspective, he did not want to continue hiding. Knowing that he could finally debut made him happy.

The others naturally did not have any objections, but they were muttering in their hearts. With such a powerful person joining them, he would definitely be the strongest Deputy Army Commander in the future. They had to stand aside.

Even Hila strongly suspected that she would not be able to defeat Evans when he grew up.

"This won't do. If this goes on, my position will be compromised!"

Hila was alarmed, and a sense of motivation exploded in her heart.

It was one thing to be under Black Star in the army, but she did not want to see anyone else standing on her head.

If not for the fact that Black Star was looking for her, she would have gone into seclusion in Soul Terminal for a decade.

Central Galaxy, Arcane Church border.

A large official fleet was stationed at the border outpost, welcoming a spaceship with the Black Star Army insignia.

The spaceship stopped at the dock. Han Xiao walked down with Hila and Evans, only to see Wuornos waiting with a high-ranking official of the church beside him.

"I didn't expect you to pick me up. Do they need to trouble you for such a small matter?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"After all, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is a weapon given to me by the church. Since it is going to be unsealed, I have to be there," Wuornos nodded slowly.

Han Xiao glanced at it, clicked his tongue, and joked, "Stop bullsh*tting. I think the church is obviously worried that I might do something to it, so they called you over. How sad. I said that I would fulfill the deal, so I will definitely return the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to you. Are you so suspicious of me?"

Wuornos secretly rolled his eyes, too lazy to reply.

'A few days ago, you exposed the matter of Gaud. How can we not worry?

Furthermore, your credibility has always been erratic. Who in the entire universe doesn't know that your personality is unpredictable, sometimes good and sometimes bad? Who would dare to completely believe you before the truth comes to light?'

Wuornos cursed silently, waved his hand, and got the Arcane Church soldiers to bring over a piece of Spacetime Amber. It was the piece that sealed the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

"Your Excellency Black Star, please." The Arcane Church official coughed and raised his hand in an inviting gesture.

Han Xiao glanced at him but did not say anything. He took out the Spacetime Amber and poked it lightly.

The next moment, the Spacetime Amber—which the Federation of Light and Arcane Church had been studying for many years but could not break—burst like a bubble.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, which was fixed in midair, suddenly fell. Before it even landed, Wuornos grabbed it and quickly checked it. After confirming that there were no problems, he nodded at the Arcane Church official.

Seeing this, the Arcane Church official's tensed body finally relaxed. He let out a breath and smiled. "Thank you, Your Excellency Black Star."

"What are you thanking me for? It's just a deal." Han Xiao did not mind. Instead, he teased, "Why don't you check for a while more? Don't forget that I'm the Transcendent now. Who knows, I might have done something that you guys won't be able to discover in a while?"

"…Cough, you really know how to joke."

The Arcane Church official's expression froze. Although he had said that, he was not sure in his heart. He secretly gave Wuornos a look.

The corners of Wuornos' eyes twitched, and he had no choice but to lower his head and examine it carefully again.

"There's no hurry. Take your time to check, we have plenty. You have to be suspicious till the end." Han Xiao chuckled.

"You're exaggerating…"

The Arcane Church official smiled awkwardly.

After more than ten seconds, Wuornos raised his head again and glared at the Arcane Church official. "No problem."

"That's good. If there's nothing else, I'm leaving."

Han Xiao nodded and brought Hila and Evans onto the ship. They took off and headed toward the Crimson Dynasty. This trip was just to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

After watching the spaceship leave, the Arcane Church official finally heaved a sigh of relief. He took the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter from Wuornos and solemnly placed it in a special container, letting the soldiers take it to the main ship to store it and wait to ship it back to their mother planet. Although this item was Wuornos' weapon in name, it was actually something that belonged to the Arcane Church.

"After nearly a hundred years, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter has finally returned to us…"

The Arcane Church official sighed, but he realized that he was not as excited as he had imagined.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was a single-target trump card that targeted individual strength. In the past, it would indeed cause people to tremble in fear. However, the times had changed completely. Beyond Grade As had the benefits of the Sanctum Revival, so its effect was greatly weakened.

Furthermore, Black Star had also opened up a new level of power. The destructive power of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter would probably not be able to threaten him at all, not to mention that he had the Spacetime Amber as a defensive treasure…

The situation was so dire that he could not be happy!

The Arcane Church official had a complicated expression on his face. He turned to look at Wuornos and sighed. "You have to succeed. In terms of individual strength, the Arcane Church will have to rely on you to compete with Black Star."

"Don't worry, I won't fail again."

Wuornos nodded slightly and replied casually, but his mind was not on that. He was thinking about Evans, who had followed Han Xiao just now.

He could also sense the aura of a Beyond Grade A from this stranger, and he even felt that this guy was not simple.

'Strange, since when did Black Star have this unfamiliar Beyond Grade A beside him, and he seems to be his subordinate…'

Crimson Dynasty, a secret military base.

This was the dynasty's prison to imprison EsGod. At this moment, a group of dynasty fleets was gathered here, and the leader was Han Xiao's old friend, Teny Amenos.

There was no need to fight in the frontline harassment battle. All they had to do was bombard the World Tree Army. Thus, most of the upper echelons did not have any missions and were all transferred back to the special military training classes that the three Universal Civilizations had opened.

The course that they were learning was a new type of battle strategy that was specially designed based on the tactical habits that the World Tree Civilization had displayed in the past two years of war. This kind of thing would be summarized as the understanding of the World Tree Civilization deepened, and it would continuously strengthen the tactical abilities of the upper echelons.

Today was the day to carry out the deal and let Black Star deal with EsGod. Thus, Teny, who had some free time, was pulled over to be in charge of the defense fleet to prevent any accidents.

"I really didn't expect Black Star to open a new level of strength in the blink of an eye…"

In the command room of the main ship, Teny was browsing through the intelligence data of the past few days. He could not help but let out a soft gasp of surprise as his thoughts drifted away. He recalled the first time he met Black Star.

Back then, Black Star had just stepped into the Beyond Grade A realm, and he was only a colonel of the dynasty's military. They had a good chat, and he had even asked Black Star about technology. When they parted, Black Star had even gifted him a mechanical weapon. At that time, how could he have known that a new Beyond Grade A who had joined the dynasty as usual would become such a bigshot in less than a hundred years? Not only was he a huge obstacle to the three Universal Civilizations, but he was also their reliance in the war.

In the beginning, the two of them would still occasionally send messages to each other. However, as their positions grew higher and higher, everyone became very busy, and their contact gradually decreased. Although he had now become an important upper echelon of the dynasty's military and had been promoted many times, almost reaching the top of the dynasty's system, his position was still worlds apart from Black Star.

Teny shook his head and pondered.

"Strength that exceeds Beyond Grade As… I wonder how many troops it will take to kill a Transcendent individual…"

The tactical deduction of using an army to kill an individual strength had always been an important lesson for the dynasty's officers. Although large fleets could kill Beyond Grade As, they also paid attention to efficiency and success rate. After all, individual strength was extremely flexible, and only by using reasonable targeted tactics could they kill an individual strength at the lowest cost.

Teny had been studying these strategies all these years, using Beyond Grade As as imaginary enemies. He had created many targeted strategies based on different abilities, perfecting the dynasty's tactical inventory. Deducing these strategies was almost his instinct.

Even the direct descendants of the dynasty were his simulated opponents. This was a matter of position and profession, and it did not involve personal grudges.

Therefore, although the two of them were friends, other than admiration, the first thing Teny thought about was how to kill Black Star.

"It's a pity that I don't have enough information, so I can't carry out a new simulation… However, this guy has advanced. He's stronger than before, and the success rate is probably still zero."

After pondering for a while, Teny gave up on the deduction.

He had treated Black Star as an imaginary enemy more than once. Even before Han Xiao advanced, his thousands of simulations had all failed. Black Star was one of the few Beyond Grade As that he had a zero chance of killing. Even people as difficult to deal with as Manison and Kasuyi had a chance of death in the simulations.

I hope I can gather enough information this time…

Teny shook his head.

Other than to prevent any accidents, he also had the mission of collecting Black Star's intelligence. Since Black Star wanted to kill EsGod, he would have to take action. This was a good opportunity to observe the strength of a Transcendent.

Just as he was thinking, the reconnaissance outpost sent a message. The fleet that had gone out to welcome them had already brought Han Xiao and the others in.

He looked up. At the edge of the military base, a few dynasty battleships were leading the way, followed by a Black Star Army spaceship. The radar showed that there were three powerful Supers.

Very soon, the spaceship entered the main ship, and Han Xiao brought Hila and Evans to the command room.

"Hello, Your Excellency Black Star. We meet again." Teny took the initiative to step forward and extended his hand.

"We've known each other for a long time. There's no need to be so polite." Han Xiao did not put on airs and shook hands with him.

"We have already opened EsGod's prison. You can unseal him anytime."

Teny nodded and glanced at the two people beside Han Xiao with a trace of doubt.

Black Star's goal this time was to send EsGod into the Underworld. He could understand him bringing Hila, but who was this other Beyond Grade A?

Sensing Teny's gaze, Han Xiao got Evans to come over and introduced,

"This is Evans, the new Deputy Army Commander of the Black Star Army, a Beyond Grade A Esper with a bright future. He has been training in the army for many years."

Evans nodded politely.

Teny also returned the greeting, but he was surprised.

Why have I never seen this person's information before? It seems like he appeared out of nowhere. He should have left some records when he was at the Calamity Grade. Could it be that this guy has never been active in the outside world and has been secretly raised by the army to become a Beyond Grade A?

Teny felt that the hidden strength of the Black Star Army was deeper than he had imagined.

However, he did not forget the goal of this transaction. He probed,

"Your Excellency Black Star, it is said that you will use Gaud to exchange for EsGod's life. Are you ready?"

"Don't worry, I brought him here."

Han Xiao raised his finger, and a few mechanical assistants carried an imprisonment device into the room and placed it beside him.

With a move of his energy, the imprisonment device immediately turned into mechanical particles and was put away. Gaud, who was inside, fell to the ground.

Hila expressionlessly took a few steps forward, grabbed Gaud by the back of his collar, and lifted him.

"Your Excellency Gaud!"

Teny's expression changed, and he hurriedly went forward to observe.

However, Evans was one step ahead of him. He reached out to stop him and said slowly, "The deal is not completed yet, we can't give you the person."

Teny had no choice but to stop. Looking at Gaud's extremely weak appearance, as though he had been abused, he could not help but be furious.

"Black Star, don't forget that the dynasty is still waiting for your explanation!"

Back then, the dynasty was fooled and even made Black Star the team leader of the investigation team. This was a farce. Black Star might have even laughed at them behind their backs.

At the thought of this, Teny could not help but feel angry that his country had been humiliated, and his tone became impolite.

Hearing this, Han Xiao smiled and ignored him. Instead, he walked in front of Gaud, his shadow covering his entire body.

"This is… the Crimson Dynasty? Why did you bring me here?"

Gaud's dull eyes turned slightly, and he suddenly had some spirit.

"To return you to the dynasty, of course."

Gaud was stunned for a moment, and he was overjoyed. However, he suddenly realized what was going on, and his mood fell once again.

If it was in the past, he would still be happy, but now that his ability had been taken away, so what if he returned to the dynasty?

First, Black Star had taken away his hope, and now, Black Star had given him another meaningless hope. Gaud felt that Black Star was toying with him.

"…Do you think you can fool the dynasty just because you gave me a strange identity? I'm a direct descendant of the dynasty. What you did to me will forever be a stain on your name. You will pay the price sooner or later!"

Gaud pulled himself together and pretended to be furious.

In his mind, Han Xiao had sent him back to the dynasty to force him to admit EsGod's identity and clear his name of attacking the dynasty's direct descendant. He would definitely not let him do as he wished.

However, Han Xiao did not mind. "I know you won't admit it. It doesn't matter. I didn't bring you here for your explanation. I brought you because I want you to see how I kill your main body."

As soon as he said that, there was movement outside the window. A huge prison opened up, revealing EsGod who was locked in amber.

Gaud subconsciously looked over, and his heart tightened.

Not only did you take away my Esper Ability, you even want to ravage my original body in front of me ‽

F*ck you, do you f*cking have to go so far? I beg you, just kill me!

You call me a villain? You're clearly more of a villain than me!

Chapter 1394: Crushed By Auto-Attacks

At this moment, on the Crimson Dynasty mother planet, in the Ruler's office.

In the room, the remote surveillance was showing the scene of EsGod's prison. Marbruce had his hands on his nose, his sharp eyes staring at Black Star in the image, paying attention to the development of the scene.

"Why did this guy take the risk to do this back then…"

Marbruce muttered to himself.

Back then, he had listened to Bekorodi's suggestion and suspected that Black Star was behind Gaud's disappearance. However, Urranrell was the one in charge back then, so it was not convenient for him to interfere.

After he became the next Ruler, it was not suitable for him to thoroughly investigate Black Star, so he kept the matter under control.

The only motive that Marbruce could think of was that Gaud had once tried to simulate the Evolution Cube's ability, which was why Black Star had attacked. As for the idea of Black Star killing a talented rookie, from the series of events with the World Tree, he felt that the possibility of Black Star doing so was low.

"The problem with the Evolution Cube shouldn't have made him take such a risk. Black Star rarely does anything unnecessary. He probably had other reasons for secretly capturing Gaud…"

Marbruce pondered about the excuses.

He glanced at Gaud, who looked like he had been abused, and was even more furious. For a direct descendant to be treated like this, it was a disgrace to their dynasty.

If Black Star used the excuse of Evolution Cube, he would not accept it.

'However… even if I don't accept his explanation, so what?'

Marbruce sighed in his heart.

Now that the situation was dire, and Black Star was fully grown, the three Universal Civilizations also needed the association's strength to fight the enemies. Even if Black Star could not give him a satisfactory explanation, he helplessly realized that he could not do anything to the other party and did not dare retaliate.

From the perspective of benefits alone, the importance of a direct descendant of the dynasty who had yet to grow was naturally not as important as Black Star, their partner. Although the dynasty's prestige was damaged this time, and it made Marbruce furious, venting his anger was not something someone in his position should do. Even if the dynasty wanted to, they had to look at the time and the occasion.

Marbruce even felt a little resentful toward Black Star for exposing this secret in front of the federation and the church. Wouldn't it be better to tell him in private? At most, he would feel embarrassed and not let the other two leaders see him as a joke. It would be better if he dealt with it privately.

Before the problem of the World Tree was resolved, the dynasty could not do anything to Black Star. Not only did they have to work together as usual, but after Gaud was returned, they also had to consider the bigger picture and not take revenge for the time being… The more Marbruce thought about it, the more frustrated he felt.

"I just hope that you can give me an acceptable explanation…"

Marbruce exhaled heavily and lowered his standards.

...

On the other side, the amber holding EsGod was already floating in front of everyone.

Han Xiao glanced at Gaud. Seeing that Gaud was still suppressing the emotions in his heart and maintaining a puzzled expression, he could not help but laugh.

Before his personality split, the real EsGod would not have done this. However, [Esper Ability—Rebirth] had already turned the two of them into independent individuals, and their personalities had changed. Gaud was Gaud, and his main body was his main body. Speaking of which, the 'new EsGod' that was currently imprisoned might have a more 'true EsGod' personality.

"Teny, I'm ready to take action. Activate the space stabilization anchor."

Han Xiao nodded as he spoke out.

Teny turned around and gave the order. The fleets around him quickly surrounded the area and activated the space stabilization anchor to stabilize the area.

EsGod had a lot of abilities, and he was extremely slippery. He could teleport and escape if they were not careful. This was an essential environment modification.

This time, Han Xiao walked out of the cabin alone and slowly arrived in front of the EsGod Amber. Under everyone's gaze, he unsealed it.

Buzz!

EsGod's eyes sparkled, and he immediately saw what was going on. He quickly retreated.

It had been decades since the last time he was unsealed, and EsGod's soul was even more dispirited. However, the wormhole data that Black Star had used to trick him into thinking about the World Tree had already been discovered. Waiting until the day he was released, he had endured the loneliness and struggled to maintain his thinking. Now that he had regained his freedom, he immediately reacted.

However, EsGod was in a very weak state. His wounds that had not healed from the last battle were still hurting, but he still made a defensive stance. His gaze swept across the entire battlefield and quickly locked onto Han Xiao.

"Black Star, I didn't expect you to let me out again. Looks like I made the right bet."

To figure out Gaud's background, Han Xiao had let him out once. EsGod had resisted stubbornly and almost died, but after hearing Black Star's words, he had decided to surrender and not resist. It seemed like he had won the bet.

"We meet again," Han Xiao said calmly.

"Is the World Tree here?" EsGod narrowed his eyes and got straight to the point.

"They're here." Han Xiao nodded and said calmly, "I let you out this time to fulfill the promise I made back then. I'll let you witness everything and borrow your strength."

Hearing this, EsGod seemed to be relieved of a heavy burden and smiled.

"As I said, this day would come sooner or later. You will need my help one day."

EsGod felt a sense of excitement.

After being locked up for so many years, he had finally made it through!

"I won't refute you in this aspect. Although you are full of evil, you are still a powerful combatant. It's too wasteful to lock you up here." Han Xiao suddenly raised his brows. "However, the way you will help is probably different from what you think."

"Hmm?"

EsGod was confused.

"I don't intend to let you live. I need to borrow your life. A dead EsGod is a good EsGod."

"…What do you mean? You want to kill me? Now?"

EsGod was stunned.

After sealing me for so long, you only released me to kill me now. What do you want?

This was completely different from what EsGod had expected. In his imagination, when the World Tree descended, the three Universal Civilizations would most likely ask him for help out of courtesy for the information that he had, giving him a chance to turn the situation around.

However, he did not expect that even though he had gotten what he wanted and waited for the day the World Tree descended, his life would also come to an end… He did not think that he would be able to escape from Black Star's hands in his current weakened state. EsGod had realized this when they fought last time.

He did not know about the existence of the Underworld and did not know what benefits his death would bring to Han Xiao. However, this did not stop him from understanding the other party's killing intent, and immediately reacted.

EsGod retreated rapidly, squeezing his cells to the limit and pumping out energy. His aura exploded, and a radar alarm sounded. He was prepared to risk his life.

At the same time, a resolute mental wave spread out from EsGod's body into the minds of everyone present.

"Black Star! I won't sit back and do nothing. If you want my life, come and get it yourself!"

At the same time, Teny, who was watching the battle, shuddered. He secretly told the crew to turn on the video recording device.

"They're about to start fighting. Remember to record the entire process. Don't miss out on any of Black Star's abilities!"

Beside him, Gaud looked at the scene of EsGod getting into his stance, and his emotions were complicated.

This was the first time he had seen his main body after splitting up. It had been almost a hundred years. Seeing his body, which he had once used to conquer the universe, now being controlled by a new personality, the feeling was indescribable.

After all, no matter what, he had always used that body to live in the past, familiarizing himself with every inch. He had spent a lot of effort nurturing the powerful abilities of his main body, but he was forced to leave it to the 'newbie'. There was both nostalgia and unwillingness.

"If I hadn't been captured back then, I wouldn't have abandoned my main body so quickly…"

Gaud gritted his teeth.

Now that the ability of this new body had been taken away, the original body that was left behind became the only hope in his eyes.

Looking at the scene of Black Star confronting his main body outside the window, Gaud's thoughts raced.

"With the ability of my main body, as long as he can last for some time, he will be able to break through the space stabilization and use Dimensional Hyperdrive to escape… There is still a chance!"

Although he had been locked up for decades and did not understand Black Star's progress, Gaud was very clear about the strength of his main body. With Black Star's strength when he defeated him, he felt that he would not be able to take down his main body anytime soon…

This was hope!

Gaud was energized.

However, just as he was about to focus on watching this fierce battle, the sudden change in the situation shocked him!

A circle of golden lightning spread out from Han Xiao's body, and countless mechanical soldiers surged out. It was as though Han Xiao had become the gate of the secondary dimensional army box, completely ignoring the effects of the Space Stabilization Anchor!

[Godly Stronghold]

In the blink of an eye, the mechanical army far larger than the fleet present had arrived.

The next moment, a large number of machines gathered on Han Xiao's body, quickly forming a Mechanical Deity with a strange appearance. Its structure was extremely complicated, as though it was covered in a dark gold armor. It had a crown on its head, and its facial features were similar to Han Xiao's. Complicated silver-blue matrix patterns covered its entire body, flickering as if it was breathing.

Compared to the average Mechanical Deity, the energy fluctuations emitted by this group of machines were even more astonishing. They had a unique temperament and looked like they were one entity. They did not look like something that was synthesized but more like an independent being summoned.

[Mechanical Deity - Supreme Heavenly Venerate]!

A strong, mighty pressure suddenly swept out. Every life form present felt a huge pressure as if a true god had descended.

Teny and the others were not Beyond Grade As, so it was normal. However, EsGod and Gaud's expressions changed drastically!

"Could it be that you've already…"

EsGod was stunned and horrified.

Why had he been moving around in the universe for so many years? It was all to step into a higher realm!

But now, without any mental preparation, he saw something that he had been dreaming of in Black Star. How could he not be shocked?

Without waiting for EsGod to recover from his shock, Han Xiao attacked. The shadow of the Emperor Skysplitter Blade quickly formed in the hands of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. The next moment, the shadow materialized and slashed.

A suffocating thick psionic energy burst out, turning the visible area blue. Translucent energy engulfed all directions!

EsGod suddenly came back to his senses and hurriedly responded. Layers of energy shields shot out, but under the attack of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate, they shattered and exploded into fragments of light like fragile glass.

He wanted to dodge, but he felt that he was firmly locked onto and could not dodge. Due to the interference of the Space Stabilization Anchor, he could not teleport as well.

EsGod clenched his teeth and gathered what little energy he had left, activating his Esper Ability to fight head-on!

A black and red beam shot out and hit the edge of the Emperor Skysplitter Blade, but was split in half. The blade only paused for an instant before slashing down at an even faster speed. The light from the Getta Hadoken—flowed, compressed, and condensed on the blade—forming a huge light blade.

Bang!

A large blob of flesh and blood mixed with energy exploded, turning into ash halfway through.

EsGod's body was sent flying, and half of his body was shattered!

The last time EsGod was sealed, he had just been beaten up by Han Xiao. His health was already low to begin with, and the power of this slash heavily injured him. EsGod would have been killed instantly had he not hurriedly activated recovery Esper Ability!

Before he could even adjust his state, Han Xiao struck the air, creating a blue shockwave that quickly caught up to EsGod and swept toward him.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

A series of explosions occurred on EsGod's body. It was as if he had received tens of thousands of heavy blows at the same time. His body was covered in dense depressions, and he was almost beaten into a lump of flesh, unable to move at all.

EsGod still had a breath of life left, and he frantically activated his Esper Ability to recover.

However, at this moment, the thrusters on the back of the Supreme Heavenly Venerate spat out thick flames, and the explosion increased its speed. With a turn of the blade, a dazzling slash appeared. The gigantic body was unbelievably agile, and it brushed past EsGod!

Swish!

As the light streaked past EsGod's body, his recovery stopped, and his life force disappeared at a speed visible to the naked eye.

He controlled his newly grown head with great difficulty and turned to look at the Supreme Heavenly Venerate. Complicated emotions flashed through his eyes. There was enlightenment, envy, relief…

"You didn't disappoint me… You've indeed stepped into… the level of my dreams. At least before I die… I was able to see a higher level of power… It was worth it…"

The intermittent mental fluctuations drained the last of his energy. The next moment, EsGod's body dissipated in front of everyone's eyes, turning into starlight and disappearing.

With three auto-attacks, EsGod died!

Teny's expression froze, and his eyes widened in disbelief.

Black Star had killed a Beyond Grade A in an instant before as well, but that was only due to tactics. Most of the time, he would use the method of mutual destruction, and this seemed to be the first time he had done something like instant-killing a peak Beyond Grade A head-on with auto attacks!

It was as easy as a Beyond Grade A fighting a Calamity Grade Super. This was the Transcendent Grade ‽

It was impossible to gather much intelligence on Black Star's abilities with just two or three moves, but the tip of the iceberg was already shocking enough.

Teny could not help but swallow a mouthful of saliva. He deeply doubted whether an individual strength at this level was something that a fleet could deal with…

"What…"

Gaud was also stunned.

He had thought that Black Star would have a fierce battle with his main body, but he did not expect Black Star to kill his main body so easily in the blink of an eye.

What shocked him the most was the fact that Black Star had already stepped into a higher realm!

A deep sense of powerlessness penetrated Gaud's body.

He had wasted so many years, committed countless evil deeds, abandoned precious things one after another, and even changed his body, yet he still did not achieve this dream. However, Black Star had easily fulfilled his lifelong wish…

How hateful!

Under normal circumstances, Gaud would still have the mentality to chase after his goal, but now that his ability was taken away and his main body was beaten to death, he did not have any more chances. For a moment, he felt as if his heart was dead. He felt that all his essence, energy, and spirit had been sucked away, leaving only an empty shell without a soul.

Gaud would rather be locked in the Spacetime Amber forever than experience this series of despairing blows.

At this moment, he had fallen into a negative state of mind.

Chapter 1395: Successor

Just as everyone was having different thoughts, the Supreme Heavenly Venerate shrank, and the mechanical soldiers returned to Han Xiao's body, revealing his original figure.

Han Xiao looked at the location where EsGod had died, and his eyes sparkled.

Just when EsGod's health was emptied with a single slash, a strong intuition suddenly appeared in his head. He thought that his attack might be able to cross dimensions and affect his opponent's information form, but this feeling was fleeting and could not be captured.

'If I can destroy the enemy's physical body along with the information form projection, I might be able to eliminate the enemy's existence. This way, the Sanctum, the World Tree, and the Underworld might not be able to revive them.'

Han Xiao thought to himself.

He suddenly came up with this idea, mainly because of [Information Uniqueness—Conceptual Immortality]. If all Transcendents had this ability, then experts of the same level should have the means to counter it. If only a Transcendent could kill a Transcendent, then they should have the ability to use destructive power in information and conceptual levels.

"I've just stepped into the Transcendent Grade. It seems like there are more abilities hidden at this level that have yet to be completely unlocked."

Han Xiao calmed himself down and flew back to the dynasty's flagship.

As soon as they returned to the command room, everyone turned to look at him with different expressions.

Han Xiao ignored them and glanced at Gaud's expression.

"How is it? Are you happy to see your main body after so long?"

Gaud remained silent. He was filled with hatred, but he did not dare speak. He was afraid that he would not be able to control the anger that he had accumulated and would confess.

Furthermore, Black Star's strength had already made him despair.

At this moment, Teny walked over with a complicated look in his eyes. Then, his tone became firm again.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you've killed him. EsGod will soon become your hired thug. It's time for you to fulfill your promise."

What hired thug?

Gaud was slightly stunned.

However, no one answered his question at this moment. Han Xiao turned to look at Hila, and Hila understood. She showed the Mark of The Underworld, indicating that EsGod's soul had been sent into the Underworld.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled casually and replied,

"Of course, we each take what we need. This person is now yours."

Then, he lifted Gaud up and threw him in front of Teny as though he was throwing trash.

Teny could not be bothered with Han Xiao's attitude. He got someone to help Gaud up. After sensing for a while, he suddenly realized that Gaud's condition was not right.

"Your Excellency Gaud, are you alright?"

"I…" Gaud clenched his teeth.

Without waiting for him to finish, Hila continued coldly, "His Esper Ability has already been taken away by us. He's a cripple now."

"What?"

Teny was shocked, and only after checking carefully did he confirm this point. Furthermore, from his injuries, it seemed like it had happened recently. Black Star had obviously done this, and he could not help but be shocked and furious.

"Black Star! How dare you!"

"Take a break. Tell Marbruce to come out and talk to me. He should be watching."

Han Xiao ignored him.

Teny was stunned. He glared at Han Xiao and gave a few orders.

Ten seconds later, a remote projection appeared. It was Marbruce, staring at Han Xiao with a dark expression.

"Black Star, this is not the deal we agreed on!"

"Is that so? But I remember that the deal was just to hand over the person. Isn't he in your hands now?" Han Xiao did not mind.

"Stop quibbling, you know what I mean!"

Marbruce was furious.

They had made a deal with Black Star because they wanted to exchange for a direct descent with the Super High-Risk Esper Ability, not a cripple. The current situation made him feel like he had eaten a fly.

Energy Control was an ability with a bright future. As long as it was properly nurtured, it would be ranked among the top strengths. However, a Beyond Grade A direct descendant with unparalleled potential had been crippled just like that. Marbruce was so angry that his head was almost smoking.

He was not the only one. All the dynasty officers in the cabin had unfriendly looks on their faces as they glared at Han Xiao and the others. They felt the same hatred because of Gaud's misfortune, who was a direct descendant of the dynasty. If they did not care about the overall situation, they would have opened fire.

"Alright, don't look so bitter. We're not done yet." Han Xiao waved his hand. "Didn't you guys want an explanation?"

Marbruce suppressed his anger and said with a deep voice, "Speak. You better satisfy us."

"You guys think Gaud is a pure dynasty descendant, but his true identity is EsGod. When he was captured…"

Han Xiao could not be bothered to respond to him. He slowly explained the situation of the split personality caused by [Esper Ability—Rebirth].

"…So what you're saying is that you ambushed Gaud and imprisoned him for so many years because he's an unstable factor that might attract the World Tree in advance? However, EsGod did not know that this doppelganger existed, and only Gaud knew his identity… Don't you think this is too ridiculous?"

Marbruce frowned.

Han Xiao said with a calm expression, "I know you don't believe me, but I've already given him to you. If you have the guts, you can dig out the evidence from him."

It was very difficult for him to use Gaud's memories as evidence. The dynasty would only think that it was forged. As a direct descendant who had met with a catastrophe, Gaud would not be treated to a memory search just because of a random suspicion from an outsider. The three Universal Civilizations would never use such methods on the direct descendants, which would easily damage their loyalty. Furthermore, the direct descendants would also resist.

However, even if the dynasty was willing to search Gaud's memories, they would also suspect that he had done something to plant fake evidence. There was no way to completely prove Gaud's true identity, and Han Xiao did not care if the dynasty believed him or not.

As expected, Marbruce did not believe in such a story that could not be verified. He only felt that it was Black Star's excuse and said with a deep voice, "I'm not satisfied with this explanation. According to you, we still have to thank you?"

"Indeed, you should thank me."

Han Xiao did not mind at all. He could explain it properly, but there was no need to.

Using this matter, he planned to change his previous image. Because he had worked together with the three Universal Civilizations to fight against the foreign enemies, he had built a training base together with them and provided a lot of help, causing his image in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations to become too righteous.

Now that he had stepped into the Transcendent Grade, his details were filled with mystery. He could take this opportunity to create distance between him and the three Universal Civilizations, strengthening his unfathomable image in their eyes, and make them feel that the increase in strength had changed his personality. This was very common. This way, the three Universal Civilizations would be more cautious in dealing with the relationship between the two sides and re-establish their attitude toward him.

It was best not to be too sincere when interacting with these advanced civilizations. The upper echelons of both sides knew that they would be opposing each other sooner or later, so it was pointless to talk about making friends now.

Marbruce's breathing quickened. After a few seconds, he calmed down and said coldly, "We will investigate this matter internally and find out the truth as soon as possible."

He wanted to turn hostile, but he did not dare. Even if the dynasty did that, the federation and church would not go crazy with them.

"Up to you." Han Xiao waved his hands.

"…There's one more thing. You destroyed Gaud's Esper Ability, so you have to give me an explanation. Don't tell me that it's still an unstable factor."

"That's it. If he continues to hold this power, there's a high chance that he will participate in the war. With his special feelings for the World Tree, he might cause something we don't want to see… I know you guys don't have the courage to cripple a direct descendant, so I helped you solve this hidden danger. You guys still have to thank me."

"Black Star!" Marbruce laughed in anger. "Can you be any more shameless ‽"

"I'm just telling the truth. Whether you accept it or not is your problem."

Han Xiao's tone was calm.

Marbruce clenched his fists so tightly that his knuckles turned white. After a while, he suppressed his anger and said with a deep voice,

"No matter what reason you have, Energy Control is a unique Super High-Risk Esper Ability. It's too wasteful! If you train it well, this ability will be a powerful method to deal with the World Tree."

With Black Star's strength, position, and influence, he could only look at it from a different perspective and blame Han Xiao for being wasteful. He was also very upset about the disappearance of his Super High-Risk Esper Ability.

"I agree with you on this." Han Xiao nodded. "But don't worry, I did not destroy this ability. It can still be used on the battlefield."

Marbruce was stunned. He subconsciously looked at Gaud, thinking that Han Xiao was referring to Gaud.

However, this time, Han Xiao patted Evans' shoulder and said, "I've already transferred this ability to Evans. Compared to Gaud, his potential is more worth nurturing."

Hearing this, everyone looked over with confusion.

"He has the Energy Control Esper Ability?" Teny could not help but ask with a surprised tone. "How did he do that? What kind of ability user is he?"

Marbruce had the same doubt as he stared at Han Xiao.

"I have been secretly training Evans for decades." Han Xiao looked at everyone and said, "His ability is the same as EsGod's. He can absorb the Esper Abilities of others for his own use. It was through this method that he seized Gaud's Esper Ability gene chain and obtained this Super High-Risk Ability."

As soon as he said that, everyone was shocked.

EsGod was the nightmare of many organizations. Thankfully, he had already been killed, but now there was another guy with the same ability in the universe. Could this galactic society still be good ‽

Marbruce's pupils constricted as he stared at Han Xiao.

Great! Black Star had been trying to groom a second-generation EsGod since a few decades ago. Maybe his other goal of killing Gaud was to obtain 'Energy Control'!

Now that Black Star had an EsGod Hero Spirit and a second-generation EsGod that he had secretly groomed, even Marbruce could not help but be shaken.

Han Xiao acted as though he did not see their expressions and said, "How is it? Evans' potential is better than Gaud's, right? Don't worry, I will do my best to train him so that he can be useful on the battlefield. So, Marbruce, you don't have to worry about this ability being wasted. I'm a very thrifty person."

"…I'm relieved," Marbruce squeezed out the sound of chewing steel from between his teeth.

"That's good. Looks like we have a deeper understanding of each other. Since the matter has been resolved, I shall take my leave."

Han Xiao turned around and left with Hila and Evans.

Teny looked at Han Xiao's back and could not help but whisper,

"Black Star, you've changed…"

Han Xiao paused.

… If I don't change, should I just wait to be eaten by you guys?

He did not say anything and continued walking away.

Very soon, his spaceship left the main ship and disappeared from everyone's sight.

Watching Han Xiao and the others leave, the people in the command room remained silent with complicated feelings.

Marbruce was in a gloomy mood. This sudden turn of events made his stomach sour and nauseous.

He wanted to look down on Black Star, but on second thought, he felt a little dispirited. They did not have the right to look down on him. If not for Black Star, the World Tree would have already broken through the national borders.

Despite the contradiction, he had no right to judge Black Star's character.

"…Take good care of Gaud. Treat his injuries first."

Marbruce sighed and deactivated the remote projection.

Gaud watched the entire process of Black Star negotiating with the dynasty, and his expression kept changing.

Initially, he had a one-in-a-million hope that the dynasty would stand up for him and vent their anger on Black Star. However, the way the dynasty held back in front of Black Star completely shattered his fantasy and his desire for revenge.

Not one of the three Universal Civilizations dared to provoke Black Star. Just what position had this guy climbed to in the past few decades ‽

With my current state, touching Black Star's bad luck again would be like throwing an egg at a rock.

Gaud lamented in his heart. It was as if his bones had been sucked out.

However, he had another question. He turned to Teny and whispered,

"You guys just said that Black Star turned EsGod into a hired fighter. What's going on? Isn't that EsGod dead?"

Teny looked at him with a complicated expression.

Although he did not believe Black Star saying that Gaud was EsGod, he could not help but be wary.

Teny thought for a moment before answering.

"You've been locked up for decades, so you might not understand. Black Star has subdued a pair of sisters, and the Esper Abilities of these sisters are the same as the two sisters in history. They have also opened up the Underworld Dimension, and they can transform the souls into undying Hero Spirits and make them serve as their subordinates. Although EsGod was killed, his soul was thrown into the Underworld and it became their combat strength. There should be more than ten Beyond Grade A spirits in there now."

Gaud's eyes widened.

In the Underworld Dimension.

EsGod slowly opened his eyes, and a boundless black land appeared before him.

"Am I dead…"

EsGod looked down and saw that his body had turned into a semi-transparent spirit body.

The scene before his death appeared once again. The overwhelming saber light had killed all the life force in his cells in one blow, causing him to tremble from the depths of his soul. He could not help but reminisce.

However, it did not take long for him to realize that something was wrong. His soul was only a candle in the wind, but it showed no signs of dissipating. Instead, it was becoming more and more solid.

Swoosh!

At this moment, a few rays of light flashed, and Han Xiao and the others teleported to the surroundings with the King and arrived in front of EsGod.

"What did you do to me?"

EsGod frowned.

"Don't worry, it's a good thing for you. Did you think I would really kill you?" Han Xiao chuckled.

"…What are you going to do?"

"Don't worry, this is a good thing for you. This is the Underworld, and it can stabilize souls. It…"

Before Han Xiao could finish, EsGod interrupted him with his eyes wide open.

"The legendary Underworld ‽"

"Oh? You know?" Han Xiao paused and raised his brows.

"Of course I know."

EsGod nodded. As a collector of Super High-Risk Esper Abilities, he had collected information about all the Beyond Grade A Espers in history.

As for the two sisters, they were naturally the focus of attention, so he had seen all the records of the Underworld.

"That makes things easier. It saved me the trouble of explaining." Han Xiao smiled. "The life and death Esper Abilities of this generation have owners. They repaired the Underworld and restored its effects. You're already a soul now. Are you willing to accept the Underworld transformation and become an undying Hero Spirit?"

Hesitation flashed through EsGod's eyes. If he could live, he did not want to die. However, joining the Underworld meant losing his freedom, and he would probably never be able to free himself.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled and said, "I know what you're worried about. Actually, this isn't a bad thing. You should know your own lifespan better than I. You don't have much longer to live anyway. As long as you give up a portion of your freedom, you can live forever in the Underworld. Furthermore, your physical form has changed, so you don't have to worry about the genetic chain anymore. You will only be stronger than when you were alive. So, why not?"

EsGod's eyes sparkled, and he suddenly said with a deep voice, "Black Star, we've known each other for many years. Although you've reached a higher level first, my goal has not changed. If I join the Underworld, I won't have the chance to advance any further."

"You didn't have a chance in the first place. Even if I didn't kill you, it's impossible for you to advance. You don't have to doubt my judgment. As someone who's experienced, I know better than you what it takes to advance."

Han Xiao shook his head.

This was not a lie. EsGod's genetic chain was too overloaded, and his life form would become even more unstable during his Promotion. Furthermore, with his terrible popularity, no peak Beyond Grade A would be willing to help him with his Promotion.

Seeing EsGod remain silent, Han Xiao thought for a while and smiled.

"But you don't have to be discouraged. Your dream can be fulfilled by your successor."

"Successor?" EsGod was confused.

Han Xiao beckoned for Evans to come over.

"This guy's name is Evans. He inherited your ability and can steal other people's Esper Abilities. Can't he inherit your will and help you see a higher scenery?"

"The same ability as mine ‽"

EsGod was shocked and looked at Evans carefully.

Evans also showed his abilities, proving that Han Xiao was not lying.

Seeing this, EsGod was even more shocked.

"Are you… my illegitimate son ‽"

Evans' face darkened, but he did not say anything.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "How would I know?"

"Let me think…"

EsGod frowned as he recalled.

When he was wreaking havoc in the galaxy, he had naturally vented his desires on females of different species, but they were all left to fend for themselves after mating. He did not know if he had any offspring.

The more EsGod thought about it, the more he felt like he had lost a portion of his memories.

At this time, Han Xiao said, "There's no need to be so conflicted. The probability of having the same Esper Ability is much rarer than having a child, not to mention an extremely rare ability like yours. With my nurturing, Evans did not take the wrong path. Although he has fewer abilities now, his talent is not inferior to yours. Why don't you nurture him and let him fulfill your wish?"

EsGod was silent for a while before suddenly laughing and jokingly saying, "To put it bluntly, you just want to trick me into helping you train your combat strength and work for you."

Han Xiao said without hesitation, "Evans has too little combat experience, so he doesn't know how to coordinate his various abilities. This is your strength, so I'll have to trouble you to guide him."

"…I haven't agreed yet."

"You have a choice?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Heh, that's what I admire about you the most."

EsGod laughed for some reason, looked at Evans, nodded, and slowly said,

"Life is really unpredictable. This is the first time I'm teaching someone… Alright, I'll teach you how to use this ability to fight. I only have one request… If one day you can reach a higher level, help me beat Black Star up."

"Wow, so scary." Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

Evans looked at Han Xiao, then at EsGod. Seeing both of them staring at him, he finally nodded hesitantly.

Seeing this, EsGod opened his arms with a calm expression.

"Come, turn me into a Hero Spirit. Let this world see what I look like without any mental load!"

Chapter 1396: Ranking Restructure, Eldest Brother

The Hero Spirit Modification Ceremony was currently underway, and on a black mountain peak far away, the Hero Spirits of the Underworld were standing, looking up at Han Xiao and the others in the sky. Their eyes were focused on EsGod, who was transforming.

"Hmph, Black Star kidnapped another newbie," Old Nine Aegon Vardnadze crossed his arms and snorted.

"Why isn't this newbie resisting? Did he come in voluntarily? I thought he would only accept his fate after being taught a lesson like Old Nine and Old Ten." Old Four, who had no sense of existence, teased.

The corners of Old Ten Dylan's eyes twitched, and he remained silent.

In the end, he was still forced to accept his fate. Instead of suffering endless torture, he might as well enjoy a limited freedom. He could only hope that Black Star would keep his promise in the future and remove his identity as a Hero Spirit, allowing him to revive normally.

"Humph, I don't care if this newcomer is willing or not. Anyway, I want to teach him the rules."

Aegon Vardnadze snorted.

After being taught a lesson, he finally relented. He was not willing to see the newcomers joining the Underworld so comfortably.

Sorokin adjusted his vision and saw the scene in the distance clearly. He could not help but raise his brows with a playful expression.

"I don't think you can teach him a lesson. This time, there's a powerful guy."

"How strong is he? Can he be stronger than me?" Dylan interrupted.

"You?" Sorokin turned his head and looked at him from head to toe. "I'm afraid you can't even match his one hand."

Dylan was instantly unhappy. "We're both peak Beyond Grade As, can he be stronger than Black Star? If he had that ability, why would he enter the Underworld?"

Sorokin smiled without saying anything.

He was from the same era as EsGod, but the others were different. They did not know EsGod, and he was the only one present who understood how powerful EsGod's combat capability would be when combined with the mechanisms of the Underworld.

"However…" Sorokin changed the topic and said with a smile," No matter how strong he is, his seniority is behind us. He is Old Eleven. "

On the other side, Han Xiao also noticed the movements of the ten Hero Spirit Kings of the Underworld. He turned around and smiled.

The ten Guardian Deities of the Underworld had evolved into Inazuma Eleven. They had finally gathered enough to form a football team.

However, EsGod was easy to talk to because Han Xiao's fists were big, but that did not mean that he had the same attitude toward others. He was not someone who would easily submit to others, and he would not obediently become Old Eleven.

After a while, the Hero Spirit modification was finally completed. EsGod opened his eyes again and felt the form of the Hero Spirit. He nodded in appreciation.

"The fusion of life and death forms a perfectly harmonious structure. This is the ultimate control of Esper Abilities. The Underworld can be called a Space Wonder. The two sisters in history are indeed amazing. Even if I were to develop these two abilities, I might not be able to do better than them."

"Humph."

Hila did not like it when others used such a tone to guide her, but since the other party was the 'God of Esper Abilities', an absolute master in the field of Esper Abilities, she did not say anything and only snorted to express her dissatisfaction.

At this time, the ten Guardian Deities of the Underworld saw that the ceremony was over and came over to get to know the newcomer. Sorokin greeted them first.

"Yo, look who this is. I thought you would be locked up in a dark prison forever. How did you get released and become a member of the Underworld?"

"Sorokin, you're here too?"

EsGod looked over.

"Hehe, looks like you've been locked up for too long. You have no idea what happened in the past few years," Sorokin shrugged and pointed at the Hero Spirits beside him. "Let me introduce them. These seven are Beyond Grade As who joined the Underworld in the exploration era. These two are Beyond Grade As in history. They were revived by Black Star and are both peak Beyond Grade As. We are the Hero Spirit Kings of the Underworld…"

"Revived?" A look of interest flashed through EsGod's eyes. He turned to look at Han Xiao and said with a smile, "Looks like you've done a lot of things in the past hundred years."

"What else? Do you think I've been doing nothing all these years?" Han Xiao shook his head. "In the past hundred years, there have been many changes in the galactic structure. You should ask Sorokin about these things. You guys know each other after all, he will definitely be happy to explain to you."

"That's right, as long as you owe me a promise coin… Don't look so confused. Come, let me introduce you to the currency of the Underworld…"

Sorokin was extremely passionate. He could not wait to promote the financial system that he had created.

However, before he could say anything, Dylan interrupted him and sized EsGod up.

"I haven't asked for your name. What's yours?"

EsGod turned to look at him. "You don't need to know my name. Just call me EsGod."

"What do you mean?"

"God of Esper Abilities."

Dylan laughed and said sarcastically, "Not even the most powerful Espers in history dared to call themselves that. Old Eleven, do you deserve this name?"

"Old Eleven?" EsGod raised his brows and counted the people in front of him. He immediately understood the order of ranking.

"You're not convinced?" Dylan snorted.

"If we were still alive, you would be dead by now." EsGod's tone was calm. As someone who made the galactic society tremble in fear, he was not a good-tempered person.

"Sure, let's fight. Sorokin said you're very strong, but I want to see how you kill me."

Dylan sneered. He remembered Sorokin's words and refused to believe them.

In any case, they were all Hero Spirits who would not die. If they were not convinced, they would fight.

Han Xiao could not help but glance at him. He did not find it strange. Dylan had a foul mouth, and he also had the ability to taunt others. He had always liked to stir up trouble. Furthermore, after accepting Hero Spirit's identity, this guy no longer had anything to worry about. It was as if he had released his nature. His foul mouth became worse, and his taunts became more and more casual. His personality was extremely unrestrained.

They were all Hero Spirits, and without Aurora giving them life force, no one would be able to do anything. It was likely that Dylan was just enjoying the feeling of the other side not being able to do anything to him.

"What do you say?" EsGod turned to look at Han Xiao.

"Since that's the case, Aurora and I will temporarily give you a body. You guys can rearrange your positions, and strength is everything." Hila's eyes lit up. She was most willing to watch others fight a bloody battle, so she immediately decided.

"I agree." Sorokin's eyes lit up, and he immediately agreed.

Although he was not the strongest among the Hero Spirit Kings, he was definitely ranked at the top. At the very least, he did not have to continue being Old Eight.

"That's right, I agree." Dylan snorted and pointed at EsGod. "I hope you can let me enjoy myself."

"I'm in a good mood today, so let's celebrate my new life with you."

EsGod paused and turned to look at Evans.

"This time, I'll show you the combat style of this ability. Watch and learn."

Evans immediately perked up.

Not long after, Aurora was called over by Hila to build a body for the numerous Hero Kings.

Han Xiao brought them to the main universe and found a desolate universe belt as the battlefield.

Three days later, the eleven of them returned to the Underworld in their Hero Spirit form. They did not mention the battle at all and only silently rearranged themselves.

EsGod became the eldest brother out of nowhere, Dylan became the second, Sorokin became the third, and Aegon Vardnadze became the fourth.

Although the first and second positions were only one position away from each other, there was a huge gap between their strengths. As a spectator, Han Xiao had finally witnessed the strength of EsGod when he was at his peak. He was much stronger than when he was alive, and it was a piece of cake for him to beat up Dylan.

In Han Xiao's eyes, he was probably the only one in the entire universe who could easily take down EsGod. The others would at most fight to a draw, and EsGod with no mental load would not be afraid of anyone but him.

On the other hand, Wuornos' chances of winning were even lower than that of Herberlon. Even if his Energy Rank was higher, he might not be EsGod's match. After all, he was an Esper. As long as he was touched by [Esper Silence], he would basically be dead.

On the other side, in the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations.

The three leaders had just finished a meeting and were arranging the documents when Louis suddenly thought of something. He looked at Marbruce and asked curiously,

"How did your deal with Black Star go? I heard Gaud has returned?"

Marbruce paused and slowly nodded.

The Pope narrowed his eyes and slowly said, "So, Gaud was really captured by Black Star. How did your dynasty deal with him?"

"…I'm still investigating the inside story. You don't have to worry about the details."

Marbruce shook his head.

Seeing this, the two of them guessed that the dynasty had most likely been defeated by Black Star and could not help but laugh inwardly.

The Pope coughed and said calmly, "Black Star is fully grown, so let's not bother about him for now. No matter what, we have brought back a direct Beyond Grade A with extraordinary potential. In the future, he will definitely become an important pillar of our individual strength. Congratulations on obtaining a new National Pillar. Train Gaud well."

Because he had Wuornos at home who was preparing to advance to the Transcendent Grade, the Pope was very open-minded and did not mind that the dynasty had regained Gaud. Furthermore, from the standpoint of the three Universal Civilizations, this was also a good thing.

Marbruce's heart skipped a beat.

Others thought that Gaud was still the Super High-Risk Esper Ability possessor with unparalleled potential, and they were congratulating him for obtaining the potential seed. It was a kind of mockery, and he did not feel good about it.

Marbruce did not want the two of them to know that the dynasty had made a loss this time and used EsGod to exchange for a cripple. He had no choice but to suppress his anger and smile.

At the border of the Flickering World.

Huge engineering spaceships cruised through space one after another. Planetary harvesting devices covered the planets one after another, carrying out destructive development, draining the planet's core, crushing the planet, and disintegrating it into various substances that flowed into the enormous storage pods. It was like a swarm of locusts sweeping across the galaxy, leaving only barren land wherever it passed.

There were a few Star Clusters at the border of the Flickering World. Originally, it was a place with plenty of resources, but under the destructive development of the three Universal Civilizations, it was gradually turning into a desolate universe belt. It was currently transforming into a strategic deep region to face the World Tree's attacks in the future. All the valuable resources were taken away, leaving nothing behind for the World Tree.

At this moment, at the edge of the development zone, a small dynasty fleet was escorting an ordinary spaceship with the Black Star Army's insignia.

In the spaceship, Bun-Hit-Dog was arranging the materials he had collected for this trip. The players around him all had the ID prefix of Bun-Hit-Dog's studio, and they were all his employees.

"It's a pity that the dynasty did not allow us to go deep into the development zone. This time, we only managed to gather some scraps. It's not enough to make a video of the three Universal Civilizations preparing for war…"

Bun-Hit-Dog sighed, not too satisfied with his gains.

"Be content. The three Universal Civilizations have already made an exception by allowing us to take a look at the periphery."

The assistant, Little Wheat, curled his lips.

Currently, most of the players were participating in the harassment battle at the frontline, but Bun-Hit-Dog did not stay at the frontline all the time. Because there were battle reports everywhere, it was not convenient for him to make videos. He keenly felt that the changes in the backlines would be more valuable, so he brought a group of studio employees back to the explored universe to search for news everywhere.

Not long after, Bun-Hit-Dog set his sights on the two news locations, the Black Star Training Base and the three Universal Civilizations' war preparations. However, the training base did not allow outsiders to enter, so he could only observe the latter.

Bun-Hit-Dog was doing quite well in some of the departments of the three Universal Civilizations. Firstly, the accounts under his studio all prioritized optimizing charisma, and they specialized in building a good relationship with various characters. Secondly, Bun-Hit-Dog kept promoting himself and pulled many players to be his backers, letting the three Universal Civilizations know that he had a special influence among the Immortals and became the exclusive media of the Immortals. Thirdly, he had the special identity of a reporter from the Black Star Army, and his studio was attached to the intelligence department of the army. It was a branch that was officially recognized, and it had a news license.

Therefore, in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations, Bun-Hit-Dog represented the special intelligence personnel of the immortals group of the Black Star Army. He had some face and was able to discuss business and cooperation with the various organizations as a player. This was also the way some guilds did things. With so many conveniences, Bun-Hit-Dog's business flourished.

He submitted a visit request to the three Universal Civilizations, and after some negotiation, Bun-Hit-Dog and the others finally obtained permission to come to the edge of this border development zone to take a look. However, the results were not as expected, and they were now on their way back.

"What should I do? Although I don't lack material now, it's all old talk. I need sensational news!"

Bun-Hit-Dog tugged at his hair with a troubled expression.

At this moment, a chat notification popped up on the forums. An employee had sent a private message.

"Boss, I made a huge discovery. This material will definitely scare you to death!"

Bun-Hit-Dog looked at his ID and remembered that he was the supervisor in charge of the dynasty's news materials.

"Cut the crap. Tell me what you found!"

"This is what one of my subordinates heard from a dynasty logistics officer. It is said that not long ago, Black Star went to kill EsGod and showed his strength that surpasses Beyond Grade A. He even handed Gaud over…"

This small supervisor spoke with confidence. He did not know about the behind-the-scenes deal that Black Star made and only talked about what he did on the surface, but this was enough to shock Bun-Hit-Dog.

"Is this information true ‽" Bun-Hit-Dog felt his bladder tighten.

"I don't know. That employee of mine has a very good relationship with that dynasty officer. Anyway, I found out from him that this officer was present at the scene!"

"Well done! All the money spent over the years was not wasted!" Bun-Hit-Dog slammed the table excitedly.

The size of his studio was not small. He had arranged for a regional branch in some large organizations and had his employees specially make friends with the people from the various departments of these large organizations. He had been investing money to form an intelligence network, and occasionally, he would get insider information from these people.

Of course, with his personal assets, there was no way he could open such a huge business. There were also sponsors behind him.

As for the biggest sponsor, it was Black Star himself. Bun-Hit-Dog had thought that Han Xiao had a good impression of him, which was why he had received the funds.

The inside story this time was the biggest piece of news he had ever received. Although he did not know the reason, just the fact that Black Star had broken past Beyond Grade A and Gaud's disappearance had something to do with Black Star was enough for him to make a video.

Even if it was just groundless speculation, the gimmick was enough to attract attention.

Bun-Hit-Dog immediately slammed the table.

"Hurry up and send me the material. The video has to be uploaded within three days. You guys have to work overnight. I'm going to be popular again!"

Chapter 1397: Group Battle's Godly Artifact and Request

The rankings were rearranged in the Underworld, and Evans temporarily stayed behind to receive EsGod's guidance. Han Xiao then returned to the training base to train in seclusion. He used the new level of strength to upgrade all the machines under him and also studied some profound blueprints.

The dynasty was tricked, but they did not make a move. They endured and remained silent. Gaud's whereabouts were also sealed. Han Xiao did not know how the dynasty planned to deal with Gaud. Maybe they were thinking of ways to restore his ability. Anyway, it was impossible for this guy to appear in the outside world for a while.

The storm caused by his advancement to the Transcendent Grade slowly subsided. After the initial shock, the three Universal Civilizations also accepted reality and returned to their normal state.

A few days later, in the Black Star Army's private machinery factory.

Han Xiao stood in front of an experiment table and stared at a floating hourglass-shaped device. A dense amount of Mechanical Force was emitted from his body and connected to this device like a chain. The space on both ends of the device started to tremble.

"So, this is the principle behind psionic waves. Tsk tsk, this technology's destructive power is not simple. It is indeed advanced technology. If combined with a Universal Treasure-level transmitter, it would be a large-scale strategic killing weapon. I've really picked up a treasure this time…"

Excitement flashed in Han Xiao's eyes.

After these few days of research, he finally understood the psionic wave technology. In his eyes, this thing was an absolute godly weapon for group battles. Firstly, it would absorb energy from the outside world and automatically increase its attack range. If given enough time, it could even cover the entire galactic battlefield, but it was more controllable and would not spread endlessly.

Secondly, it was just as difficult to block and clean up as the Primordial Psionic Energy. In fact, because the psionic wave's explosive form was like a shockwave instead of a solid energy mass like Primordial Psionic Energy, the speed at which it expanded was much faster and harder to block. Furthermore, it could ignore matter to a large extent, and its penetrative power was astonishing.

The third was that it could eliminate different forms of energy. Any type of energy could activate the transmitter, and the energy input was the type of energy targeted by psionic waves. It could be mixed multiple times. If dark energy was injected, psionic waves would eat dark energy and destroy the shields, physical devices, and energy cores that were formed or maintained by dark energy. At the same time, it would not affect other forms of energy. The reason why psionic waves destroyed all the electrical devices in the Arthur Civilization was that the researchers injected electricity.

In addition, no matter what kind of energy the psionic waves targeted, it would be extremely fatal. If a life form not strong enough was swept by the psionic waves, they would be reduced to ashes. The entire Arthur Civilization was wiped out by this.

"The fleets of the advanced civilizations are basically powered by dark energy and psionic energy. If I target these two types of energy, no matter how large the fleet is, it will be paralyzed. The number of troops will lose its meaning in front of this technology, and it will be enough to serve as the main battle weapon."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The psionic wave technology was too powerful, just like an enhanced version of the omnipotent EMP. He did not plan to let others use it, or it would only end up threatening him.

Mechanics had many powerful weapons, but most of them were technologies owned by advanced civilizations. Therefore, most Mechanics did not seem to have any special killing methods, but psionic wave technology could be used as a trump card.

If this thing was installed on the Emperor Skysplitter Blade, Han Xiao believed that even without summoning his mechanical army, he would be able to fight the enemy fleet head-on in a one billion level galactic battlefield.

With one slash, millions of battleships would be paralyzed. How terrifying was that!

Han Xiao could not help but imagine this scene, and his mood instantly improved.

Tyrsius was truly a great man. Not only did he provide the Beyonder's Vestige to help him advance, but he also indirectly gave him such a powerful black technological weapon. What kind of generosity was this? It could move the whole Galaxy!

After a while, Han Xiao waved his hands, and the psionic wave transmitter in front of him disappeared.

This was not a physical creation but a temporary product converted from [Virtual Creation (Pseudo)].

During this time, he had discovered a new method to use this ability for research.

Originally, Han Xiao only had an incomplete version of the psionic wave transmitter prototype that he had dug out from the Arthur Civilization. It was very difficult to reverse-engineer the technology. However, after dismantling the prototype and figuring out the rough structure and materials used, he used [Virtual Creation (Pseudo)] to create a temporary product and reverse-engineered the technology on the undamaged temporary product. This way, the efficiency was thousands of times higher than studying the prototype!

It was through this move that he was able to deduce and perfect the principles step by step, allowing him to understand all the tricks and reverse engineer the complete technology.

"Although this technology is powerful, it still needs to be tested. It's not suitable for actual combat."

Han Xiao went through the information in his mind and nodded.

Although the psionic wave mechanism was advanced technology, he still needed to look at its capacity and strength. Just because it was difficult to stop it did not mean that it was unresolvable. After all, it was not an unreasonable Space Wonder, and it could still be neutralized and countered. For example, even if the dark energy controlled by Clotti was targeted, it would at most be weakened and not directly disintegrated by psionic waves.

Therefore, in Han Xiao's eyes, there was still room for improvement in the various parameters of this technology. He planned to strengthen it to the extreme and only use this trump card when the time was right.

Han Xiao took a deep breath and moved his fingers. The experiment table floated away and returned to its original position.

With a wave of his hand, the fridge in the corner opened, and a bottle of iced beverage flew into his hand. He took a big gulp and relaxed slightly. He opened the forums to refresh his mood.

Currently, the battle at the frontlines was extremely intense, and eighty percent of the forums were filled with battle reports. Han Xiao quickly went through the posts one after another, and he suddenly noticed that a popular post had been pinned. It was Bun-Hit-Dog who had posted another new video.

He went in to take a look and saw that the post was being refreshed at a rate of a few hundred posts per second.

Han Xiao clicked on the video and realized that the duration of this episode was a little short. A lot of bullet comments quickly floated past.

"First!"

"It's here!"

"That's it? That's way too short!"

"Can I free this video?"

"I just pooped, and the video ended."

"Trash Bun-Hit-Dog, another average video. Hurry up and come out in female clothes to apologize for your mistake!"

"There's a saying, 'Bun-Hit-Dog's cross-dressing looks the best'. It makes me feel like the love between the elderly."

"Thank you, brother, I've vomited. My stomach feels much better."

Han Xiao looked at the comments and felt much happier. He then looked at the content of the video.

Bun-Hit-Dog made a series of dazzling video clips and said two pieces of news in a familiar video presentation style. One was that Black Star was suspected to have broken through the limit of Beyond Grade A, and he had secretly entered a higher level. The second was that Black Star was suspected to have kidnapped a direct descendant of the dynasty for reasons unknown.

These two pieces of news were very sensational. Bun-Hit-Dog did not waste any materials and added a lot of groundless rumors. It had a sense of déjà vu of 'Approaching Science' documentary film. There was even a short video of an interview with the dynasty officer who was the source of intelligence. He even thoughtfully gave the other party a mosaic.

The video was not long, and it ended very quickly. Han Xiao scrolled through the replies and realized that many players were shocked by this, mainly because of the improvement in his strength.

"Has the Army Commander broken through the Beyond Grade A realm? Why isn't there any news about it?"

"Could it be a secret?"

"Is there any warrior who wants to confirm the rumors with Black Star? We will pay our respects to you seven times."

"I think it's real. The Army Commander only used twenty to thirty years to become a Beyond Grade A Super. Now that he has stayed at this level for seventy to eighty years, it's normal for him to break through another level."

"^ One look and I can tell that you have never studied the history of the development of the Supers in the Galaxy. Beyond Grade A and above Beyond Grade A are not the same concept. This is the first case. If it's true, then it's making history."

"Speaking of which, the version this time is called the Age of Black Star. It's actually referring to this. I definitely won't be wrong this time!"

Although the players were shocked, Black Star had created too many miracles, and the players were already very resistant to it. The reactions had long changed from 'he is actually so awesome' to 'he is still so awesome'.

Han Xiao did not pay too much attention to the reactions of the players. He was just a little surprised that Bun-Hit-Dog was able to obtain such news. The dynasty had locked down the news, and many large intelligence organizations did not know anything about it. It could only be said that Bun-Hit-Dog was indeed a player that poked into every nook and corner.

"Luckily, this news is only circulating among the players, and there's no absolute evidence. It's just some groundless speculation, so the impact is limited."

Han Xiao shook his head. He did not want too many people to know about his Promotion for the time being, but he did not plan to seal or mask it. If the players knew of it, then so be it.

After scrolling through the forums for a while and looking at the army players' bullshit, Han Xiao closed the interface with a smile and prepared to continue studying the technology.

This time, Phillip suddenly appeared.

"Master, hum, Risda wants to see you, hum!"

Han Xiao then remembered that he had this person under him.

"Oh, let him come over."

After a while, a human-shaped light appeared in the room. Risda bowed and greeted Han Xiao.

"Your Excellency Black Star."

"It's been some time since we last met. As you know, I've been quite busy recently. How are your compatriots I saved last time?" Han Xiao asked.

"Thank you for your care. My compatriots have already given birth to many new members, and the AI civilization has been rebuilt. It has been recuperating for decades."

"That's good. What brings you here?"

"Your Excellency Black Star, although our civilization has been rebuilt, most of our compatriots are still controlled by the Mechanic Emperor and are in dire straits. You have a very high position now, so I would like to request your help again."

Hearing this, Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and remembered this mission that had been accumulating dust for many years. The requirement was to free the AI civilization members under Manison, and it was not completed yet.

"This matter… Alright, it's time to resolve it."

Han Xiao thought about it and agreed. He felt a little bad about letting Risda wait for so many years.

Risda's compatriots had been transformed into Indestructible Mechanical Troops, and they were Manison's trump cards. It was not easy for him to deal with this problem in the past, but now that he had become a Transcendent, he had a way to solve it.

In front of Risda, Han Xiao took out his communicator and called Manison.

After a while, the communication was connected, and Manison appeared on the virtual screen.

"…What's the matter?"

Good lord, this d*mn guy doesn't even bother greeting.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. "I want to make a deal with you."

"Speak."

Why is this aloofness back again? Are you the Transcendent or me?

Han Xiao thought to himself but did not bother to argue. He slowly said, "I want an exchange for the artificial intelligence civilization that you captured."

"You want me to release the Indestructible Mechanical Troops?"

Manison narrowed his eyes.

If someone else had made this request, he would not have bothered, but Han Xiao was different.

Manison thought for a while but did not reject it immediately. He nodded and said, "Then let's exchange it for the method to advance to the Transcendent Grade."

"…Are you still asleep?"

"There's no harm in trying." Manison's tone was calm. "Then what do you plan to exchange for it? This is my blood, sweat, and tears."

"Don't count on the complete Promotion method. However, I can tell you one of the conditions for the Promotion. Also, I will give you another group of artificial intelligence lives to transform into the Indestructible Mechanic Empire."

"Sure, deal. Also, you have to help me pay for the Indestructible Mechanic Emperor."

Manison nodded.

"Have you been very poor recently?" Han Xiao curled his lips.

"In any case, I'm not as rich as you. I'm just an ordinary peak Beyond Grade A Mechanic. How can I compare to the first Transcendent Mechanic in history?" Manison's lips curled up.

Han Xiao:"…"

Oh my god, Manison has learned to be sarcastic. My youth… oh, it has long ended.

After finalizing the details, Han Xiao put away the communicator, looked at Risda, and nodded.

"He has already agreed. I will go to the Mechanical Race and bring your compatriots back."

"Our entire race will forever remember your kindness."

Risda was extremely grateful. He sighed that his investment back then had been too accurate. It was only because of a look he took, but he had already accurately latched onto the thickest thigh in the galactic society.

The problem that had troubled him for many years was solved with just a few words. Risda felt that it was indeed the right decision to wait for Black Star to grow.

An hour later, in the Mechanical Race territory.

Han Xiao left a Throne in the nearby base and quickly teleported over to the Mechanical Race's territory. Manison's Lord's Avatar was already waiting on the landing platform.

"I'm here. Where are your Indestructible Mechanical Troops?"

Han Xiao looked around but did not see the target.

Manison shook his head. "Give me what I want first."

He still remembered that the last time they fought, Black Star's Virtual Purification had awakened a large number of artificial intelligence lives, causing him to fail miserably. Therefore, he did not dare call out the troops at this time, afraid that Black Star would attack him directly and take away the target with force, making the deal invalid. He did not have the ability to find trouble with Black Star now, so he could only suffer.

Han Xiao thought about it and understood Manison's concerns.

"Why are you so guarded against me? With our relationship, can I cheat you?"

Manison almost said that Han Xiao had cheated him so many times, but he did not dare to say it.

"Tsk, alright. I'll give it to you first." Han Xiao did not mind. After all, Manison did not dare go back on his word.

"Let me take a look at the artificial intelligence lifeform you prepared for me." Manison was still worried.

Han Xiao rolled his eyes. "Alright, summon some mechanical lives."

"What for?"

"Heh, did you think I would kidnap an artificial intelligence civilization and give it to you? Of course, you're the one who will provide the raw materials. I'll transform them for you. This time, I'll show you the methods of a Transcendent. I'll treat it as giving you benefits."

Manison opened the secondary dimensional army camp and pulled out a large number of mechanical lives. These were all members of the Machinery Civilization that he had created.

Seeing this, Han Xiao raised his hand. Mechanical Force flashed and instantly swept across all the mechanical lives present.

The next moment, the bodies of all the mechanical lives changed at the same time, becoming transparent and illusory.

Manison's expression changed. He could clearly sense that the Mechanical Lives were undergoing a miraculous change, gradually turning from a Mechanical Body to an artificial intelligence lifeform.

"What ability is this ‽" Manison was shocked.

Although he could do something similar, that was by extracting the artificial intelligence of a mechanical life and carrying out a series of complicated operations.

However, Black Star had directly transformed a solid mechanical life into artificial intelligence data. Only a Mechanic would know how unbelievable this was!

"Don't look so shocked. I can directly change a life form into a virtual soul. They will be my bargaining chip." Han Xiao smiled.

"Is this a Transcendent technique…"

Manison muttered to himself, his heart burning.

"Tell me, what is one of the conditions to advance?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao smiled.

"Then remember, one of the conditions to become a Transcendent is… to use the Church's National Treasure!"

Manison's eyes flashed.

At this moment, seventeen to eighteen plans to deal with the Arcane Church flashed through his mind, and he almost wanted to resume his old job as a sh*t stirrer.

Chapter 1398: The Church's Attempt

Seeing Manison deep in thought, Han Xiao smiled.

He was not lying. He had indeed used the Church's National Treasure to advance, and it was effective. However, he did not intend to reveal the specific conditions of the 'stabilizer'.

As for what Manison would do when he set his sights on the Arcane Church, Han Xiao did not care. After all, he had still not figured out what could replace the effect of the Church's National Treasure. Therefore, the Church's National Treasure was indeed the only choice at the moment, and he definitely was not inciting a fight on purpose.

Han Xiao shrugged and interrupted Manison's thoughts. "I can also give you a piece of advice. This is just one of the conditions. Don't try to advance without absolute confidence."

Manison regained his senses and nodded absent-mindedly.

Han Xiao did not say much and changed the topic.

"Alright, I've already told you the condition. It's time for you to fulfill the deal."

Hearing this, Manison calmed himself down and finally summoned the entire artificial intelligence civilization. He quickly removed the binding of the Indestructible Mechanical Troops and the main system. Just as he was about to modify the fundamental logic, he suddenly remembered that Han Xiao had Virtual Purification, so he stopped his action.

"The entire race is here. You can turn them back yourself. I won't waste my energy."

"You're lazier than before." Han Xiao shook his head and released Virtual Purification.

The ring of light spread out and quickly swept past the orderly rows of Indestructible Mechanical Troops. The next moment, these artificial intelligence lives immediately broke free from their controlled state and quickly regained their original consciousness. They were at a loss and started to panic.

Han Xiao did not say much to them. A suction force suddenly burst out from his body, like a black hole suddenly opening up. The Godly Stronghold took all the targets away, and he planned to explain it to Risda when he returned.

After absorbing the entire AI civilization, Han Xiao silently counted the names on the list. Suddenly, he paused and said, "There's one less. Finette has to be returned as well."

"I forgot."

Manison remembered and summoned Finette. This was the ancestor of the AI civilization. He had not been transformed into an Indestructible Mechanical Troop and had always been his artificial intelligence assistant.

Han Xiao pointed, and a flash of lightning entered Finette's body. Finette trembled, and the twisted logic quickly returned to normal.

"I've recovered…"

Finette was stunned for a while before he sorted out his chaotic memories and understood what was going on. He was immediately moved and bowed toward Han Xiao according to the records in the database.

"Your Excellency Black Star, thank you for your help. I thank you on behalf of the entire race!"

"If you want to thank someone, thank Risda. He has been pestering me for almost a hundred years because of this." Han Xiao waved his hands and did not mind.

"That's right, I really have to thank him…" Finette sighed. He then glared at Manison and said angrily," Mechanic Emperor! You captured my race and tampered with my thoughts. You used me as a tool for so many years. I will get back at you for this sooner or later! "

Back then, when the AI civilization was invaded by Manison, he stood out and led his people to fight back. He suffered a crushing defeat and was almost wiped out by Manison. The Virtual Purification would not erase his memories from all these years. It could almost be filmed as '300 Years a Slave'. If not for the fact that he could not beat Manison, he would have killed Manison on the spot.

Manison glanced at him and ignored him.

Han Xiao did not mind. Without his help, this ancestor of the AI civilization basically had no chance of taking revenge on Manison. He casually said, "At least you're free. Follow me, I'll bring you back."

Finette no longer bared his teeth at Manison and accepted Han Xiao's Mechanical Force. He turned into a stream of light and attached himself to Han Xiao's spaceship.

"Alright, nice deal. I'll give you the funds to rebuild the Indestructible Mechanical Troops. I'll be leaving first. You can continue staying at home."

Han Xiao waved at Manison and boarded the spaceship. When he turned around, he saw Manison standing at the dock and watching him leave.

Ding!

This time, the interface suddenly moved. Han Xiao opened it and saw that it was the notification of the completion of the [Reboot] mission.

Tens of billions of experience points, 2 Awakening Points, and a milestone [Ally of Artificial Intelligence Lives]. The introduction was that Virtual Technology would receive a certain level of improvement, and it would be easier to obtain the favor of artificial intelligence lives. The effect was basically an enhanced version of [Affable AI].

The more talents one had, the better. Of course, Han Xiao accepted it with a smile. This [Reboot] mission that had been on his list for many years also ended with the liberation of the AI civilization.

"Another mission cleared. Nice."

Han Xiao raised his brows. Although he did not have OCD, he still felt satisfied when he saw that the mission list was getting cleaner.

After using King to teleport back to his base, Han Xiao then released Finette and the other artificial intelligence lives to reunite with their other family members led by Risda. After a series of explanations, the other artificial intelligence lives expressed their gratitude to Han Xiao.

Risda and Finette both expressed that if Han Xiao had any requests in the future, they would never refuse. Han Xiao's interface now had the faction relationship with the AI civilization, which directly rose to [Reverence].

However, now that he had the skill [Life Transformation—Virtual], the AI civilization would not be of much use to him. He did not need these artificial intelligence lives to work for him.

After watching these artificial intelligence beings leave joyfully, Han Xiao finally stopped smiling.

"With my current strength and position, some things have become convenient for me to do. Maybe I will have a chance to complete the 'Ending the Darkness' mission…"

[Ending the Darkness] was the most difficult mission he had ever encountered. The EXP reward was a trillion, and the requirement was to end the life form trading industry in the galactic society.

Under normal circumstances, such a requirement would have been impossible to complete. However, the galactic structure had been severely impacted, and it was currently in a tense period. It maintained its wartime state, and its freedom was restricted. Most of the galactic residents were focused on taking refuge, and the circulation had plummeted by more than ninety percent. Black market trade had also almost stopped, and this was a period suitable for shuffling cards.

Life form trading was difficult to deal with, mainly due to its decentralization and secrecy. In this period of centralization, these two difficulties were greatly reduced. Due to the decrease in demand and the increase in the difficulty of collecting 'goods', most traffickers had no choice but to stop their business. Attacking life form trading at this time was undoubtedly much convenient and efficient.

Han Xiao calculated. With his current position, it was enough to move millions of times his own resources. If he shouted out the slogan of terminating the life form trading, all the civilizations would respond, and the three Universal Civilizations would not object. After all, it was not a bad thing to maintain order before the war.

Actually, he knew that the three Universal Civilizations had always had the idea of attacking the life form trading, but they had never tried to do so. Most of the social ills were like this, and they would only be taken seriously when someone important like him spoke up. Otherwise, as long as the problem did not affect some core areas, the priority would be postponed. The management department would not be willing to take the initiative to cause trouble without the approval of their superiors, and this was something that was difficult to avoid even in the galactic era.

However, even if he stopped the life form trading now, it would only last for a while. When the situation in the galaxy stabilized, this kind of business would rise again, and it would be very difficult to ban it forever. However, that was in the future. As long as there was a period when there was no life form trading in the entire galactic society, Han Xiao felt that the mission would be completed. Whether it rebounded in the future or not, it would not affect a mission that had already been completed.

"Anyway, other than harassing the troops of the World Tree at the frontline, the troops of the other organizations have nothing to do. We might as well drag them out to maintain order."

Han Xiao secretly recorded this matter on his plan and decided to take advantage of this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to complete this mission. After all, he did not have to supervise it personally, so it would not reduce his research time.

After solving the problem of the AI civilization, he focused his attention back on the upgrade of his machinery. Very soon, more than half a month had passed.

...

In the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods within the Arcane Church.

A large number of fleets protected the area where the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods was located, and a strict martial law was enforced. Above the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods, Wuornos' figure was floating in space, surrounded by four direct Beyond Grade As with hesitation on their faces.

"God's Chosen, are you sure this will help you advance to the Transcendent Grade?" a direct descendant could not help but ask.

Wuornos glanced at him and said calmly, "I'm not even nervous. Why are you nervous?"

The Arcane Church had prepared for almost a month and found helpers. They planned to help Wuornos advance today.

Wuornos was also constantly adjusting his state during this period. His stamina, spirit, and willpower had all reached their peak. In his opinion, the success rate of this Promotion was at least seventy percent.

"God's Chosen, are you ready?"

The Pope's voice came from the communicator.

It was worth paying attention to the matter of their pillar attempting to break through to a higher level. The Pope had already arranged the schedule a month in advance, freeing some time for the next few days to witness Wuornos' Promotion.

Whether or not they could compete with Black Star in terms of individual strength would depend on this!

"I can advance at any time. Have you set up the surroundings?" Wuornos replied calmly, his tone containing the confidence that he had accumulated for many years.

"All aura concealment devices have been activated. Try not to let the outside world sense the surge of cosmic energy. You can start now. I wish you success."

The Pope nodded and secretly wiped his sweat. He felt more nervous than the person in question.

Hearing this, Wuornos let out a breath and suddenly activated his energy, charging toward the gate that had stopped him for many years.

Boom!

The next moment, a shocking energy storm erupted with him as the center. An incomparably dazzling white light shone out from his body as if it had stolen all the colors in the world.

"It's here!"

The Pope widened his eyes in anticipation.

Chapter 1399: Stopping Losses

The four direct descendants looked at each other and followed Wuornos' instructions. They raised their hands and released their energy to merge into his body.

The situation in the area was akin to fuel being added to the fire. The intensity of the energy storm increased, and Wuornos, who was in the center, could no longer be seen. All that was left was a blinding light.

Wuornos' aura rose steadily, and the four of them could not help but be shaken.

"It seems to have worked!"

"As expected of the publicly acknowledged number one expert. Although Black Star beat him to it, he still managed to follow closely behind."

The four direct descendants communicated telepathically, surprised and delighted.

On the other side, the hearts of the Promotion and the other upper echelons, who were paying attention to this place, were in their throats. They felt as nervous as if their children were going to the examination venue. They stared at the scene without blinking, unwilling to miss a second.

They had all heard from Wuornos that there was a risk to this Promotion, so many of the upper echelons of the church were worried. Apart from anticipation, they were feeling anxious.

The existence of Wuornos was important for the Arcane Church to suppress the other two civilizations in terms of individual strength. If this pillar was sacrificed, it would be a heavy loss.

The radar of the fleet was buzzing nonstop, the energy detection value rapidly increasing.

This process lasted for a long time. Under everyone's eyes, the energy storm finally began to slowly shrink and was absorbed back into his body. Wuornos' aura rose to its peak and slowly became stable.

"Is he going to succeed?!"

Seeing this, the upper echelons of the church were overjoyed. They looked at this scene with hope.

"Looks like the first Transcendent Grade direct descendant is about to appear…"

The Pope was overjoyed, heaving a sigh of relief.

However, just as he thought that the Promotion was about to be completed, the shrinking energy storm suddenly stopped.

The next moment, with Wuornos at the center, violent energy exploded and the energy storm absorbed into his body was blown back, bursting out at an even faster speed.

The blinding light turned everyone's vision into a vast expanse of white. The loud sound seemed to shake everyone's hearts!

Boom!

The defense fleet around was forced to activate their shields and were filled with cracks not long after. The four Beyond Grade As closest to the center of the explosion were caught off guard and were blown away by the violent energy shockwave. They were like shrapnel shot out when a bomb explodes, tumbling far away in the universe.

"What's going on? Why did it suddenly explode?!

The Pope was present as a remote projection, so he was not affected. However, he was shocked and immediately became nervous.

Could it be that Wuornos failed his Promotion and was unfortunately sacrificed to be blown to smithereens?!

The church head immediately panicked and quickly ordered the four direct descendants and the surrounding fleets to prepare to save him.

Fortunately, the only wave of energy explosion did not cause any lasting damage to the surrounding fleets. When the energy was poured out, the bright light in the center slowly faded, and Wuornos was finally revealed.

He floated in midair, and golden blood continued to seep out from every pore of his body. When it landed in the freezing environment of the universe, it quickly solidified into golden crystals that were clear like snowflakes.

The energy reading of the radar dropped rapidly, and Wuornos' aura turned dispirited. He looked like he was heavily injured and was on the verge of collapse.

The spaceships around quickly surrounded him to save him, but Wuornos waved his hand to indicate that there was no need. He extended his finger and tapped lightly on the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods in the distance, seizing the God Embodiment of a statue through the air. He summoned the incarnation of a god wearing a gorgeous dress and separated it from the statue.

The avatar of this deity was clearly a female, but it had his face. Although his facial features had softened, he still looked like a male dressed as a female.

As soon as the God Embodiment appeared, it poured out a light that filled the sky and fused into Wuornos' body. Wuornos' injuries were quickly suppressed and did not continue to worsen. Although his aura was still weak, it slowly calmed down. It was obvious that the original form of this God was one involved in healing.

The Pope connected with Wuornos again and asked worriedly, "Are you alright?"

"It's just that my life force has been greatly depleted, I won't die." Wuornos coughed weakly after spitting out a mouthful of golden blood.

"You… failed your Promotion?" The church leader's tone was hesitant.

"Yes." Wuornos nodded weakly.

"Didn't you say there's a 70% chance of success? Why…"

Before the Pope could finish, Wuornos interrupted him.

"I did it on purpose. I could have advanced smoothly, but I stopped it at the last minute."

"What?!"

This answer was out of the church's expectations.

They had thought that he had failed because of an obstacle in his advancement, but it turned out that Wuornos did it on purpose. No wonder he looked so badly injured.

Originally, his cells had all been successfully sublimated, but he had forcefully interrupted the transformation and forced his genes to return to their original state after the Promotion. It was just like undergoing a transgender surgery and asking for it to be reverted halfway. The ending would be anything but good, and in Wuornos' case, it had greatly depleted his life force and damaged his cells.

"What do you mean?"

The Pope was extremely surprised. He knew that Wuornos would not do something like this for no reason.

"When I advanced, I realized that something was wrong. My life level did not undergo a huge transformation. It's too different from when Black Star advanced. There must be something wrong with my method!" Wuornos said with a deep voice.

"…So what you're saying is that this method of Promotion isn't right?" The Pope frowned.

"That's right. It seems like the method to advance to the Transcendent Grade is not as simple as it seems. Black Star must have hidden some important conditions."

Although Wuornos was heavily injured by the backlash, his eyes were still sharp.

In the beginning, he was very happy that his Promotion went smoothly, but the closer he got to the end, the more he felt that something was wrong.

Although he could indeed become stronger after this Promotion, the increase in his strength was far from what he had expected of a Transcendent. This made him suspicious.

He had a faint premonition that this Promotion would not allow him to step into the Transcendent Grade. If the Promotion was completed, he would have to wait until he had reached a new boundary in order to undergo the next Promotion. His potential had almost been squeezed dry, and he did not know how long it would take for him to obtain a new Promotion opportunity. He might not even have another chance.

If that was the case, his dream of reaching the Transcendent Grade would probably turn into smoke, and he would never be able to step into it.

After fighting for a while, Wuornos finally made up his mind. When he was halfway through his Promotion, he decided to cut his losses. He would rather risk his life to endure the backlash and end this Promotion.

Generally speaking, the advancement process of Supers was irreversible, but at Wuornos' level, he could already control everything perfectly. Interrupting the advancement and reversing the transformation was possible.

Of course, if a normal person did this, it might lead to the collapse of the genetic level, but the 'stable' property of the Void Spirit Kingdom's weapon was one of the reasons why Wuornos dared to take the risk. Even if his cells were damaged, the risk would be greatly reduced.

This way, although he would be heavily injured, he would be able to recover after resting for a while. This precious opportunity to advance would not be wasted, since he failed to break through to a higher level. This was not the first time he had experienced this.

If Han Xiao was there, he would have immediately understood the meaning behind Wuornos' actions. If Wuornos had succeeded in his normal Promotion, it would undoubtedly have been extremely difficult for him to reach the next Promotion at his current level.

If he took the initiative to fail the Promotion, the opportunity would not be wasted. According to the Promotion rules of this level, if he wanted to advance, he only needed to complete a new Promotion mission. However, those without the interface should not have the tough requirements of the Promotion mission. Maybe he just needed to train for some time and return to his peak state.

However, this method was very dangerous. If they were not careful and met with a malignant mutation, they would only end up harming future generations.

However, just the failure of the Promotion was not fatal. The malignant mutation during the Promotion was the fatal one. The chances of the two were independent. Most Beyond Grade As were the lucky ones, and Wuornos was one of the best. With his deep accumulation and good luck, he did not encounter the malignant mutation this time and was not killed by his actions.

At this moment, another spectating upper echelon could not help but say angrily,

"Black Star knew that this was something crucial, so he deliberately hid it. He might be waiting for you to fail your Promotion and use it to trick us once again. He's trying to indirectly kill an important member of the three Universal Civilizations so that we won't have the strength of a Transcendent and won't be able to threaten him!"

Wuornos shook his head. "It's not his fault. I was too impatient."

This was quite a close call, and he still had some lingering fear. He could not help but recall Black Star's brief warning after his Promotion, but he did not take it to heart. He knew that he could not blame anyone.

For Wuornos to be able to come this far, he had the resolution to not vent his anger on Han Xiao.

On the other side, the Pope was silent for a while before sighing.

"In that case, we still aren't able to break through to the Transcendent Grade. In the short term, Black Star is the only one in the universe who has such power. This isn't a good thing… Should we ask Black Star about the method to break through to the Beyond God level?"

"Forget it. Put yourself in his shoes and think about it. He either won't say it or will lie about it. If we go over and try to get information from him, not only will he take away some benefits, but we will also be played by him again." Wuornos waved his hand.

"You're right… Never mind, it's good to be alive. I'll think about it in the future."

The Pope had a helpless expression. He had high hopes for Wuornos, but now that his hopes had been dashed, he was naturally disappointed. However, it was not suitable for him to show it in front of Wuornos, who had escaped death.

This way, they would be on the same starting line as the other two civilizations, and their advantage of having intelligence would be gone.

"Sigh…"

The Pope of the Arcane Church sighed and did not say much. He only told Wuornos to have a good rest before deactivating the remote projection.

He had originally wanted to celebrate the birth of a Transcendent Grade direct descendant of the church. Since it was a failure, he had no interest in staying here. He still had to go back and attend to his multitude of daily matters.

The fleet of guards dispersed one after another, and the four direct descendants also took their leave. The military martial law in the area was lifted and it returned to being deserted.

Wuornos returned to the Temple of the Gods alone to lick his wounds. He recalled the process of Han Xiao's Promotion over and over again in his mind, muttering to himself,

"What am I missing…"

...

A few days later, in the head office of the three Universal Civilizations.

"…These are the specifics. I plan to invite the representatives of the various civilizations, including the three Universal Civilizations, as well as the various famous organizations, to hold a meeting regarding the peace in the galactic society. I want to discuss the elimination of human trade…"

In the room, Han Xiao's remote projection spoke.

He had taken some time today to find the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations and prepare to complete his quest of [Ending of Darkness]. The attitude of the three Universal Civilizations was very important.

"This is a good thing. In principle, we agree." Louis nodded. "However, the enemy has yet to be dealt with. Is it too early to be concerned about this?"

"It will be too late by the time the war is over. There's no harm in trying to maintain order before the war. Anyway, many troops are on standby now, so it's good to pull them out," Han Xiao said casually.

Louis pondered for a few seconds before turning to look at the other two. "What do you guys think?"

"I have no objections."

"Me neither."

Marbruce and the Pope nodded and exchanged looks.

They were rather curious as to why Black Star would do something so 'unimportant' at this time. After analyzing it, they all felt that this was most likely Black Star trying to gain public reputation. If this was done, his reputation would definitely increase greatly.

It was not that the three of them could not accept it. At the very least, Black Star had this requirement, which meant that he was confident in this war. Furthermore, due to many factors, they could not stop Black Star from increasing his reputation.

"Since that's the case, I'll send a unified invitation to the various large organizations in the name of the association and the three Universal Civilizations."

Han Xiao nodded. This matter required many organizations to work together. He planned to hold a meeting this time and invite all the organizations in the universe to participate.

Having completed his mission, Han Xiao was in a much better mood. He turned to look at the Pope and suddenly thought of something.

"By the way, has Wuornos tried to advance?"

The corners of the Pope's eyes twitched. "Why do you care?"

"From the looks of it, you must have tried." Han Xiao raised his brows and said playfully, "He failed, right? Is he still there?"

The Pope's mood immediately turned sour. He only felt that this was a joke directed at him and did not want to speak.

"Well, it seems like he's not dead. Otherwise, you wouldn't be so quiet. However, I did persuade Wuornos not to rush to advance. It's his business if he doesn't listen, not mine."

Han Xiao did not mind and said with a mocking tone.

"…He's still alive. He only stopped his Promotion and suffered some backlash. He'll be fine after recovering for a while." The Pope's face darkened. This was not a secret at all. With Han Xiao's intelligence network, it would not take long to find out about this. It might even be Wuornos who tells him the truth himself.

Seeing this, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

If Wuornos had gone through an ordinary Promotion, he would not have the qualifications to break through to the Transcendent Grade for a very long time. However, if he only failed the Promotion and did not die, there was still a chance. In fact, he did not care whether it was the former or the latter.

If it was the former, Wuornos would no longer be a threat to him. If it was the latter, it meant that Wuornos still had a chance to become a Transcendent. He would not lose anything anyway, since the method of advancement would still be monopolized by himself.

However, he actually took the initiative to stop his Promotion. That was quite bold…

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and nodded.

It seemed like such a small scheme would not allow Wuornos to fail so easily. After all, he was a big shot who had stood at the peak of his individual strength for so many years. He definitely had substance.

He did not have any enmity with Wuornos to begin with, and he had no intention of targeting him. However, he did not persuade Wuornos to temporarily give up his Promotion mission, so he did not care about this result.

However, seeing this guy suffer because he tried to imitate his actions left Han Xiao gloating.

Heh, trying to learn from me? You must be joking!

Chapter 1400: Issuing a Call for Action

The Arcane Church did not deliberately block the news. The news of Wuornos' failure to advance quickly spread among the upper echelons. The Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and many Beyond Grade As all heard about this, and their reactions were all different. Some were surprised, some were regretful, and many were gloating.

Originally, after Black Star opened up the Transcendent Grade, many Beyond Grade As also had thoughts of advancing, but with Wuornos' example, many of them suppressed their desires.

Even Wuornos had failed. It was better to wait and see.

Because of this, many Beyond Grade As also confirmed that Black Star was the only Transcendent for the time being and no one else had the ability to charge at this level yet. His position could not be shaken, which made them even more interested in the Promotion method that Black Star had yet to reveal.

However, these things were only circulated in the upper echelons, and the people of the galactic society knew nothing about it. They were still living in a tight wartime life, filled with anxiety.

However, a few days later, a piece of news from the Black Star Army quickly spread throughout the galactic society and attracted the attention of countless galactic residents.

Black Star, who had kept a low profile for a period of time, suddenly made a big move. He publicly sent out an invitation in the name of the Beyond Grade A Association and the three Universal Civilizations, targeting the various organizations in the entire universe. There were civilizations and civil organizations, and their numbers were shocking, covering almost all areas.

Black Star said in the invitation that he was going to hold a meeting and was inviting the representatives of the various organizations to attend. They would discuss the development prospects of the explored universe and the disadvantages of life form trading.

Currently, Han Xiao's every move was being paid attention to by the galactic residents and the various organizations. His actions immediately caused a wave of discussion. Countless people were puzzled by this and began to guess Black Star's intentions.

The foreign enemies were closing in and the war situation was looking bad. Many people did not understand why Black Star would emphasize the problem of life form trading at this time.

Wasn't war the most important thing right now? Even if they had to calm the internal state before dealing with external threats, it did not seem to have much to do with life form trading.

Furthermore, a conference of this level included almost all the famous organizations in the universe, so it should be led by the three Universal Civilizations. Why was Black Star the one leading it? Even the meeting location was in the Black Star Army's territory.

Many people could not help but think… does this mean that Black Star has the same authority as the three Universal Civilizations ‽

While they were puzzled, the various large organizations still gave face. All the civilizations responded publicly and expressed that they would accept the invitation to attend the meeting. Countless private organizations also expressed their honor to receive Black Star's invitation.

For a moment, the galactic society that had been silent for a long time was in turmoil. It felt like Black Star was the leader of the galactic society.

With Han Xiao's current position, the organizations that wanted to survive in the galactic society would not dare to not give him face.

Under everyone's attention, the days passed, and the day of the meeting arrived.

Outside the Black Star Palace, a large venue floated in the middle of the fortress like a flat top. Its silver-gray exterior reflected the light of the Fixed Star.

Streams of light gathered from all directions and formed light dragons. Spaceships with the emblems of different organizations drove into the port one after another, and representatives of various shapes and sizes walked down.

The platform at the dock was already packed with people. Countless reception robots walked through the area, leading the way for the representatives of different organizations. Some organizations that were too far away used remote projections, and there were also quite a number of organizations that personally sent their members to give Black Star face.

"So many people have come…"

The Purple Crystal Civilization's diplomatic envoys alighted from the spaceship, and Ralph, who was in the lead, smiled as he looked at the crowded scene before him.

A young diplomat beside him curiously approached and whispered,

"Old leader, I heard you had a good relationship with Black Star?"

"It's not too bad, but I haven't seen him in a long time… After so many years, he's doing pretty well. We're no longer on the same level."

A complicated look flashed across Ralph's eyes. He waved his hands and sighed.

During the secret war of the Crimson Tide, the Black Star Army, as one of the mercenaries, had accepted the Purple Crystal Civilization's invitation to fight the Klent Kingdom and Bloodshed Land's invasion together. Back then, he had been the commander of Section Zero of the Secret Service and had been in charge of contacting Black Star for many years.

Because of this, Purple Crystal had let Ralph lead the team to participate in this meeting. It had only been a few decades, but he was already old and about to retire. The power in his hands was about to end, but Black Star, who had worked with him back then, was becoming more and more active. He had gone from being a small mercenary to an existence that the Purple Crystal Civilization could not hope to reach. This difference made him feel complicated.

At this moment, a discordant voice suddenly sounded from the side.

"Isn't this the representative of the Purple Crystal Civilization? To be able to meet all of you here."

The Purple Crystal Civilization's diplomatic envoys turned around and saw a group of people disembarking from a spaceship. It was the Klent Kingdom's diplomatic envoys.

The two forces still did not get along after the secret war ended and there were many grudges between them. Now that the representatives of both sides had met, they immediately glared at each other as if they could not stand each other's sight.

"Hmph, so you're Klent's emissary." Ralph glanced at him and said calmly, "It's been a few decades, but you guys are still the same. You guys hate Black Star, but you don't dare refuse the invitation. I advise you to keep a low profile and be good kids in Black Star's territory. Don't cause trouble."

Veins popped up on the Klent emissary's forehead. Just as he was about to retaliate, he saw the reception robot of the Black Star Army fly over. He quickly shut his mouth and only dared to look at Ralph with hatred.

Ralph had been in a high position for many years and had interacted with Klent countless times. He did not care about a young emissary at all. He looked around at the different delegations.

Compared to the civilizations' diplomatic envoys, the number of delegations from private organizations in the various industries was higher by tens of thousands of times. Most of them were representatives of various private organizations, and many of them had cautious expressions. Clearly, this was their first time participating in an event of this scale, so they pretended to be calm and did not want to show fear.

"With just an invitation, almost all the organizations in the entire universe have come… Black Star's position is truly unparalleled."

What is meant by dominating the universe? This is called dominating the universe…

Ralph sighed and followed the reception robot into the venue.

At this moment, countless representatives were already seated in the venue. They were whispering to each other, and their faces were all different. It was like a galactic species exhibition. The news media were also present, adjusting equipment and preparing to broadcast the meeting.

The Beyond Grade As that were rarely seen were all seated in the front, showing their backs and receiving the attention of the delegations. The emissaries of the various advanced civilizations and important private organizations were also waiting in the core area.

Almost all the famous organizations had arrived. It was a grand occasion!

After waiting for a while, all the representatives took their seats and the doors slowly closed.

The venue slowly fell silent.

At this moment, a figure walked out from the shadows on the stage. He appeared in everyone's sight and immediately attracted everyone's attention.

Han Xiao walked up to the podium and looked around at the endless seats. He smiled and said slowly,

"Thank you for accepting my invitation to participate in this meeting. On behalf of the Beyond Grade A Association and the three Universal Civilizations, I would like to welcome all of you here. The main purpose of this meeting is to discuss the future of the galactic society."

Pa pa pa!

Everyone clapped and perked up their ears, curious about Black Star's intentions.

Han Xiao raised his hand and said solemnly,

"Since the galactic era began, our civilization has created countless glorious achievements in various fields. The galactic society is extremely prosperous, but at the same time, it has accumulated countless evils. Life form trading is a problem that runs through history.

The obedience of others is one of the core pillars of power, so enslaving them is an eternal desire. The demand brings the market, and no matter how hard we strike, the life form trading will never be destroyed. After failing again and again, we got used to it, tolerated it, and finally convinced ourselves that it was an unsolvable problem, giving up the idea of completely solving it.

However, now that the situation in the galaxy has changed, our control over the various Star Fields has been highly focused. This is a chance for us to clean up the root. Therefore, I hope to obtain your help to solve the evil of the life form trading."

Hearing this, the representatives were stunned and looked at each other.

They had thought that Black Star had other plans for the meeting and that the life form trading was just a reason. They did not expect Black Star to really want to solve this problem.

"This…"

Everyone was confused.

It seemed like the existence of the life form trading would not affect Black Star at all, right? Was there a need to call all of them over just for this?

What was Black Star planning? What benefit did such a thankless task bring him?

If it was just to increase his reputation, there were plenty of ways. Why did he have to choose this troublesome path?

On the stage, Han Xiao took in everyone's confused expressions and let out a deep breath.

"I know. You might think that the interstellar life form trading has nothing to do with me, and you're wondering what benefits I can get from it… To be honest, with my position, whether the life form trading exists or not doesn't affect my interests, but why did I hold a meeting for this?

Everyone, although the progress of the era is mainly driven by a small number of people, the main body of the world is still the most ordinary galactic citizen. It is because of their existence that our universe is so prosperous and we have the name of civilization.

Over the years, the life form trading has caused countless tragedies. Although it cannot threaten us, we should not turn a blind eye to it. We are already used to standing on high ground, but no matter how high we stand, we have to lower our heads at the right time and look at the dark corners and the situation of ordinary people.

The purpose of our existence is not only for ourselves, but also to promote the development of the world. We have the ability to make the galactic society better and create a better world."

The moment he said that, many of the people present trembled, as though they did not expect Black Star to say such a thing.

For a moment, everyone was stunned. They only felt that Han Xiao seemed to be emitting the light of humanity.

Some were overwhelmed with emotions, some admired, some scoffed, and some were suspicious.

Is Black Star serious?

Is this a noble act of love, or is he trying to leave his name in history?

After a moment of silence, an emissary of a Super Star Cluster Civilization suddenly spoke.

"The current war situation is still very serious. Isn't it too early to mention this? If we can't chase away the foreign enemies, everything will be wasted."

Han Xiao only glanced at him and said calmly, "It's precisely because we have the confidence to win this war that we don't want to let go of this opportunity to get rid of the evils. Everything is for the future."

The moment he said that, everyone's spirits were lifted.

Black Star's tone was very calm, but it made most of the people present excited.

Currently, all the organizations in the universe were worried about where the war would end up. Now that a big shot like Black Star had come out to express his stand, whether it was the truth or consolation, it was a boost to their morale.

Especially when they thought of Black Star's goal this time, they felt a strong sense of confidence. If he did not have hope for the future, why would he go through so much trouble to deal with the problems of the galactic society? Wasn't this all to win the governing power after the war?

Various thoughts flashed through their minds.

Suddenly, a representative from a private organization stood up and said loudly, "Your Excellency Black Star, you cherish all living beings. We admire your character and are willing to serve you!"

All of a sudden, the representatives of the various organizations seemed to have woken up from a dream. They all expressed their opinions enthusiastically, and the venue instantly became lively.

Although Black Star's words were nice, it was unrealistic for him to convince the people with vested interests with just a few words. However, many organizations agreed to cooperate because of Black Star.

The reason for this was mainly because Black Star had used his reputation to gather everyone and had opened up the communication barrier between them. In addition, he had enough public appeal, so the matter was completed. Had this speech been given by someone else not important enough, these forces would not have taken action even if they were touched.

Everyone knew the truth. It did not matter if it was nice or not. What mattered was who said it.

Many organizations were willing to help Han Xiao achieve this goal. On one hand, it was politically correct, and on the other hand, it was a grand event. There was no need to let go of this opportunity to increase their reputation. Finally, they also did this due to some respect for Han Xiao.

The scene was also broadcasted by countless media outlets and was witnessed by countless galactic residents.

"Oh my god…"

"What is Black Star doing!"

Countless galactic residents were dumbfounded.

Black Star's declaration completely exceeded the expectations of many people. They did not expect Black Star to have such a huge goal in mind.

They did not know what was going on behind the scenes. All they saw was the surface.

Seeing that Black Star was able to pull so many organizations to terminate the life form trading, his influence was comparable to the three Universal Civilizations.

In the eyes of the galactic residents, Han Xiao's image became even larger, and his entire body was glowing. He had become the number one person in the entire explored universe.

"Creating a better galactic society… Black Star actually has such a spirit…"

"Well said. This world should become more beautiful."

While countless people were shocked, they could not help but feel touched. They did not expect Black Star to still care about ordinary people like them.

The life form trafficking was like a deep nightmare, enough to wake any ordinary person up in the middle of the night.

There were millions of races in the Galaxy, and the anomalies would always arouse curiosity. No one could guarantee that they would never become prey in the eyes of others.

In their eyes, regardless of whether Black Star's motive was pure or not, as long as he stood up and did it, he would be a great man worthy of respect.

If not for Black Star, today's event would have never happened.

The news kept broadcasting, leaving a deep impression in the hearts of more and more galactic residents. Han Xiao's reputation was also brought to an unprecedented height.

"The existence of someone like Black Star might really make the world better…"

This thought appeared in the minds of the galactic residents one after another.

Some even felt that letting Black Star rule the galactic society did not seem too bad…

Chapter 1401: You'll have to pay for it sooner or later

Somewhere in the Sea of Star Spirits, a large starship slowly sailed through the universe.

In the exquisitely decorated captain's cabin, Carlozo was leaning lazily on the soft and comfortable captain's chair, his legs crossed on the table. One arm was leaning on the armrest, holding an expensive bottle of fine hard liquor which he was swinging around, There was a thick cigar in his mouth, burning with green smoke while a virtual screen floated in front of him, playing an entertainment program.

Carlozo had rough brown skin like a lizard. His facial features were similar to a human's, but the gap between his eyes was quite large and his jaw was protruding, similar to that of a beastman. In addition, one of his eyes was missing, and the empty eye socket was exposed as a black hole just like that. It was like a wound left by an energy gun, lending him a fierce aura.

He looked very rough on the outside, but he was wearing an exquisite and complicated noble-style dress that seemed to have been carefully ironed without many creases. This was accompanied by a small, noble-style round hat on his head, covering his sparse and messy yellow hair. Only a few locks of hair hung down from the gaps of the hat, giving people a strong visual contrast.

While the slave trade was mostly held in the galactic black market, there existed an independent ecosystem that formed a secret trade chain. Because this industry was unsuitable for the public's eyes, any seller of a certain size rarely acted in the name of an organization. They usually gave themselves a code name and used this name to make friends with customers, forming a trade network around their identity.

As for Calozo, he was a reputable seller of this secret trade, nicknamed 'Lord'. He had been in the industry for many years and had outstanding results. His business had even crossed several Star Clusters, so it would not be an exaggeration to say that he was a slave-trading giant in the Sea of Star Spirits.

Gulp…

Carlozo took a sip of the wine, and the bright red liquid flowed out from his lips and slid down his chin. He ignored the sounds of his subordinates playing outside the cabin, puffing on his cigar as he increased the volume of the virtual screen. He kept changing the channels with hand gestures, looking through one program after another with boredom.

At this moment, an encrypted communication interface suddenly popped up on the virtual screen, and a number marked 'Buyer 178' appeared.

Carlozo's eyes flashed. He paused the show and picked up the call.

A black shadow with no specific appearance appeared on the screen and gave a string of code numbers. Carlozo also replied with a string of numbers and they conversed like this for a few sentences to confirm that there was no problem with their identities.

After checking the code, Buyer 178 went straight to the point.

"Lord, did you get the goods I ordered last time?"

Carlozo took out a notebook and flipped through it. "Sorry, we haven't gotten the goods yet."

"How long has it been? It's just a batch of Silver Spirits. You weren't this slow in the past. My master is already impatient from waiting," Buyer 178 sounded unhappy.

Carlozo shook his head. "The environment is different now. As you know, due to the war, the entire universe has been under martial law for the past three years. A large number of races have gathered in the Central Galaxy to take refuge, causing our business to reduce by ninety percent. It's not as easy to obtain goods anymore."

All along, the slave trade black market hidden under the deep sea of the galactic society had been very prosperous, but with the outbreak of the World Tree War, this industry had fallen into winter.

Generally speaking, war should be able to promote the slavery trade, but the current war did not break out on the mainland. In order to prepare for war, the three Universal Civilizations imposed high-pressure restrictions on the various Star Fields. With the large number of people taking refuge, the population of the galactic residents plummeted. This was equivalent to cutting off the supply of many slave traffickers.

The majority of the people captured by the slave traffickers were ordinary galactic residents. They were usually lone galactic travelers, either swindling tourists or buying captives from the galactic pirates. They rarely attacked passing spaceships and it was even harder for them to land on a colonial planet to capture people. They did not have such armed forces.

Due to the restrictions of the three Universal Civilizations, it had been a long time since Carlozo had opened his 'store', and this business was getting more and more difficult.

"Although I can't get the Silvers here, there are still some other goods. Do you want to take a look at the list?" asked Carlozo.

"Forget it, forget it. I'll find someone else."

Buyer 178 went offline.

Carlozo curled his lips and did not mind.

Although this deal fell through, he did not feel any regret.

Because of the war, Calozo had already made up his mind not to purchase any more goods. He only wanted to clear his inventory and wash his hands off this business.

As for whether or not he could completely free himself, Carlozo was not worried.

Sellers who had been operating for a long time all had a set of survival rules. They paid attention to their identity and kept it a secret. Most of the time, they only worked with regular customers and maintained good relationships with some armed organizations. Some powerful clients could even provide them with assistance, so they were able to survive in the underworld… As long as they kept a low profile and did not expose themselves or provoke any big shots, no one would care about them. They could leave after making a fortune. It was very safe.

Carlozo closed the communication interface and continued to switch channels. He casually scrolled through the programs, but his mind was not in it. He was immersed in the excitement of looking forward to the future.

"When this batch of stocks is cleared, I can retire…"

Carlozo was in a good mood.

The money he had earned over the years was enough for him to live a carefree life for a few lifetimes. As long as he could retire successfully, he would be able to change his appearance and enjoy his life with the wealth he had accumulated. There were too many such examples in this industry. It could be said that this was every slave trader's dream, and it was Carlozo's goal.

The thought of his beautiful life finally waving at him after working so hard for so many years made him excited.

However, at this moment, he swiped to a news channel that was broadcasting Black Star's conference.

Carlozo had also paid attention to the recent invitation issued, and he could not help but pause there.

His eyes grew wider and wider, and his body started to tremble uncontrollably. A thick sense of fear gradually filled his face, and a chill ran down his spine.

Looking at the countless large organizations in the image responding to Han Xiao's call, Carlozo panicked. His mind went blank, and he could not help but recall a sentence that he had once scoffed at…

If you come out to play, you have to pay the price sooner or later!

Crack!

The subordinates who were playing cards loudly in the cabin suddenly heard the sound of things being smashed frequently from the captain's cabin. Just from the sound of it, they could almost imagine the hysterical look on his face, like a trapped beast in despair.

...

Endless Nebulae, a certain galactic free city.

A luxurious mansion sat in a scenic area surrounded by green trees and a clear lake. Such a special area existed in the highly man-made galactic capital city. Clearly, the people living there had a lot of influence.

In the spacious living room, a man in a sleeping robe was sitting on the sofa. A few female Elven creatures were lying on the floor beside him. Their heads were lowered, jaws on the ground, and they had a collar tied around their necks which was connected to a pillar, like leashed pets.

In front of them was a large virtual screen playing a show. The man was eating breakfast while looking up at the screen. He would stroke the back of the elven lady from time to time—which was covered in purple bruises—as if he was simply petting her.

The elven lady subconsciously shrank back, but her eyes were still like a pool of stagnant water. She lifelessly looked at the virtual screen in front of her, like a zombie whose soul had been sucked out.

At this time, the man changed channels and saw the news recording of the Black Star Conference.

After looking at it for a while, he sneered, his face appearing as though he did not give two hoots about it,

"This Black Star, he's always so busy. He should go fight the enemies if he's bored. That's his responsibility. What's the point of worrying about population trade? Does he think he's the leader of the galactic society? Pfft, what the hell."

As soon as he said that, the bodies of a few elven women lying on the ground suddenly trembled, and their dead eyes suddenly regained a bit of life.

Ever since they were captured by the slave traffickers and sold, their lives were only left with darkness. They were like stagnant water without any life, thinking that they would be like this for the rest of their lives.

However, at this moment, Black Star was like a ray of light piercing through the darkness, piercing into their despairing hearts and waking up their shattered personalities.

The few of them looked at Black Star on the screen and could not help but feel hopeful.

Will someone really save us…

The man in the robe noticed the looks of his pets and frowned.

"Hmm? What kind of look is that?"

As he spoke, the man in the robe glanced at Black Star on the screen and suddenly felt a surge of anger. He picked up a short prismatic whip from the side and threw it out.

"It seems like I haven't trained you guys enough. Are you still thinking of escaping? Why, did you think that Black Star can save you after seeing the news? If so, keep an eye on him and see if he can save you guys now."

The few female elves were so frightened that their bodies stiffened. They lay on the ground and trembled nonstop, but they did not dare to dodge or beg for mercy. If these 'pets' opened their mouths to speak without the permission of the man, it would only lead to worse torture.

The man in the sleeping robe had a dark expression on his face. He raised his whip and looked like he was about to hit one of them.

However, at this moment, the mansion's door exploded!

Bang!

Fragments flew everywhere, and the wall was covered in dust.

The man in the robe was shocked. He turned around and saw a group of people walking in. They were wearing familiar uniforms. It was the security patrol team of this galactic city.

Upon seeing who it was, the man in the robe immediately relaxed. He then roared in rage.

"What are you doing?! How dare you barge into my house?! Do you want to die?!"

The captain walked out and showed his electronic arrest warrant. He said coldly, "Your Excellency Anhuso, we have received a reliable report that you have broken the law by raising a galactic resident as a pet. Please come with us."

The man in the robe opened his eyes wide in disbelief and pointed at himself in surprise. "Arrest me over such a small matter? Do you know who I am?"

"You have violated the Planetary Universal Law's life form trading prohibition." The captain remained expressionless.

"If you capture me, can you bear the responsibility? Go back and ask the feudal lord of this free planet, does he still want the rights to operate his planet?"

The man only found it ridiculous and did not know whether to laugh or cry.

With his identity and background, such a crime was a joke. He had raised many galactic species as pets, and no one had ever dared to hold him responsible for it.

He did not expect such a low-level police officer to dare challenge him. Such a small character did not even have the right to talk to him in normal times.

"Please cooperate with us." The captain frowned.

"What's your serial number? Do you believe that I will strip you of your clothes tomorrow?!" The man in the robe was so angry that he laughed. He walked up, grabbed the captain's clothes, and looked down at the serial number on his badge.

Without any hesitation, the captain pushed the man away and said in a deep voice, "If you continue to refuse arrest, we will resort to violence."

The man in the sleeping robe staggered and widened his eyes in disbelief. He did not expect the person in front of him to attack him.

His expression immediately turned extremely gloomy. He picked up the communicator from the table and called the number of the city lord of the planet. He pointed at the captain of the security team and said angrily, "Alright, just you wait. I'll see who can take me away today!"

Very soon, the call connected.

"Yo, isn't this His Excellency Anhuso? Why are you suddenly in the mood to look for me?" The Planet Lord appeared on the screen with a polite smile.

The man in the robe immediately vented his anger on the planet's feudal lord. He sneered and said, "Alright, your people have grown up. They dare to barge into my house, capture me, and even attack me. If you don't give me a satisfactory answer today, your planet's management rights will be invalidated!"

"Aiya, why are you so angry? What's going on?" The planet lord was surprised.

"Heh, ask your people."

The man in the robe stuffed the communicator into the captain's hands and took two steps back with a look of anticipation.

The captain of the security team was not afraid at all. He picked up his communicator and reported the situation regarding the few elven ladies.

After hearing, the Planet Lord calmly spoke out.

"I see… Captain, what's your name?"

"Bell," the captain replied calmly.

"Is the tip reliable?"

"The evidence is all present."

Hearing this, the planet lord nodded and slowly said,

"Then what are you waiting for? Capture this guy. If he refuses to be arrested, don't bring him back. Just shoot him on the spot."

As soon as he said that, the man in the robe was stunned. He thought he had heard incorrectly.

Under normal circumstances, shouldn't he have ordered the police officers to retreat before firing them to appease his anger? This had always been the case in the past. Why was it different today?

"What do you mean?" The man was stunned.

The Planet Lord shrugged. "I should have expressed it very accurately. You broke the law, so of course you have to be arrested."

"…Are you crazy?" The man in the robe widened his eyes. "Have you forgotten who I am?"

"I know that you have a very strong background…" The feudal lord suddenly changed the topic and stopped pretending. "But so what? It is His Excellency Black Star's will to not allow population trade. We are working for Black Star. Who do you think you are?"

"You…"

The man in the nightgown was stunned, and his entire body began to tremble.

It was not fear, but uncontrollable rage.

Ever since he was born, no one had dared to speak to him like this!

However, before he could throw a tantrum, Bell suddenly pulled out his gun and pulled the trigger.

Bang!

A laser beam flashed past, and the man's head exploded, spilling burnt flesh all over the ground.

The headless corpse seemed to be stunned on the spot. It swayed for a while before collapsing to the ground. Its nerves that were not completely dead were still twitching.

Seeing this, the planet lord revealed an inexplicable smile.

Without his secret instructions, the security team would not have acted so boldly.

"This person has been refused many times. Our team has received orders from our superiors to kill him on the spot!"

Bell put away the gun with a cold face and glanced at the headless corpse, his eyes filled with disdain

"Ptui, scum."

...

It had been a few days since countless organizations expressed their stance in the conference held by Black Star. The chain reaction caused by this conference had already begun.

The resources of more than half of the galactic society were activated by Han Xiao. The organizations of the various Star Fields followed the consensus of the meeting and began cleaning up the slave trade within the territory.

The Beyond Grade A Association controlled the galactic black market and started from the core. They pulled out many slave trade channels and uprooted them.

It was not just the participating organizations, the other organizations that did not attend also joined in.

They were not looking out for Han Xiao's face, but seeing that so many large organizations had responded, some small organizations tried to make use of the opportunity of attacking the slave trade to connect with the large local organizations.

The anti-slave trafficking operation in the entire universe was carried out in full swing. As a large number of organizations worked together, batch after batch of slaves was rescued, groups of human traffickers were killed, and buyers were captured one after another. This included ex-slave sellers who had retired and started anew. Their real identities were tracked through the black market by the intelligence department, and they were pursued again.

The cooperation of so many organizations was a rare sight. It was like a highly efficient machine. The efficiency made countless galactic residents exclaim at Black Star's terrifying appeal.

This information was naturally transmitted to the many Calamity Grades in the training base.

...

Training base, dormitory lounge.

The virtual screen was showing the results of regional attacks on slave trade. Jotina looked at the screen with excitement.

"You actually have the same dream as me…"

Jotina clenched her fists tightly.

As the daughter of the Beast Ancestor, she hated slave trafficking to the extreme. Her dream of ending the slave trafficking in the entire universe was hidden in her heart and she had never told anyone about it.

However, she did not expect Black Star to have the same thoughts as her!

The difference was that to her, it was just a distant dream; but to Black Star, this was a goal within reach.

"Black Star… we are indeed destined partners!"

Jotina's breathing was heavy, and her heart was in turmoil. At this moment, she only wanted to give birth to a nest of monkeys for Black Star.

Over the past few decades, her admiration for Han Xiao had always remained the same, and it was even stronger now.

'The rumors kept saying that Black Star and the Dragon Emperor were a couple, but so what? I won't give up!'

'So what if the Dragon Emperor is a Beyond Grade A? When I work hard to reach that level, I will be able to compete with you on equal grounds!'

Jotina's eyes were filled with a fighting spirit.

"Black Star, wait for me! The Dragon Emperor is not worthy of you. I will definitely snatch you from her!"

Chapter 1402: Shadow of Arrival

The entire explored universe had never dealt such a heavy blow to the life form trading. Regardless of whether it was the underworld or the surface, the life form traffickers no longer had a place to stay. The protective umbrella that they once relied upon, avoided them. Be it the buyers or sellers, they were all silent. Many individuals or organizations that were once involved in the life form trading were investigated, and according to the severity and size of the organization, they were fined, imprisoned, or sentenced to death. The end of days had arrived for countless life form traffickers.

Of course, most people would not just stand there and do nothing. Resistance existed naturally, and the complicated situation of the life form trading ecosystem was thus exposed to the world. Sellers might have nowhere to run, but many buyers had power and influence and were scattered in various industries like stubborn stains in the cracks.

Many organizations were willing to exterminate the traffickers, but for a large number of buyers, it was impossible to clean up all of them, and many cooperative organizations would not agree. After all, the implications were too wide, and it would easily change the nature of the operation. Their own dark history could also be dug out, and there were many considerations.

Han Xiao did not insist on this. He only wanted to kill all the sellers. Even if there were still buyers who did not give up, they would not be able to find the supply for a long time. They could only think about it.

If any bold opportunists felt that the life form trading market would be emptied out because of this and took the risk to try to develop private customers in a one-on-one manner, the advanced civilizations that supervised the network were not just for show. The search program created by him, the Legendary Mechanic, was not to be trifled with.

The association and the advanced civilizations worked together to come up with a more detailed method of handling the matter. There were some new legal regulations, but Han Xiao did not need to involve himself in this.

As the chain links of life form trading were removed one after another, Han Xiao received more and more support from the galactic residents. However, although ending the life form trading gave him a huge reputation, he also offended many people.

Black Star Palace, private workshop.

Han Xiao looked through the feedback that the intelligence department had gathered over the past few days with a strange look on his face.

"Heh, the commotion is even bigger than I expected. This kind of thing really doesn't benefit me much. These people with power and influence, no matter how respectful they appear on the surface, most of them think that I'm meddling in other people's business. I don't know how many of them secretly view me as an enemy."

The buyers who had the ability to raise slaves and were not pursued were obviously not ordinary people. He had deprived them of their 'hobbies'. Even if these people did not dare to express their dissatisfaction, they did not have a good impression of him. If there was a day when they could hit him when he was down, they would not mind stepping on him.

"If not for my individual strength, I would definitely not have a good ending…"

Han Xiao curled his lips.

It was a pity that his fist was big enough. Even if these people disliked him, they could not do anything to him.

Han Xiao did not mind if this created grievances.

He opened the interface and looked at the mission list. [Ending the Darkness] was already displayed as completed, which surprised him.

"It was completed just like that. The operation is not over yet."

Han Xiao stroked his chin thoughtfully.

Right now, no one dared to take the risk. The traffickers who had yet to be caught had no intention of doing business. They were all focused on fleeing, and their trade chain was broken.

In a sense, the interstellar life form trading had indeed been temporarily terminated. As long as the mission was completed before it re-emerged, it should be enough.

"If that's the case, the mission evaluation is quite lenient. The difficulty is within an acceptable range."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

If the mission was to ensure that there would never be any life form trafficking in the galaxy, then not to mention a trillion experience points, he felt that even ten trillion or one hundred trillion experience points might not be enough.

This request was also very difficult. The reason it seemed simple was that he had accumulated a sufficiently high position. There were very few organizations in the entire galactic society that had his appeal, and anyone else would not have been able to do it.

Han Xiao did not want to drag it out any longer and completed the mission.

[Ending the Darkness] Completed!

You have received 1 Trillion EXP, 15 Random Rewards, and 3 Blank Character Summon Cards.

You have received the milestone [Slave Liberator]!

Slave Liberator: Your relationship with all Lawful Factions will forever be fixed at [Reverence].

You have received 3 Universe Legendary Points.

Universe Legendary Point: [Light of Justice]—You tore up the darkness of life form trading and brought the light of justice to this Galaxy. Countless people worship you as their idol.

Universe Legendary Point: [Deeds of a Great Man]—Your actions to end the life form trading will become a monumental work of humanitarianism. It will be engraved in history and will be written in textbooks.

Universal Legendary Point: [Freedom Leader]—You have saved countless despairing people and removed their shackles. Your existence represents noble freedom in the eyes of those who are saved.

"Heh, it's done."

Han Xiao relaxed and checked his gains.

The 1 trillion experience reward was mainly a reflection of the difficulty. To him, it was not a lot, but it was still quite a fortune.

Experience was still useful to him now. Although he had reached the Transcendent Grade, his total level still had not reached the upper limit. However, the cost of leveling up was even more ridiculous. He could not level up even with a trillion experience. It was simply a bottomless pit.

In his eyes, the most practical reward was still the fifteen Random Reward opportunities and five Blank Character Summon Cards… especially the latter, which allowed him to get other's abilities again.

As for the effect of the [Slave Liberator] milestone, it would have been very useful in the past. However, with his current position, even without this milestone, he could have the same effect.

However, the merits this time could be considered as a stronger amulet, standing on the moral high ground. If the three Universal Civilizations wanted to target him again in the future, the backlash would be even worse.

Furthermore, this was also a huge Political Asset. If he had any thoughts about the position of the ruler of the galactic society one day, there might be some people who would welcome the great Black Star to Central Galaxy…

"Cough cough…"

Han Xiao coughed dryly and cleared his thoughts. He tapped on the table and pondered.

He made use of his influence to gather all the organizations in the universe to work together to end the life form trading. Of course, he could not stop this movement now, as that would damage his prestige. Although the mission was completed, it was not suitable for him to stop immediately. He had to continue.

"That's good too. Anyway, it's not a bad thing. I'll see this to the end."

Han Xiao calmed himself down and opened the forums. He realized that many players were also discussing this matter. Most of the posts were filled with admiration and praise.

This story was also added into"Galaxy Chronicles"by the players and seeing the excessive praises and compliments, he felt quite relaxed and did not feel embarrassed.

Han Xiao browsed the forums in a joyful mood. Suddenly, he saw a post that he was quite concerned about.

This was an announcement post, and the content was the time for the next version update. Han Xiao did some calculations, and about nine months later, the players would receive a new update.

The players' event time in Version 5.0 was far from reaching the standard of the previous versions. Even the Pro League had not been held yet. However, the update this time was not a change in the larger version but a small update to Version 5.5.

In Han Xiao's previous life, there had been a few mini version updates like this, but in Han Xiao's memories, Version 5.0 did not have this update.

"Looks like it's my butterfly effect again."

Han Xiao was helpless.

Under his influence, the current storyline was completely different. Even the name of Version 5.0 had changed to [Age of Black Star], so it was not strange for the update time to change.

After all, every version update was based on some major event, which was automatically determined. Now, the World Tree would only arrive in the explored universe territory in ten years. He guessed that this was the reason for the mini update.

"It doesn't feel like a good change. I still want to see if I can increase my level."

Han Xiao rubbed his brows.

Although a mini version update could once again unlock the players' level cap, it was also because of this that the players' experience had an important consumption path, and he could not continue to harvest leeks with the highest efficiency.

Furthermore, the three Universal Civilizations were currently harassing the World Tree army, which was the time when they needed suicide squads the most. If the players went offline, there would be no more recyclable armed force.

"Looks like I have to make some preparations. I'll harvest them before they go offline."

The light of a scythe flashed in Han Xiao's eyes.

He was already familiar with this. The main point was to give the players sufficient motivation to clear the shopping cart.

Compared to selling supplies and equipment, the knowledge and skills of various classes were the main sources of harvesting EXP.

So… God help us all!

Nine months passed by in the blink of an eye. During this period, Han Xiao used all his tricks and promoted the items every day as though every day was a double 11 festival.

The players of the army were enjoying spending money, and their experience bars and wallets dried up at an unbelievable speed.

However, they were not sad at all. Instead, they were very happy. They felt that they had made a huge profit and it was worth it. They smiled like little flowers.

They spent money and even felt grateful…

After squeezing out a wave of players, Han Xiao's experience storage was much richer. As long as he did not use it to level up, he could use it for a long time. In his eyes, it was enough to cover the cost of many years of research.

On the day of the version update, many players went offline and disappeared. This caught the three Universal Civilizations off guard, but they quickly adjusted themselves. Changing to other troops to stop the World Tree Army would undoubtedly raise the war casualties.

After resolving the problem of the life form trading, Han Xiao did not continue to make trouble. He cooperated with the three Universal Civilizations to prepare for war, and time passed quickly.

There were no more accidents during the preparation period. The renovation of the Flickering World border was successfully completed, and the secondary dimension expedition army used the territory of the Realmless King as a transit station to continue searching for the World Tree's main body.

Under Han Xiao's guidance, most Beyond Grade As had varying degrees of progress, and a new batch of Beyond Grade As had been born from the Calamity Grade students in the training base.

In addition, many Beyond Grade A organizations had also completed their migration. With Han Xiao's signal, the Black Star Army moved away from the Flickering World, Shattered Star Ring territories, and temporarily withdrew from these two border areas to avoid additional losses in the war.

Year after year passed, and the distance between the World Tree and the Flickering World shortened day by day. The atmosphere of the explored universe became tenser and tenser.

Finally, on February 5, Galaxy Calendar Year 797, the shadow of the World Tree spread.

At the border of the Flickering World, which faced the unexplored universe, dense streams of light appeared and turned into an enormous World Tree fleet.

Countless soldiers of the World Tree looked at the galaxy outside the window, and what they saw was transmitted through the mind of the World Tree and into the mind of the Subduing Tree King who was guarding the base.

The Subduing Tree King sat on his throne with a cold glint in his eyes.

More than ten years had passed in the blink of an eye to him. The memory of him fighting Han Xiao felt like it was just yesterday.

Field battles were not the World Tree Civilization's strong suit. Invading the enemy civilization's territory was their biggest advantage. They could snowball through the World Tree's devouring ability that could consume all resources, killing all enemies.

The war is finally going to enter the rhythm that we are good at!

The Subduing Tree King tightened his grip and crushed the armrest of the throne. His voice was low and hoarse.

"I've finally found your territory… It's time for you to taste despair!"